<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0" version="8.0.0.0">
<wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Date:&lt;/strong&gt; February 24, 2009&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time:&lt;/strong&gt; 8:00 a.m. to 3:00 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location:&lt;/strong&gt; Hilton Washington, DC North/Gaithersburg, 620 Perry Parkway, Gaithersburg, MD 20877&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agenda&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p class="data"&gt;The Science Board will hear about and discuss updates from the agency on the continued assessment of Bisphenol A (BPA) in FDA-regulated products. The Science Board will hear about the plans for the following: (1) The review of FDA Center&amp;rsquo;s science programs, (2) the review of each Center&amp;rsquo;s projects within scientific priority areas, and (3) the handling of biospecimens used for genomic and proteomic analyses. The Science Board will also hear updates from two working groups on economically motivated adulteration of FDA-regulated products and rapid detection of Salmonella in foods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;a href="[!--$ssLink(&amp;quot;ucm115667.htm&amp;quot;)--]"&gt;Other Meeting Materials&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Public Participation Information&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interested persons may present data, information, or views, orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="mainlist"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Written submissions may be made to the contact person on or before February 17, 2009.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled approximately 1 p.m. and 2 p.m. on February 24, 2009. Those desiring to make formal oral presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before February 11, 2009.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Time allotted for each presentation may be limited. If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session. The contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by February 12, 2009.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;ul class="listspace"&gt;&lt;li class="data"&gt;Carlos Pena&lt;br /&gt;Office of Commisioner&lt;br /&gt;Food and Drug Administration&lt;br /&gt;5600 Fishers Lane, HF-33&lt;br /&gt;Rockville, MD&amp;nbsp; 20857&lt;br /&gt;Phone: 301-827-6687 FAX: 301-827-3042&lt;br /&gt;e-mail: &lt;a href="Carlos.Pena@fda.hhs.gov"&gt;Carlos.Pena@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="data"&gt;FDA Advisory Committee Information Line&lt;br /&gt;1-800-741-8138&lt;br /&gt;(301-443-0572 in the Washington, DC, area)&lt;br /&gt;code 8732310001&lt;br /&gt;Please call the Information Line for up-to-date information on this meeting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="data"&gt;Persons attending FDA&amp;rsquo;s advisory committee meetings are advised that the agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="data"&gt;FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical disabilities or special needs. If you require special accommodations due to a disability, please contact Carlos Pena' at least 7 days in advance of the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="data"&gt;Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5 U.S.C. app. 2).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="data" align="center"&gt;Updated February 10, 2009&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
