<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;table id="schedule" border="0" cellspacing="0" summary="This table shows the date, time, and location of the meeting" cellpadding="2" width="98%"&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th id="a1" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" width="12%" align="left"&gt;Center&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a2" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" width="22%" align="left"&gt;Date&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a3" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" width="29%" align="left"&gt;Time&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a4" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" width="37%" align="left"&gt;Location&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td height="61" valign="top" width="12%" headers="a1"&gt;CDER&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" width="22%" headers="a2"&gt;June 9, 2009&lt;br /&gt;June 10, 2009&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" width="29%" headers="a3"&gt;8:00 a.m. - 6:00 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;8:00 a.m. - 5:00 p.m.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" width="37%" headers="a4"&gt;Marriott Conference Centers&lt;br /&gt;UMUC Inn and Conference Center by Marriott&lt;br /&gt;3501 University Blvd. East&lt;br /&gt;Adelphi, Maryland&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agenda&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The committee will discuss safety and efficacy issues for the following new drug applications (NDA): 1) NDA 20-639/S-045 and S-046: Seroquel (quetiapine), AstraZeneca Pharmaceuticals LP, for (a) the acute treatment of schizophrenia in adolescents (13-17 years of age), and (b) the acute treatment of bipolar mania in children (10-12 years of age) and adolescents (13-17 years of age); 2) NDA 20-825/S-032: Geodon (ziprasidone), Pfizer Inc., for the acute treatment of manic or mixed episodes associated with bipolar disorder, with or without psychotic features in children and adolescents ages 10-17 years; and 3) NDA 20-592/S-040 and S-041: Zyprexa (olanzapine), Eli Lilly and Company, for (a) the acute treatment of manic or mixed episodes associated with bipolar I disorder, and (b) the acute treatment of schizophrenia in adolescents.&amp;nbsp; The committee will be asked to vote on whether or not these products have been shown to be effective and acceptably safe for these pediatric indications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Meeting Materials&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting.&amp;nbsp; If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA&amp;rsquo;s Web site after the meeting.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="[!--$ssLink(&amp;quot;ucm126199.htm&amp;quot;)--]"&gt;Background material&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Public Participation Information&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interested persons may present data, information, or views, orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Written submissions may be made to the contact person on or before May 26, 2009.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled between approximately 4 p.m. and 6 p.m. on June 9, 2009. Those desiring to make formal oral presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before May 22, 2009.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Time allotted for each presentation may be limited.&amp;nbsp; If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session.&amp;nbsp; The contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by May 26, 2009.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Diem-Kieu Ngo&lt;br /&gt;Center for Drug Evaluation and Research (HFD-21)&lt;br /&gt;Food and Drug Administration&lt;br /&gt;5600 Fishers Lane (for express delivery, Fishers Lane, rm. 1093)&lt;br /&gt;Rockville, MD 20857&lt;br /&gt;Phone: 301-827-7001&lt;br /&gt;Fax: 301-827-6776&lt;br /&gt;E-mail: &lt;a href="mailto:diem.ngo@fda.hhs.gov"&gt;diem.ngo@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;FDA Advisory Committee Information Line&lt;br /&gt;1-800-741-8138&lt;br /&gt;(301-443-0572 in the Washington DC area)&lt;br /&gt;Code: 3014512544&lt;br /&gt;Please call the Information Line for up-to-date information on this meeting.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;A notice in the Federal Register about last minute modifications that impact a previously announced advisory committee meeting cannot always be published quickly enough to provide timely notice. Therefore, you should always check the agency&amp;rsquo;s Website and call the appropriate advisory committee hot line/phone line to learn about possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting. If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA&amp;rsquo;s Web site after the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Persons attending FDA&amp;rsquo;s advisory committee meetings are advised that the agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets. FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical disabilities or special needs. If you require special accommodations due to a disability, please contact Diem Ngo at (301) 827-7001 at least 7 days in advance of the meeting. FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its advisory committee meetings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please visit our &lt;a href="[!--$ssNodeLink(&amp;quot;1840&amp;quot;)--]"&gt;Web site&lt;/a&gt; for procedures on public conduct during advisory committee meetings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5 U.S.C. app.2)&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
