<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;p&gt;DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH AND HUMAN SERVICES&lt;br /&gt;Food and Drug Administration&lt;br /&gt;[Docket No. FDA&amp;ndash;2009&amp;ndash;N&amp;ndash;0664]&lt;br /&gt;Radiological Devices Panel of the Medical Devices Advisory Committee;&lt;br /&gt;Notice of Meeting&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;AGENCY: Food and Drug Administration, HHS.&lt;br /&gt;ACTION: Notice.&lt;br /&gt;This notice announces a forthcoming meeting of a public advisory&lt;br /&gt;committee of the Food and Drug Administration (FDA). The meeting will be&lt;br /&gt;open to the public.&lt;br /&gt;Name of Committee: Radiological Devices Panel of the Medical Devices&lt;br /&gt;Advisory Committee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;General Function of the Committee: To provide advice and&lt;br /&gt;recommendations to the agency on FDA&amp;rsquo;s regulatory issues.&lt;br /&gt;Date and Time: The meeting will be held on November 17 and 18, 2009,&lt;br /&gt;from 8 a.m. to 5:30 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;Location: Holiday Inn, Ballroom, Two Montgomery Village Ave.,&lt;br /&gt;Gaithersburg, MD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Contact Person: Toby Lowe, Center for Devices and Radiological Health,&lt;br /&gt;Food and Drug Administration, 10903 New Hampshire Ave., Silver Spring, MD&lt;br /&gt;20993, 301&amp;ndash;796&amp;ndash;6512, or FDA Advisory Committee Information Line, 1&amp;ndash;800&amp;ndash;&lt;br /&gt;741&amp;ndash;8138 (301&amp;ndash;443&amp;ndash;0572 in the Washington, DC area), code 3014512526.&lt;br /&gt;Please call the Information Line for up-to-date information on this meeting.&lt;br /&gt;A notice in the Federal Register about last minute modifications that impact&lt;br /&gt;a previously announced advisory committee meeting cannot always be&lt;br /&gt;published quickly enough to provide timely notice. Therefore, you should&lt;br /&gt;always check the agency&amp;rsquo;s Web site and call the appropriate advisory&lt;br /&gt;committee hot line/phone line to learn about possible modifications before&lt;br /&gt;coming to the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Agenda: On November 17, 2009, the committee will discuss and make&lt;br /&gt;recommendations regarding the agency&amp;rsquo;s regulatory strategy for Full Field&lt;br /&gt;Digital Mammography (FFDM) Devices. The committee will discuss the public&lt;br /&gt;comments received in response to the publication of the draft guidance&lt;br /&gt;document entitled &amp;lsquo;&amp;lsquo;Class II Special Controls Guidance Document: Full Field&lt;br /&gt;Digital Mammography System.&amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo; This guidance document can be found on the&lt;br /&gt;FDA Web site at http://www.fda.gov/MedicalDevices/DeviceRegulation&lt;br /&gt;andGuidance/GuidanceDocuments/ucm107552.htm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On November 18, 2009, the committee will discuss and make&lt;br /&gt;recommendations regarding the agency&amp;rsquo;s regulatory strategy for computer assisted&lt;br /&gt;detection (CADe) devices for radiological devices. CADe devices are&lt;br /&gt;devices intended to identify, mark, highlight or in any other manner direct&lt;br /&gt;attention to potential abnormalities revealed in radiological data of the human&lt;br /&gt;body or imaging device data during interpretation of patient images or patient&lt;br /&gt;imaging data by a physician or other health care professional. The committee&lt;br /&gt;will discuss two draft guidance documents entitled &amp;lsquo;&amp;lsquo;Computer-Assisted&lt;br /&gt;Detection Devices Applied to Radiology Images and Radiology Device Data&amp;mdash;&lt;br /&gt;Premarket Notification [510(k)] Submissions&amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;&amp;lsquo;Clinical Performance&lt;br /&gt;Assessment: Considerations for Computer-Assisted Detection Devices Applied&lt;br /&gt;to Radiology Images and Radiology Device Data&amp;mdash;Premarket Approval (PMA)&lt;br /&gt;and Premarket Notification [510(k)] Submissions.&amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo; These guidance documents&lt;br /&gt;can be found on the FDA Web site at http://www.fda.gov/MedicalDevices/&lt;br /&gt;DeviceRegulationandGuidance/GuidanceDocuments. Type in the title of the&lt;br /&gt;guidance document included in this notice. The guidance documents will also&lt;br /&gt;be available as background materials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later&lt;br /&gt;than 2 business days before the meeting. If FDA is unable to post the&lt;br /&gt;background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background&lt;br /&gt;material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory&lt;br /&gt;committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA&amp;rsquo;s Web&lt;br /&gt;site after the meeting. Background material is available at http://www.fda.gov/&lt;br /&gt;AdvisoryCommittees/Calendar/default.htm. Scroll down to the appropriate&lt;br /&gt;advisory committee link.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Procedure: Interested persons may present data, information, or views,&lt;br /&gt;orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committee. Written&lt;br /&gt;submissions may be made to the contact person on or before November 12,&lt;br /&gt;2009. Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled between&lt;br /&gt;approximately 1 p.m. and 2 p.m. on both days. Those desiring to make formal&lt;br /&gt;oral presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief&lt;br /&gt;statement of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to&lt;br /&gt;present, the names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication&lt;br /&gt;of the approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before&lt;br /&gt;November 6, 2009. Time allotted for each presentation may be limited. If the&lt;br /&gt;number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably&lt;br /&gt;accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may&lt;br /&gt;conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public&lt;br /&gt;hearing session. The contact person will notify interested persons regarding&lt;br /&gt;their request to speak by November 9, 2009.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Persons attending FDA&amp;rsquo;s advisory committee meetings are advised that the&lt;br /&gt;agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets.&lt;br /&gt;FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee&lt;br /&gt;meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical&lt;br /&gt;disabilities or special needs. If you require special accommodations due to a&lt;br /&gt;disability, please contact AnnMarie Williams, Conference Management Staff,&lt;br /&gt;301&amp;ndash;796&amp;ndash;5966, at least 7 days in advance of the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its advisory committee&lt;br /&gt;meetings. Please visit our Web site at http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/&lt;br /&gt;AboutAdvisoryCommittees/ucm111462.htm for procedures on public conduct&lt;br /&gt;during advisory committee meetings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act&lt;br /&gt;(5 U.S.C. app. 2).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dated: October 16, 2009.&lt;br /&gt;David Horowitz,&lt;br /&gt;Assistant Commissioner for Policy.&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
