<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;table cellspacing="4" cellpadding="4"&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td valign="top" width="15%" style="text-align: left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Name of Committee&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Ophthalmic Devices Panel&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td valign="top" width="15%" style="text-align: left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Date and Time&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;The meeting was held on the following dates:&lt;br /&gt;Mar 27, 09 8:00 AM - 5:00 PM&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td valign="top" width="15%" style="text-align: left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Hilton Washington DC North/Gaithersburg, Salons A,B and C&lt;br /&gt;620 Perry Pkwy.&lt;br /&gt;Gaithersburg , MD&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td valign="top" width="15%" style="text-align: left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;James Swink, Center for Devices and Radiological Health, Food and Drug Administration, 9200 Corporate Blvd., Rockville, MD 20850, 240-276-4050, or FDA Advisory Committee Information Line, 1-800-741-8138 (301-443-0572 in the Washington, DC area), code 3014512396.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please call the Information Line for up-to-date information on this meeting. A notice in the FEDERAL REGISTER about last minute modifications that impact a previously announced advisory committee meeting cannot always be published quickly enough to provide timely notice. Therefore, you should always check the agency&amp;rsquo;s Web site and call the appropriate advisory committee hot line/phone line to learn about possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td valign="top" width="15%" style="text-align: left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agenda&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;The committee will discuss, make recommendations, and vote on a premarket approval application, sponsored by VisionCare Technologies, Inc., for an implantable miniature telescope (IMT&amp;trade;). The IMT&amp;trade; is indicated for monocular implant in patients greater than 65 years of age with stable moderate to profound central vision impairment, i.e., distance BCVA of 20/80 to 20/800, due to bilateral central scotomas associated with end-stage macular degeneration, defined as retinal findings of geographic atrophy or disciform scar, with foveal involvement as determined by fluorescein angiography and evidence of cataract. FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting. If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA&amp;rsquo;s Web site after the meeting. Background material is available at http://www.fda.gov/ohrms/dockets/ac/acmenu.htm, click on the year 2009 and scroll down to the appropriate advisory committee link.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td valign="top" width="15%" style="text-align: left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Procedure&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Interested persons may present data, information, or views, orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committee. Written submissions may be made to the contact person on or before March 20, 2009. Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled between approximately 9:30 a.m. and 10 a.m., and between approximately 3:30 p.m. and 4 p.m. Those desiring to make formal oral presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before March 18, 2009. Time allotted for each presentation may be limited. If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session. The contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by March 19, 2009.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td valign="top" width="15%" style="text-align: left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Persons attending FDA&amp;rsquo;s advisory committee meetings are advised that the agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td valign="top" width="15%" style="text-align: left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conduct&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its advisory committee meetings.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Information about procedures on public conduct during advisory committee meetings: &lt;a href="/FDAgov/AdvisoryCommittees/AboutAdvisoryCommittees/ucm111462.htm"&gt;Public Conduct During FDA Advisory Committee Meetings&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="[!--$ssLink(&amp;quot;ucm147051.htm&amp;quot;)--]"&gt;Materials for this Meeting (March 27, 2009: Ophthalmic Devices Panel Meeting)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
