<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;p&gt;This notice announces a forthcoming meeting of a public advisory committee of the Food and Drug Administration (FDA). At least one portion of the meeting will be closed to the public.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Name of Committee: Circulatory System Devices Panel of the Medical Devices Advisory Committee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;General Function of the Committee: To provide advice and recommendations to the agency on FDA&amp;rsquo;s regulatory issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Date and Time: The meeting will be held on July 22 and 23, 2009, from 8 a.m. to 6 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Location: Hilton Washington DC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;North/Gaithersburg, Salons A, B and C,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;620 Perry Pkwy., Gaithersburg, MD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Contact Person: James Swink, Center&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;for Devices and Radiological Health&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(HFZ&amp;ndash;450), Food and Drug&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Administration, 9200 Corporate Blvd.,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rockville, MD 20850, 240&amp;ndash;276&amp;ndash;4050, or&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA Advisory Committee Information&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Line, 1&amp;ndash;800&amp;ndash;741&amp;ndash;8138 (301&amp;ndash;443&amp;ndash;0572&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;in the Washington, DC area), code 3014512625. Please call the Information Line for up-to-date information on this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;meeting. A notice in the Federal Register about last minute modifications&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;that impact a previously announced advisory committee meeting cannot&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;always be published quickly enough to provide timely notice. Therefore, you&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;should always check the agency&amp;rsquo;s Web site and call the appropriate advisory&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;committee hot line/phone line to learn about possible modifications before&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;coming to the meeting.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Agenda: On July 22, 2009, the committee will discuss, make&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;recommendations, and vote on a Humanitarian Device Exemption (HDE)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;application, sponsored by Medtronic, Inc., for the MEDTRONIC MELODY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Transcatheter Pulmonary Valve (Model PB10) and MEDTRONIC ENSEMBLE&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Transcatheter Valve Delivery System (NU10). The MEDTRONIC MELODY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Transcatheter Pulmonary Valve (Model PB10) and MEDTRONIC ENSEMBLE&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Transcatheter Valve Delivery System (NU10) is indicated for use in patients&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;with the following clinical conditions: Regurgitant (insufficient or leaky)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Right Ventricular Outflow Tract (RVOT)&amp;mdash;The right ventricular&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;outflow tract is that portion of the right ventricle leading up to the&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;pulmonary valve and pulmonary artery. When the ventricles&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;contract, blood moves along the outflow tract and through the&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;pulmonary valve; blood then flows to the lungs where gas exchange&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;takes place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conduits&amp;mdash;In the context of this device, a surgically implanted tube&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;that allows blood to pass from the heart to the pulmonary arteries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stenotic (stiff valve leaflets that cannot open or close properly)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;RVOT conduits where the risk of worsening regurgitation is a relative&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;contraindication to balloon dilatation or stenting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Existence of a full (circumferential) RVOT conduit that was equal to or greater than 16&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;millimeters (mm) in diameter when riginally implanted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On July 23, 2009, from 8 a.m. to 10a.m., and from 1 p.m. to 6 p.m., the&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;committee will discuss general questions about adhesion barriers for&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;cardiovascular use. Some of these questions will focus on understanding&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;the target population (pediatric and/or adult) that would benefit from these&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;devices and the development of appropriate endpoints for a clinical trial.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;than 2 business days before the meeting. If FDA is unable to post the background&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA&amp;rsquo;s Web site after&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;the meeting.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Procedure: On July 22, 2009, from 8 a.m. to 6 p.m., and on July 23, 2009,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;from 8 a.m. to 10 a.m. and from 1 p.m. to 6 p.m., the meeting is open to the&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;public. Interested persons may present data, information, or views, orally or in&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;writing, on issues pending before the committee. Written submissions may be&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;made to the contact person on or before July 15, 2009. Oral presentations from&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;the public will be scheduled approximately 30 minutes at the&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;beginning of committee deliberations and approximately 30 minutes near the&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;end of the deliberations. Those desiring to make formal oral presentations&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;requested to make their presentation on r before July 7, 2009. Time allotted for&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;each presentation may be limited. If the number of registrants requesting to&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session. The contact person will&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by July 8, 2009.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Closed Presentation of Data: On July 23, 2009, from 10 a.m. to 12 noon, the&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;meeting will be closed to permit discussion and review of trade secret&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;and confidential commercial information (5 U.S.C. 552b(c)(4)) related&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;to the design of a potential clinical trial. Persons attending FDA&amp;rsquo;s advisory&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;committee meetings are advised that the agency is not responsible for providing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;access to electrical outlets. FDA welcomes the attendance of the&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;public at its advisory committee meetings and will make every effort to&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;accommodate persons with physical disabilities or special needs. If you&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;require special accommodations due to a disability, please contact AnnMarie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Williams, Conference Management Staff, at 240&amp;ndash;276&amp;ndash;8932, at least 7 days&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;in advance of the meeting.FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;advisory committee meetings. Please visit our Web site at &lt;a href="[!--$ssLink(&amp;quot;ucm111462.htm&amp;quot;)--]"&gt;http://www.fda.gov/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="[!--$ssLink(&amp;quot;ucm111462.htm&amp;quot;)--]"&gt;AdvisoryCommittees/AboutAdvisoryCommittees/ucm111462.htm&lt;/a&gt; for procedures on&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;public conduct during advisory committee meetings. Notice of this meeting is given under&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5U.S.C. app. 2).&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
