<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;p&gt;DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH AND&lt;br /&gt;HUMAN SERVICES&lt;br /&gt;Food and Drug Administration&lt;br /&gt;[Docket No. FDA&amp;ndash;2009&amp;ndash;N&amp;ndash;0664]&lt;br /&gt;Gastroenterology and Urology Devices Panel of the Medical Devices Advisory&lt;br /&gt;Committee; Notice of Meeting&lt;br /&gt;AGENCY: Food and Drug Administration, HHS.&lt;br /&gt;ACTION: Notice.&lt;br /&gt;This notice announces a forthcoming meeting of a public advisory committee&lt;br /&gt;of the Food and Drug Administration (FDA). The meeting will be open to the&lt;br /&gt;public. Name of Committee: Gastroenterology and Urology Devices Panel of the&lt;br /&gt;Medical Devices Advisory Committee. General Function of the Committee:&lt;br /&gt;To provide advice and recommendations to the agency on&lt;br /&gt;FDA&amp;rsquo;s regulatory issues. Date and Time: The meeting will be&lt;br /&gt;held on December 11, 2009, from 8 a.m.&lt;br /&gt;to 5 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location: Holiday Inn, Ballroom, Two&lt;br /&gt;Montgomery Village Ave., Gaithersburg, MD.&lt;br /&gt;Contact Person: Megan M. Mickal,&lt;br /&gt;Center for Devices and Radiological&lt;br /&gt;Health, Food and Drug Administration,&lt;br /&gt;10903 New Hampshire Ave., Silver Spring, MD, 20993, 301&amp;ndash;796&amp;ndash;5590, or&lt;br /&gt;FDA Advisory Committee Information Line, 1&amp;ndash;800&amp;ndash;741&amp;ndash;8138 (301&amp;ndash;443&amp;ndash;0572 in the&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Washington, DC area),&amp;nbsp;code 3014512523. Please call the Information Line for up-to-date&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;information on this meeting. A notice in the Federal Register about last minute modifications&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;that impact a previously announced advisory committee meeting cannot always be published&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;quickly enough to provide timely notice. Therefore, you should always check the agency&amp;rsquo;s Web&lt;br /&gt;site and call the appropriate advisory committee hot line/phone line to learn&lt;br /&gt;about possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Agenda: On December 11, 2009, the committee will discuss and make&lt;br /&gt;recommendations on the study designs and endpoints of clinical investigations&lt;br /&gt;intended to support approval or clearance of devices indicated for the&lt;br /&gt;primary treatment of localized prostate cancer.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later&lt;br /&gt;than 2 business days before the meeting. If FDA is unable to post the background&lt;br /&gt;material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will&lt;br /&gt;be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee&lt;br /&gt;meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA&amp;rsquo;s Web site after&lt;br /&gt;the meeting. Background material is available at http://www.fda.gov/&lt;br /&gt;AdvisoryCommittees/Calendar/ default.htm. Scroll down to the&lt;br /&gt;appropriate advisory committee link. Procedure: Interested persons may&lt;br /&gt;present data, information, or views, orally or in writing, on issues pending&lt;br /&gt;before the committee. Written submissions may be made to the contact&lt;br /&gt;person on or before December 1, 2009.&lt;br /&gt;Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled between approximately 1&lt;br /&gt;p.m. and 2 p.m. Those desiring to make formal oral presentations should notify&lt;br /&gt;the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the&lt;br /&gt;evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of&lt;br /&gt;proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time&lt;br /&gt;requested to make their presentation on or before November 23, 2009. Time&lt;br /&gt;allotted for each presentation may be limited. If the number of registrants&lt;br /&gt;requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the&lt;br /&gt;scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine&lt;br /&gt;the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session. The contact&lt;br /&gt;person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by&lt;br /&gt;November 24, 2009.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Persons attending FDA&amp;rsquo;s advisory committee meetings are advised that the&lt;br /&gt;agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets.&lt;br /&gt;FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee&lt;br /&gt;meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical&lt;br /&gt;disabilities or special needs. If you require special accommodations due to&lt;br /&gt;a disability, please contact AnnMarie Williams, Conference Management&lt;br /&gt;Staff, 301&amp;ndash;796&amp;ndash;5966, at least 7 days in advance of the meeting.&lt;br /&gt;FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its advisory committee&lt;br /&gt;meetings. Please visit our Web site at http://www.fda.gov/Advisory&lt;br /&gt;Committees/AboutAdvisoryCommittees/ucm111462.htm for procedures on&lt;br /&gt;public conduct during advisory committee meetings.&lt;br /&gt;Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5&lt;br /&gt;U.S.C. app. 2).&lt;br /&gt;Dated: October 27, 2009.&lt;br /&gt;David Horowitz,&lt;br /&gt;Assistant Commissioner for Policy.&lt;br /&gt;[FR Doc. E9&amp;ndash;26259 Filed 10&amp;ndash;30&amp;ndash;09; 8:45 am]&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
