<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;table width="98%"&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr bgcolor="#cccccc"&gt;&lt;th scope="col" style="text-align: center; vertical-align: top"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Center&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th scope="col" style="text-align: center; vertical-align: top"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Date&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th scope="col" style="text-align: center; vertical-align: top"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th scope="col" style="text-align: center; vertical-align: top"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td style="text-align: center; vertical-align: top"&gt;OC&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td style="text-align: center; vertical-align: top"&gt;August 17, 2009&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td style="text-align: center; vertical-align: top"&gt;8:00 a.m. - 4:00 p.m.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td style="text-align: left"&gt;Hilton, Washington DC/Rockville&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;Executive Meeting Center&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;1750 Rockville Pike,&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;Rockville, Maryland, 20852&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;h5&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agenda&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Science Board will hear about and discuss reports from its subcommittees on the following: (1) the review of research at the Center for Veterinary Medicine, and (2) the review of FDA&amp;rsquo;s scientific information technology infrastructure modernization initiatives. The Science Board will hear about plans to establish an additional subcommittee for the review of research at the Center for Food Safety and Applied Nutrition. The Science board will also hear about and discuss updates from the agency regarding the continued assessment of Bisphenol-A (BPA) in FDA-regulated products.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More complete information about the topics on which FDA will seek public input will be available by or around August 13, 2009 at&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="[!--$ssLink(&amp;quot;ucm115667.htm&amp;quot;)--]"&gt;Science Board to the Food and Drug Administration 2009 Meeting Materials page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h5&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meeting Materials&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA intends to make the complete background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting. If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA&amp;rsquo;s Web site after the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="[!--$ssLink(&amp;quot;ucm115667.htm&amp;quot;)--]"&gt;Background materia&lt;/a&gt;l&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h5&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Public Participation and Sponsor Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interested persons and Sponsors (representatives from industry) may present data, information, or views, orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Written submissions may be made to the contact person on or before August 10, 2009. Comments received on or before August 13, 2009, will be provided to the committee before the meeting.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Oral presentations from the public (excluding Sponsors) will be scheduled between approximately 1 p.m. and 2 p.m. on August 17, 2009. Those desiring to make formal oral presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before July 31, 2009.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Time allotted for each presentation may be limited. If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session. The contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by August 3, 2009.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h5&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Carlos Pe&amp;ntilde;a, PhD, MS&lt;br /&gt;Office of Science and Health Coordination&lt;br /&gt;Office of the Commissioner (HF&amp;ndash;33)&lt;br /&gt;Food and Drug Administration&lt;br /&gt;5600 Fishers Lane (for express delivery, rm. 14B&amp;ndash;08)&lt;br /&gt;Rockville, MD 20857&lt;br /&gt;Phone: 301&amp;ndash;827&amp;ndash;6687&lt;br /&gt;Fax: 301-827-6776&lt;br /&gt;E-mail: &lt;a href="mailto:carlos.pena@fda.hhs.gov"&gt;carlos.pe&amp;ntilde;a@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;FDA Advisory Committee Information Line&lt;br /&gt;1-800-741-8138&lt;br /&gt;(301-443-0572 in the Washington DC area)&lt;br /&gt;Code:8732310001&lt;br /&gt;Please call the Information Line for up-to-date information on this meeting.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;A notice in the Federal Register about last minute modifications that impact a previously announced advisory committee meeting cannot always be published quickly enough to provide timely notice. Therefore, you should always check the agency&amp;rsquo;s Website and call the appropriate advisory committee hot line/phone line to learn about possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting. If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA&amp;rsquo;s Web site after the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Persons attending FDA&amp;rsquo;s advisory committee meetings are advised that the agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets. FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical disabilities or special needs. If you require special accommodations due to a disability, please contact Carlos Pe&amp;ntilde;a, PhD, MS at (301) 827-3340 at least 7 days in advance of the meeting. FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its advisory committee meetings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please visit our Web site at &lt;a href="http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/AboutAdvisoryCommittees/ucm111462.htm"&gt;http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/AboutAdvisoryCommittees/ucm111462.htm&lt;/a&gt; for procedures on public conduct during advisory committee meetings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5 U.S.C. app.2).&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
