<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;table cellspacing="0" summary="meeting date, time, location and sponsoring Center" cellpadding="5"&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr valign="top" align="left"&gt;&lt;td&gt;CBER&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;June 12, 2009&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;June 12, 2009 from 8:00 a.m. to 5:45 p.m.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Holiday Inn Gaithersburg, Grand Ballroom, 2 Montgomery Village Ave. Gaithersburg, Maryland 20879&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Agenda&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;On June 12, 2009, the Committee will review and discuss a recent report from the UK Health Protection Agency attributing a case of variant Creutzfeldt-Jakob (vCJD) disease infection to treatment 11 years earlier with a &amp;ldquo;vCJD-implicated&amp;rdquo; plasma-derived coagulation factor VIII (pdFVIII) and whether this information or any other recent scientific information about the vCJD epidemic substantially alters FDA&amp;rsquo;s risk assessment for US-licensed preparations of pdFVIII products. In the afternoon the committee will hear informational presentations on animal models of vCJD, diagnostic test development for transmissible spongiform encephalopathies (TSEs) and bovine spongiform encephalopathy (BSE) surveillance and risk management. FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting. If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA&amp;rsquo;s Web site after the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;a href="[!--$ssLink(&amp;quot;ucm129559.htm&amp;quot;)--]"&gt;Meeting Materials&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Public Participation Information&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interested persons may present data, information, or views, orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Written submissions may be made to the contact person on or before June 4, 2009.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled between approximately 10:30 a.m. and 11:15 a.m. and between 5:00 p.m. and 5:30 p.m. Those desiring to make formal oral presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before May 26, 2009. Time allotted for each presentation may be limited. If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session. The contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by May 28, 2009.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Contact Information&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;William Freas, Ph.D.&lt;br /&gt;1401 Rockville Pike, HFM-71, Rockville, MD 20852&lt;br /&gt;301-827-1295&lt;br /&gt;FAX: 301-827-0294&lt;br /&gt;e-mail: &lt;a href="mailto:william.freas@fda.hhs.gov"&gt;william.freas@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;FDA Advisory Committee Information Line&lt;br /&gt;1-800-741-8138 (301-443-0572 in the Washington, DC, area)&lt;br /&gt;code 3014512392&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please call the Information Line for up-to-date information on this meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting. If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA&amp;rsquo;s Web site after the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A notice in the Federal Register about last minute modifications that impact a previously announced advisory committee meeting cannot always be published quickly enough to provide timely notice. Therefore, you should always check the agency&amp;rsquo;s Web site and call the appropriate advisory committee hot line/phone line to learn about possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Persons attending FDA's advisory committee meetings are advised that the agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical disabilities or special needs. If you require special accommodations due to a disability, please contact William Freas or Rosanna Harvey at least 7 days in advance of the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its advisory committee meetings. &lt;a href="[!--$ssNodeLink(&amp;quot;1840&amp;quot;)--]"&gt;Please visit our Web site&lt;/a&gt; for procedures on public conduct during advisory committee meetings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5 U.S.C. app. 2).&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
