<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;table id="schedule" border="0" cellspacing="0" summary="This table shows the date, time, and location of the meeting" cellpadding="2" style="width: 100%"&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th id="a1" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" width="10%" align="left"&gt;Center&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a2" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" width="25%" align="left"&gt;Date&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a3" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" width="25%" align="left"&gt;Time&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a4" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" width="40%" align="left"&gt;Location&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td valign="top" width="10%" headers="a1"&gt;OC&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" width="25%" headers="a2"&gt;December 6, 2010&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" width="25%" headers="a3"&gt;8:00 a.m. - 6:00 p.m.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" width="40%" headers="a4"&gt;Bethesda Marriott&lt;br /&gt;5151 Pooks Hill Road&lt;br /&gt;Bethesda, MD 20814&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agenda&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Pediatric Advisory Committee (PAC) will meet to discuss donor and banked human milk. FDA is convening the meeting to obtain and discuss information and data that will provide the Agency with a better understanding of current practices, and potential benefits and risks associated with the donation and banking of human milk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA recognizes the benefits associated with breastfeeding, and is focusing this meeting on issues related to banking human milk. Human milk is banked for use by infants in need of donated milk. The agenda for the meeting will include presentations and discussions on the benefits and risks of human milk banking practices as they relate to pre-term and term infant populations. Topics will include, but not be limited to, infectious disease risks, State regulations and current practices in donor and human milk banking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meeting Materials&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting. If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA&amp;rsquo;s Web site after the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Background material&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','ucm201871.htm')--]"&gt;2010 Meeting Materials, Pediatric Advisory Committee &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Public Participation and Sponsor Information&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interested persons and Sponsors (representatives from industry) may present data, information, or views, orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Written submissions may be made to the contact person on or before November 29, 2010. Comments received on or before November 29, 2010, will be provided to the committee before the meeting.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Oral presentations from the public (excluding Sponsors) will be scheduled between approximately 1 p.m. and 2 p.m for each day. Those desiring to make formal oral presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before November 18, 2010.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Time allotted for each presentation may be limited. If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session. The contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by November 19, 2010.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comments&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA is opening a docket to allow for additional public comments to be submitted to the Agency on the issues before the Pediatric Advisory Committee beginning October 28, 2010, and closing January 6, 2011.&amp;nbsp; All comments received on or before November 29, 2010, will be provided to the committee members.&amp;nbsp;All comments received after November 29, 2010, will be taken into consideration by the Agency.&amp;nbsp; Interested persons are encouraged to use the docket to submit either electronic or written comments regarding this meeting (see ADDRESSES).&amp;nbsp; &lt;a target="_blank" href="[!--$ssExternalLink('UCM231428')--]"&gt;Submit electronic comments to Regulations.gov&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp; Submit written comments to the Division of Dockets Management, Food and Drug Administration, 5630 Fishers Lane, RM 1061, Rockville, MD 20852.&amp;nbsp; It is only necessary to send one set of comments.&amp;nbsp; Identify comments with the docket number found in brackets in the heading of this document.&amp;nbsp; Received comments may be seen in the Division of Dockets Management between 9 a.m. and 4 p.m.&amp;nbsp; Monday through Friday&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Walter Ellenberg, Ph.D.&lt;br /&gt;Office of Pediatric Therapeutics&lt;br /&gt;Office of the Commissioner&lt;br /&gt;Food and Drug Administration&lt;br /&gt;Bldg. 32, Room 5154&lt;br /&gt;10903 New Hampshire Ave.&lt;br /&gt;Silver Spring, Maryland 20993&lt;br /&gt;Phone: 301&amp;ndash;796-0885&lt;br /&gt;Fax: 301-847-8640&lt;br /&gt;E-mail: &lt;a href="mailto:walter.ellenberg@fda.hhs.gov"&gt;walter.ellenberg@fda.hhs.gov &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul type="disc"&gt;&lt;li&gt;FDA Advisory Committee Information Line&lt;br /&gt;1-800-741-8138&lt;br /&gt;(301-443-0572 in the Washington DC area)&lt;br /&gt;Code: 8732310001&lt;br /&gt;Please call the Information Line for up-to-date information on this meeting.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;A notice in the Federal Register about last minute modifications that impact a previously announced advisory committee meeting cannot always be published quickly enough to provide timely notice. Therefore, you should always check the agency&amp;rsquo;s Web site and call the appropriate advisory committee hot line/phone line to learn about possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting. If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA&amp;rsquo;s Web site after the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Persons attending FDA&amp;rsquo;s advisory committee meetings are advised that the agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets. FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical disabilities or special needs. If you require special accommodations due to a disability, please contact Walter Ellenberg at (301) 796-0885 at least 7 days in advance of the meeting. FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its advisory committee meetings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please visit our Web site for &lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','ucm111462.htm')--]"&gt;procedures on public conduct during advisory committee meetings&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5 U.S.C. app.2).&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
