<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;table id="schedule" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="2" summary="This table shows the date, time, and location of the meeting" border="0" style="width: 100%"&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th id="a1" valign="top" align="left" width="10%" bgcolor="#cccccc"&gt;Center&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a2" valign="top" align="left" width="25%" bgcolor="#cccccc"&gt;Date&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a3" valign="top" align="left" width="25%" bgcolor="#cccccc"&gt;Time&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a4" valign="top" align="left" width="40%" bgcolor="#cccccc"&gt;Location&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td valign="top" headers="a1" width="10%"&gt;OC&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" headers="a2" width="25%"&gt;January 30, 2012&lt;br /&gt;January 31, 2012&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" headers="a3" width="25%"&gt;8:00 a.m. - 6:00 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;9:00 a.m.- 12:00 p.m. &lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" headers="a4" width="40%"&gt;Hilton Gaithersburg Hotel&lt;br /&gt;620 Perry Pkwy.&lt;br /&gt;Gaithersburg, MD 20877&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Agenda&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Monday, January 30, 2012, The Pediatric Advisory Committee will meet to discuss pediatric-focused safety reviews, as mandated by the Best Pharmaceuticals for Children Act and the Pediatric Research Equity Act for Focalin XR (dexmethylphenidate hydrochloride), Daytrana (methylphenidate), Seroquel (quetiapine fumarate), Pancreaze (pancrelipase amylase), Zenpep (pancrelipase lipase), Creon (pancrelipase protease), Xerese cream 5%/1% (acyclovir and hydrocortisone), Xolair (omalizumab), Benicar (olmesartan medoxomil), Atacand (candesartan cilexetil), Mirena (levonorgestrel&amp;mdash;releasing intrauterine system), Plan B One Step (levonorgestrel), and Flomax (tamsulosin hydrochloride).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Tuesday, January 31, 2012, the Pediatric Advisory Committee will meet to discuss pediatric-focused safety reviews, as mandated by the Best Pharmaceuticals for Children Act and the Pediatric Research Equity Act, for Prevnar 13 (Pneumococcal 13-valent Conjugate Vaccine [Diphtheria CRM197 Protein]), and Cervarix [Human Papillomavirus Bivalent (Types 16 and 18) vaccine, recombinant].&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meeting Materials&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA intends to make the complete set of background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting. If FDA is unable to post the background material on its website prior to the meeting, all efforts will be made to try and provide the background material at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA&amp;rsquo;s Web site after the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul type="disc"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Background material&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;ul type="circle"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM283814')--]"&gt;2012 Meeting Materials, Pediatric Advisory Committee&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Public Participation and Sponsor Information&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interested persons may present data, information, or views, orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committee. Written submissions may be made to the contact person on or before January 24, 2012. Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled between approximately 1 p.m. and 2 p.m. on January 30, 2012. Those individuals interested in making formal oral presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before January 16, 2012.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Time allotted for each presentation may be limited. If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session. The contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by January 17, 2012.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Persons attending FDA&amp;rsquo;s advisory committee meetings are advised that the Agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical disabilities or special needs. If you require special accommodations due to a disability, please notify Walter Ellenberg at least 7 days in advance of the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its advisory committee meetings. Please visit our Web site at &lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM111462')--]"&gt;http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/AboutAdvisoryCommittees/ucm111462.htm&lt;/a&gt; for procedures on public conduct during advisory committee meetings.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Walter Ellenberg, Ph.D.&lt;br /&gt;Office of Pediatric Therapeutics&lt;br /&gt;Office of the Commissioner&lt;br /&gt;Food and Drug Administration&lt;br /&gt;Bldg. 32, Room 5154&lt;br /&gt;10903 New Hampshire Ave..&lt;br /&gt;Silver Spring, Maryland 20993-0002&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Phone: 301&amp;ndash;796-0885&lt;br /&gt;Fax: 301-847-8640&lt;br /&gt;E-mail: &lt;a href="mailto:walter.ellenberg@fda.hhs.gov"&gt;walter.ellenberg@fda.hhs.gov &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;FDA Advisory Committee Information Line&lt;br /&gt;1-800-741-8138&lt;br /&gt;(301-443-0572 in the Washington DC area)&lt;br /&gt;Code: 8732310001&lt;br /&gt;Please call the Information Line for up-to-date information on this meeting.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5 U.S.C. app.2).&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
