<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;NOTE:&lt;/b&gt; The meeting of the General and Plastic Surgery Devices Panel of the Medical Devices Advisory Committee scheduled for August 26, 2010, is postponed. The meeting was announced in the Federal Register of June 24, 2010 (75 FR 36102). The meeting is postponed so that FDA can review and consider additional information that was submitted. A future meeting date will be announced in the Federal Register at a later date.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr /&gt;&lt;p&gt;DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH AND HUMAN SERVICES&lt;br /&gt;Food and Drug Administration&lt;br /&gt;[Docket No. FDA&amp;ndash;2010&amp;ndash;N&amp;ndash;0001]&lt;br /&gt;General and Plastic Surgery Devices Panel of the Medical Devices Advisory&lt;br /&gt;Committee; Notice of Meeting&lt;br /&gt;AGENCY: Food and Drug Administration, HHS.&lt;br /&gt;ACTION: Notice.&lt;br /&gt;This notice announces a forthcoming meeting of a public advisory&lt;br /&gt;committee of the Food and Drug Administration (FDA). The meeting will be&lt;br /&gt;open to the public.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Name of Committee: General and Plastic Surgery Devices Panel of the&lt;br /&gt;Medical Devices Advisory Committee.&lt;br /&gt;General Function of the Committee: To provide advice and&lt;br /&gt;recommendations to the agency on FDA&amp;rsquo;s regulatory issues.&lt;br /&gt;Date and Time: The meeting will be held on August 26, 2010, from 8 a.m.&lt;br /&gt;to 6 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Location: Holiday Inn College Park, Grand Ballroom, 10000 Baltimore Ave.,&lt;br /&gt;College Park, MD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Contact Person: Margaret McCabe-Janicki, Food and Drug Administration,&lt;br /&gt;Center for Devices and Radiological Health, 10903 New Hampshire Ave., Bldg.&lt;br /&gt;66, rm. 1535, Silver Spring, MD 20993&amp;ndash;0002, 301&amp;ndash;796&amp;ndash;7029, or FDA Advisory&lt;br /&gt;Committee Information Line, 1&amp;ndash;800&amp;ndash;741&amp;ndash;8138 (301&amp;ndash;443&amp;ndash;0572 in the&lt;br /&gt;Washington, DC area), code 3014512519. Please call the Information Line for&lt;br /&gt;up-to-date information on this meeting. A notice in the Federal Register about&lt;br /&gt;last minute modifications that impact a previously announced advisory&lt;br /&gt;committee meeting cannot always be published quickly enough to provide&lt;br /&gt;timely notice. Therefore, you should always check the agency&amp;rsquo;s Web site and&lt;br /&gt;call the appropriate advisory committee hot line/phone line to learn about&lt;br /&gt;possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&lt;br /&gt;Agenda: On August 26, 2010, the committee will discuss, make&lt;br /&gt;recommendations, and vote on premarket approval application for MelaFind,&lt;br /&gt;sponsored by MELA Sciences, Inc. MelaFind is a non-invasive computer vision&lt;br /&gt;system intended to assist in the evaluation of pigmented skin lesions,&lt;br /&gt;including atypical moles, which have one or more clinical or historical&lt;br /&gt;characteristics of melanoma, before a final decision to biopsy has been&lt;br /&gt;rendered. MelaFind acquires and displays multi-spectral (from blue to near&lt;br /&gt;infrared) digital images of pigmented skin lesions and uses automatic image&lt;br /&gt;analysis and statistical pattern recognition to help identify lesions to be&lt;br /&gt;considered for biopsy to rule out melanoma.&lt;br /&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later&lt;br /&gt;than 2 business days before the meeting. If FDA is unable to post the&lt;br /&gt;background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background&lt;br /&gt;material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory&lt;br /&gt;committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA&amp;rsquo;s Web&lt;br /&gt;site after the meeting. Background material is available at http://www.fda.gov/&lt;br /&gt;AdvisoryCommittees/Calendar/default.htm. Scroll down to the appropriate&lt;br /&gt;advisory committee link.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Procedure: Interested persons may present data, information, or views,&lt;br /&gt;orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committee. Written&lt;br /&gt;submissions may be made to the contact person on or before August 17, 2010.&lt;br /&gt;Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled between approximately&lt;br /&gt;1 p.m. and 2 p.m. Those desiring to make formal oral presentations should&lt;br /&gt;notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature&lt;br /&gt;of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses&lt;br /&gt;of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested&lt;br /&gt;to make their presentation on or before August 5, 2010. Time allotted for each&lt;br /&gt;presentation may be limited. If the number of registrants requesting to speak&lt;br /&gt;is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open&lt;br /&gt;public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers&lt;br /&gt;for the scheduled open public hearing session. The contact person will notify&lt;br /&gt;interested persons regarding their request to speak by August 10, 2010.&lt;br /&gt;Persons attending FDA&amp;rsquo;s advisory committee meetings are advised that the&lt;br /&gt;agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets.&lt;br /&gt;FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee&lt;br /&gt;meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical&lt;br /&gt;disabilities or special needs. If you require special accommodations due to a&lt;br /&gt;disability, please contact AnnMarie Williams, Conference Management Staff,&lt;br /&gt;at 301&amp;ndash;796&amp;ndash;5966, at least 7 days in advance of the meeting.&lt;br /&gt;FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its advisory committee&lt;br /&gt;meetings. Please visit our Web site at http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/&lt;br /&gt;AboutAdvisoryCommittees/ucm111462.htm for procedures on public conduct&lt;br /&gt;during advisory committee meetings.&lt;br /&gt;Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act&lt;br /&gt;(5 U.S.C. app. 2).&lt;br /&gt;Dated: June 18, 2010.&lt;br /&gt;Thinh Nguyen,&lt;br /&gt;Acting Associate Commissioner for Special Medical Programs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
