<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;table cellspacing="0" cellpadding="2" border="0" id="schedule" style="WIDTH: 643px" summary="This table shows the date, time, and location of the meeting"&gt;     &lt;tbody&gt;         &lt;tr&gt;             &lt;th bgcolor="#cccccc" align="left" valign="top" id="a1" style="WIDTH: 71px"&gt;Center&lt;/th&gt;             &lt;th bgcolor="#cccccc" align="left" valign="top" id="a2" style="WIDTH: 158px"&gt;Date&lt;/th&gt;             &lt;th bgcolor="#cccccc" align="left" valign="top" id="a3" style="WIDTH: 172px"&gt;Time&lt;/th&gt;             &lt;th bgcolor="#cccccc" align="left" valign="top" id="a4" style="WIDTH: 238px"&gt;Location&lt;/th&gt;         &lt;/tr&gt;         &lt;tr&gt;             &lt;td height="61" valign="top" style="WIDTH: 71px" headers="a1"&gt;CDER&lt;/td&gt;             &lt;td valign="top" style="WIDTH: 158px" headers="a2"&gt;July 20, 2011&lt;br /&gt;             &amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;             &lt;td valign="top" style="WIDTH: 172px" headers="a3"&gt;8:00 a.m. to 9:00  a.m. (open session)&lt;br /&gt;             9:00 a.m. to 1:00 p.m. (closed session)&lt;br /&gt;             &lt;br /&gt;             &amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;             &lt;td valign="top" style="WIDTH: 238px" headers="a4"&gt;Hilton Washington DC/Silver Spring&lt;br /&gt;             The Ballrooms&lt;br /&gt;             8727 Colesville Road&lt;br /&gt;             Silver Spring, Maryland&lt;/td&gt;         &lt;/tr&gt;     &lt;/tbody&gt; &lt;/table&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agenda&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;The meeting will be open to the public from 8 a.m. to 9 a.m., unless public participation does not last that long; from 9 a.m. to 1 p.m., the meeting will be closed to permit discussion and review of trade secret and/or confidential commercial information.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Closed Presentation of Data&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;On July 20, 2011, from 9 a.m. to 1 p.m., the meeting will be closed to permit discussion and review of trade secret and/or confidential commercial information (5 U.S.C. 552b(c)(4)).  During this session, the committees will discuss the drug development program of an investigational gastroenterology drug&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h4&gt;Meeting Materials&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;FDA generally makes background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting or follows other procedures to make such material available to the public.  There is no background material that is publicly available for this meeting.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h4&gt;Public Participation Information&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;Interested persons may present data, information, or views, orally or in  writing, on issues pending before the committee.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt;     &lt;li&gt;Written submissions may be made to the contact person on or before July 6, 2011.&lt;/li&gt;     &lt;li&gt;Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled between approximately 8:00 a.m. to 9:00 a.m., July 20, 2011.  Those desiring to make formal oral presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before June 27, 2011.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;Time allotted for each presentation may be limited.  If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session.  The contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by June 28, 2011.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;ul&gt;     &lt;li&gt;Kristine T. Khuc&lt;br /&gt;     Center for Drug  Evaluation and Research&lt;br /&gt;     Food and Drug Administration&lt;br /&gt;     10903 New Hampshire  Avenue&lt;br /&gt;     WO31-2417&lt;br /&gt;     Silver Spring, Maryland 20993-0002&lt;br /&gt;     Phone:  301-796-9001&lt;br /&gt;     Fax: 301-847-8533&lt;br /&gt;     E-mail: &lt;a href="mailto:GIDAC@fda.hhs.gov"&gt;GIDAC@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;ul&gt;     &lt;li&gt;FDA Advisory Committee Information Line&lt;br /&gt;     1-800-741-8138&lt;br /&gt;     (301-443-0572  in the Washington DC area) follow the prompts to the desired center or product  area&lt;br /&gt;     Please call the Information Line for up-to-date information on this  meeting.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;A notice in the Federal Register about last minute modifications that impact a previously announced advisory committee meeting cannot always be published quickly enough to provide timely notice.  Therefore, you should always check the agency&amp;rsquo;s Website and call the appropriate advisory committee hot line/phone line to learn about possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Persons attending FDA&amp;rsquo;s advisory committee meetings are advised that the agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets.  FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical disabilities or special needs.  If you require special accommodations due to a disability, please contact Kristine T. Khuc at (301) 796-9001 at least 7 days in advance of the meeting.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its  advisory committee meetings. Please visit our Web site at &lt;a href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM111462')--]" target=""&gt;Public Conduct During FDA Advisory Committee Meetings&lt;/a&gt; for procedures on public conduct  during advisory committee meetings.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5  U.S.C. app.2).&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
