<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;table width="98%" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="3" border="1"&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr bgcolor="#999999"&gt;&lt;td valign="top"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Center &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Date &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td valign="top"&gt;&lt;p&gt;CBER&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top"&gt;&lt;p&gt;November 16, 2011&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Between approximately 8 a.m and 5:30 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hilton Washington DC/ Silver Spring, 8727 Colesville Rd., Silver Spring, MD 20910&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agenda&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On November 16, 2011, the committee will meet in open session to hear an overview of the research programs in the Laboratory of Method Development, Division of Viral Products, Office of Vaccines Research and Review, Center for Biologics Evaluation and Research, FDA. The committee will also hear an update on the evaluation of Gullian-Barre Syndrome after Influenza Vaccine among Medicare population, 2010-2011. The committee will then discuss and make recommendations on the safety and immunogenicity (surrogate endpoint) of Pneumococcal 13-valent conjugate vaccine (Diphtheria CRM197 Protein) in adults aged 50 years and older using an accelerated approval regulatory pathway.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meeting Materials&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Materials for this meeting are available on the &lt;a href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM241549')--]" target=""&gt;2011 Meeting Materials, Vaccines and Related Biological Products Advisory Committee&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;page.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Public Participation Information &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interested persons may present data, information, or views, orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Written submissions may be made to the contact person on or before November 9, 2011.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled between approximately 3:30 p.m. and 4:30 p.m. Those individuals interested in making formal oral presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before November 1, 2011. Time allotted for each presentation may be limited. If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session. The contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by November 2, 2011 .&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;For those unable to attend in person, the meeting will also be Web cast. The Webcast is available on the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM292377')--]" target=""&gt;November 16, 2011: Vaccines and Related Biological Products Advisory Committee Meeting: Webcast&lt;/a&gt; page.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Closed Committee Deliberations&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;On November 16, 2011 between approximately 9:45 a.m. and 10:15 a.m., the meeting will be closed to permit discussion where disclosure would constitute a clearly unwarranted invasion of personal privacy (5 U.S.C. 552b(c)(6)). The committee will discuss the report of the intramural research program in the Laboratory of Method Development and make recommendations regarding personnel staffing decisions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Contact Information&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Donald Jehn or Denise Royster &lt;br /&gt;1401 Rockville Pike, HFM-71, Rockville, MD 20852&lt;br /&gt;301-827-0314&lt;br /&gt;FAX: 301-827-0294&lt;br /&gt;e-mail: &lt;a href="mailto:Donald.Jehn@fda.hhs.gov"&gt;Donald.Jehn@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/a&gt; or email: &lt;a href="mailto:denise.royster@fda.hhs.gov"&gt;denise.royster@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;FDA Advisory Committee Information Line&lt;br /&gt;1-800-741-8138 (301-443-0572 in the Washington, DC, area) and follow the prompts to the desired center or product area. Please call the Information Line for up-to-date information on this meeting.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting. If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA&amp;rsquo;s Web site after the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A notice in the Federal Register about last minute modifications that impact a previously announced advisory committee meeting cannot always be published quickly enough to provide timely notice. Therefore, you should always check the agency&amp;rsquo;s Web site and call the appropriate advisory committee hot line/phone line to learn about possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Persons attending FDA&amp;rsquo;s advisory committee meetings are advised that the agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets. FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical disabilities or special needs. If you require special accommodations due to a disability, please contact Donald Jehn or Denise Royster at least 7 days in advance of the meeting. FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its advisory committee meetings. Please visit our Web site for &lt;a href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM111462')--]" target=""&gt;procedures on public conduct during advisory committee meetings&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5 U.S.C. app. 2).&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
