<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH AND HUMAN SERVICES&lt;br /&gt;
Food and Drug Administration&lt;br /&gt;
[Docket No. FDA–2010–N–0001]&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Orthopaedic and Rehabilitation Devices Panel of the Medical Devices&lt;br /&gt;
Advisory Committee; Notice of Meeting&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AGENCY:&lt;/strong&gt; Food and Drug Administration, HHS.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;ACTION:&lt;/strong&gt; Notice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
This notice announces a forthcoming meeting of a public advisory&lt;br /&gt;
committee of the Food and Drug Administration (FDA). The meeting will be&lt;br /&gt;
open to the public.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Name of Committee: Orthopaedic and Rehabilitation Devices Panel of the&lt;br /&gt;
Medical Devices Advisory Committee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;General Function of the Committee:&lt;/strong&gt; To provide advice and&lt;br /&gt;
recommendations to the agency on FDA’s regulatory issues.&lt;br /&gt;
Date and Time: The meeting will be held on March 23, 2010, from 8 a.m.&lt;br /&gt;
to 5 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Location:&lt;/strong&gt; Hilton Washington DC North/Gaithersburg, Salons A, B, C and&lt;br /&gt;
D, 620 Perry Pkwy., Gaithersburg, MD.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Contact Person:&lt;/strong&gt; Tracy Phillips, Center for Devices and Radiological Health,&lt;br /&gt;
Food and Drug Administration, 10903 New Hampshire Ave., Silver Spring, MD&lt;br /&gt;
20993, 301–796–6150, Tracy.Phillips@fda.hhs.gov, or FDA Advisory&lt;br /&gt;
Committee Information Line, 1–800–741–8138 (301–443–0572 in the&lt;br /&gt;
Washington, DC area), code 3014512521. Please call the Information Line for&lt;br /&gt;
up-to-date information on this meeting. A notice in the Federal Register about&lt;br /&gt;
last minute modifications that impact a previously announced advisory&lt;br /&gt;
committee meeting cannot always be published quickly enough to provide&lt;br /&gt;
timely notice. Therefore, you should always check the agency’s Web site and&lt;br /&gt;
call the appropriate advisory committee hot line/phone line to learn about&lt;br /&gt;
possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Agenda:&lt;/strong&gt; On March 23, 2010, the committee will discuss and make&lt;br /&gt;
recommendations on issues relevant to FDA’s reevaluation of the ReGen&lt;br /&gt;
Collagen Scaffold (CS) device (marketed as the Menaflex®), which FDA cleared&lt;br /&gt;
in K082079 on December 18, 2008, sponsored by ReGen Biologics, Inc. The&lt;br /&gt;
indications for use statement for this device states that the device is intended&lt;br /&gt;
for use in surgical procedures for the reinforcement and repair of soft tissue&lt;br /&gt;
injuries of the medial meniscus. In repairing and reinforcing medial meniscal&lt;br /&gt;
defects, the patient must have an intact meniscal rim and anterior and posterior&lt;br /&gt;
horns for attachment of the mesh. In addition, the surgically prepared site for&lt;br /&gt;
the CS must extend at least into the red/white zone of the meniscus to provide&lt;br /&gt;
sufficient vascularization. The CS reinforces soft tissue and provides a&lt;br /&gt;
resorbable scaffold that is replaced by the patient’s own soft tissue. The CS&lt;br /&gt;
is not a prosthetic device and is not intended to replace normal body structure.&lt;br /&gt;
FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later&lt;br /&gt;
than 2 business days before the meeting. If FDA is unable to post the&lt;br /&gt;
background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background&lt;br /&gt;
material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory&lt;br /&gt;
committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA’s Web&lt;br /&gt;
site after the meeting. Background material is available at http://www.fda.gov/&lt;br /&gt;
AdvisoryCommittees/Calendar/default.htm. Scroll down to the appropriate&lt;br /&gt;
advisory committee link.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Procedure:&lt;/strong&gt; Interested persons may present views, orally or in writing, on&lt;br /&gt;
issues pending before the committee. These views may be submitted in writing&lt;br /&gt;
to the contact person on or before March 16, 2010. Oral presentations from&lt;br /&gt;
the public will be scheduled at approximately 1 p.m., immediately following&lt;br /&gt;
lunch. Those desiring to make formal oral presentations should notify the&lt;br /&gt;
contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the&lt;br /&gt;
arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of proposed&lt;br /&gt;
participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested to make their&lt;br /&gt;
presentation on or before March 8, 2010. Time allotted for each presentation&lt;br /&gt;
may be limited. If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than&lt;br /&gt;
can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing&lt;br /&gt;
session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the&lt;br /&gt;
scheduled open public hearing session. The contact person will notify&lt;br /&gt;
interested persons regarding their request to speak by March 9, 2010.&lt;br /&gt;
Persons attending FDA’s advisory committee meetings are advised that the&lt;br /&gt;
agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets.&lt;br /&gt;
FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee&lt;br /&gt;
meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical&lt;br /&gt;
disabilities or special needs. If you require special accommodations due to a&lt;br /&gt;
disability, please contact AnnMarie Williams, at 301–796–5966, at least 7 days&lt;br /&gt;
in advance of the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its advisory committee&lt;br /&gt;
meetings. Please visit our Web site at http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/&lt;br /&gt;
AboutAdvisoryCommittees/ucm111462.htm for procedures on public conduct&lt;br /&gt;
during advisory committee meetings.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act&lt;br /&gt;
(5 U.S.C. app. 2).&lt;br /&gt;
Dated: February 24, 2010.&lt;br /&gt;
Joanne Less,&lt;br /&gt;
Acting Associate Commissioner for Special Medical Programs.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
