<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;table cellspacing="0" cellpadding="2" border="0" summary="This table shows the date, time, and location of the meeting" id="schedule" style=" width: 100%"&gt; &lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt; &lt;th width="10%" valign="top" bgcolor="#cccccc" align="left" id="a1"&gt;Center&lt;/th&gt; &lt;th width="25%" valign="top" bgcolor="#cccccc" align="left" id="a2"&gt;Date&lt;/th&gt; &lt;th width="25%" valign="top" bgcolor="#cccccc" align="left" id="a3"&gt;Time&lt;/th&gt; &lt;th width="40%" valign="top" bgcolor="#cccccc" align="left" id="a4"&gt;Location&lt;/th&gt; &lt;/tr&gt;  &lt;tr&gt; &lt;td width="10%" valign="top" headers="a1"&gt;OC&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td width="25%" valign="top" headers="a2"&gt;May 20, 2011&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td width="25%" valign="top" headers="a3"&gt;9:00 a.m. - 3:30 p.m.&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td width="40%" valign="top" headers="a4"&gt;Food and Drug Administration&lt;br /&gt;   10903 New Hampshire Ave.&lt;br /&gt;   Bldg. 31, rm. 1503, &lt;br /&gt;   Silver Spring, MD 20993-0002&lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tr&gt;  &lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt; &lt;p&gt;For those unable to attend in person, the meeting will also be webcast. The link for the webcast is available at &lt;a target="_blank" href="[!--$ssExternalLink('UCM255449')--]"&gt;https://collaboration.fda.gov/scienceboard&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Agenda&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;The Science Board will discuss the report from the subcommittee's review of the Pharmacovigilance Program at the Center for Drug Evaluation and Research.&amp;nbsp; The Science Board will be provided with updates on FDA's nanotechnology research program plans and on FDA's activities in support of Comparative Effectiveness Research.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meeting Materials&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;FDA intends to make the complete background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting. If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA&amp;rsquo;s Web site after the meeting.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul type="disc"&gt;   &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Background material&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;ul&gt;     &lt;li&gt;&lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','ucm241888.htm')--]"&gt;2011 Meeting Materials, Science Board to the FDA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;   &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;    &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Public Participation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;Interested persons may present data, information, or views, orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committee.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt;   &lt;li&gt;Written submissions may be made to the contact person on or before May 13, 2011.&lt;/li&gt;   &lt;li&gt;Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled between approximately 1 p.m. and 2 p.m. on May 20, 2011. Those desiring to make formal oral presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before May 5, 2011.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;Time allotted for each presentation may be limited. If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session. The contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by May 6, 2011.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;Martha Monser&lt;br /&gt;   Office of Chief Scientist&lt;br /&gt;   Office of the Commissioner&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Food and Drug Administration&lt;br /&gt;   White Oak Bldg 32, Room 4286&lt;br /&gt;   10903 New Hampshire Ave.&lt;br /&gt;   Silver Spring, Maryland 20993&lt;br /&gt;   Phone: 301&amp;ndash;796-4627&lt;br /&gt;   Fax: 301-847-8617&lt;br /&gt; E-mail: &lt;a href="mailto:martha.monser@fda.hhs.gov"&gt;martha.monser@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;      &lt;p&gt;A notice in the Federal Register about last minute modifications that impact a previously announced advisory committee meeting cannot always be published quickly enough to provide timely notice. Therefore, you should always check the agency&amp;rsquo;s website and call the appropriate advisory committee hot line/phone line to learn about possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;ul&gt;   &lt;li&gt;FDA Advisory Committee Information Line&lt;br /&gt;     1-800-741-8138&lt;br /&gt;     (301-443-0572 in the Washington DC area)&lt;br /&gt;     and follow the prompts to the desired center or product area.&lt;br /&gt;     Please call the Information Line for up-to-date information on this meeting.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;Persons attending FDA&amp;rsquo;s advisory committee  meetings are advised that the agency is not responsible for providing access to  electrical outlets. FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory  committee meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with  physical disabilities or special needs. If you require special accommodations  due to a disability, please contact Martha Monser at (301) 796-4627 at least 7  days in advance of the meeting. FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its advisory committee meetings. Please visit our Web site for &lt;a href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','ucm111462.htm')--]" target=""&gt;procedures on public conduct during advisory committee meetings&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal  Advisory Committee Act (5 U.S.C. app.2).&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
