<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;table id="schedule" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="2" summary="This table shows the date, time, and location of the meeting" border="0" style="width: 100%"&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th id="a1" valign="top" align="left" width="10%" bgcolor="#cccccc"&gt;Center&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a2" valign="top" align="left" width="25%" bgcolor="#cccccc"&gt;Date&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a3" valign="top" align="left" width="25%" bgcolor="#cccccc"&gt;Time&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a4" valign="top" align="left" width="40%" bgcolor="#cccccc"&gt;Location&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td valign="top" headers="a1" width="10%"&gt;CDRH&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" headers="a2" width="25%"&gt;March&amp;nbsp;17- 18, 2011&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" headers="a3" width="25%"&gt;8:00 a.m. - 6:00 p.m.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" headers="a4" width="40%"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hilton&lt;br /&gt;620 Perry Parkway&lt;br /&gt;Gaithersburg, MD&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h5&gt;Agenda&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;On March 17, 2011, the committee will discuss, make recommendations and vote on information related to the premarket approval application (PMA) for the NovoTTF-100A Treatment Kit, sponsored by Hogan Lovells US LLP for NovoCure, Ltd.&amp;nbsp;The NovoTTF-100A Treatment Kit is intended as a treatment for adult patients (greater than 21 years of age) with histologically- or radiologically-confirmed glioblastoma multiforme (GBM), following recurrence in the supra-tentorial region of the brain.&amp;nbsp;The device is intended to be used as a monotherapy, after surgical and radiation options have been exhausted, in place of standard medical therapy for GBM.&amp;nbsp;On March 18, 2011, the committee will discuss, make recommendations and vote on information related to the PMA for the PIPELINE EMBOLIZATION Device (PED), sponsored by Chestnut Medical.&amp;nbsp;ThePED is indicated for the endovascular treatment of large or giant wide-necked intracranial aneurysms in the paraclinoid region of the internal carotid artery.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting.&amp;nbsp;If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA&amp;rsquo;s Web site after the meeting.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;Background&amp;nbsp;Material&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;2011 Meeting Materials,&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h5&gt;Public Participation and Sponsor Information&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;Interested persons may present data, information, or views, orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committee.&amp;nbsp;Written submissions may be made to the contact person on or before March 10, 2011.&amp;nbsp;Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled between approximately 1 p.m. and 2 p.m. immediately following lunch on March 17 and 18.&amp;nbsp;Those individuals interested in making formal oral presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before March 2, 2011.&amp;nbsp;Time allotted for each presentation may be limited.&amp;nbsp;If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session.&amp;nbsp;The contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by March 3, 2011.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;Persons attending FDA's advisory committee meetings are advised that the Agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical disabilities or special needs. If you require special accommodations due to a disability, please contact Ms. Ann Marie Williams, Conference Management Staff, at 301-796-5966, at least 7 days in advance of the meeting.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h5&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&lt;h5&gt;Contact Information&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;Olga Claudio&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;Food and Drug Administration&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;Center for Devices and Radiological Health&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;10903 New Hampshire Ave.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;Bldg. 66, rm. 1611, Silver Spring, MD&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;301-796-7608&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;FDA Advisory Committee Information Line&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;1-800-741-8138&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;(301-443-0572 in the Washington, DC area)&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;Please call the Information Line for up-to-date information on this meeting.&amp;nbsp;A notice in the Federal Register about last minute modifications that impact a previously announced advisory committee meeting cannot always be published quickly enough to provide timely notice.&amp;nbsp;Therefore, you should always check the Agency&amp;rsquo;s Web site and call the appropriate advisory committee hot line/phone line to learn about possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its advisory committee meetings.&amp;nbsp;Please visit our Web site at&amp;nbsp;for &lt;a target="_blank" href="[!--$ssExternalLink('UCM184210')--]"&gt;procedures on public conduct during advisory committee meetings&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5 U.S.C. app. 2).&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
