<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;p class="citable" id="p-3" data-page="55803"&gt;This notice announces a forthcoming meeting of a public advisory committee of the Food and Drug Administration (FDA). The meeting will be open to the public.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="citable" id="p-4" data-page="55803"&gt;&lt;span class="E-03 firstchild lastchild"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Name of Committee&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: Neurological Devices Panel of the Medical Devices Advisory Committee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="citable" id="p-5" data-page="55803"&gt;&lt;span class="E-03 firstchild lastchild"&gt;&lt;em&gt;General Function of the Committee&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: To provide advice and recommendations to the agency on FDA's regulatory issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="citable" id="p-6" data-page="55803"&gt;&lt;span class="E-03 firstchild lastchild"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Date and Time&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: The meeting will be held on October 8, 2010, from 8 a.m. to 6 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="citable" id="p-7" data-page="55803"&gt;&lt;span class="E-03 firstchild lastchild"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Location&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: Hilton Washington DC North/Gaithersburg, Ballroom, 620 Perry Pkwy., Gaithersburg, MD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="citable" id="p-8" data-page="55803"&gt;&lt;span class="E-03 firstchild"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Contact Person&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: James Engles, Center for Devices and Radiological Health, Food and Drug Administration,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="citable" data-page="55803"&gt;10903 New Hampshire Ave., Silver Spring, MD 20993, or FDA Advisory Committee Information Line, 1-800-741-8138 (301-443-0572 in the Washington, DC area), code 3014512513. Please call the Information Line for up-to-date information on this meeting. A notice in the &lt;span class="E-04 lastchild"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Federal Register&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; about last minute modifications that impact a previously announced advisory committee meeting cannot always be published quickly enough to provide timely notice. Therefore, you should always check the agency's Web site and call the appropriate advisory committee hot line/phone line to learn about possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="citable" id="p-9" data-page="55803"&gt;&lt;span class="E-03 firstchild lastchild"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Agenda&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: On October 8, 2010, the committee will discuss and make recommendations regarding clinical trial design issues for devices indicated for the treatment of depression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="citable on" id="p-10" data-page="55803" sizcache="7" sizset="27"&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting. If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA's Web site after the meeting. Background material is available at &lt;span class="E-03 firstchild lastchild" sizcache="7" sizset="27"&gt;&lt;a class="firstchild lastchild" jquery1284474300146="8" href="http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/Calendar/default.htm"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;font color="#004276"&gt;http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/Calendar/default.htm&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. Scroll down to the appropriate advisory committee link.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="citable" id="p-11" data-page="55803"&gt;&lt;span class="E-03 firstchild lastchild"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Procedure&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: Interested persons may present data, information, or views, orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committee. Written submissions may be made to the contact person on or before September 30, 2010. Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled at approximately 1 p.m., immediately following lunch. Those desiring to make formal oral presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before September 22, 2010. Time allotted for each presentation may be limited. If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session. The contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by September 23, 2010.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="citable" id="p-12" data-page="55803"&gt;Persons attending FDA's advisory committee meetings are advised that the agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="citable" id="p-13" data-page="55803"&gt;FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical disabilities or special needs. If you require special accommodations due to a disability, please contact AnnMarie Williams, Conference Management Staff, at 301-796-5966 at least 7 days in advance of the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="citable" id="p-14" data-page="55803" sizcache="7" sizset="28"&gt;FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its advisory committee meetings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="citable" data-page="55803" sizcache="7" sizset="28"&gt;Please visit our Web site at &lt;span class="E-03 firstchild lastchild" sizcache="7" sizset="28"&gt;&lt;a class="firstchild lastchild" jquery1284474300146="9" href="http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/AboutAdvisoryCommittees/ucm111462.htm"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;font color="#004276"&gt;http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/AboutAdvisoryCommittees/ucm111462.htm&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; for procedures on public conduct during advisory committee meetings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="citable" id="p-15" data-page="55803"&gt;Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5 U.S.C. app. 2).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="signature"&gt;&lt;p class="signature_date firstchild"&gt;Dated: September 7, 2010.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="name"&gt;Leslie Kux,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="name"&gt;Acting Assistant Commissioner for Policy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="fr_doc lastchild"&gt;[FR Doc. 2010-22804 Filed 9-13-10; 8:45 am]&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
