<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;table border="0" cellspacing="0" summary="Meeting information" cellpadding="0" width="100%"&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr bgcolor="#cccccc"&gt;&lt;th valign="top" width="12%" scope="col"&gt;&lt;p align="left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Center&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th valign="top" width="22%" scope="col"&gt;&lt;p align="left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Date&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th valign="top" width="29%" scope="col"&gt;&lt;p align="left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th valign="top" width="37%" scope="col"&gt;&lt;p align="left"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td valign="top" width="12%"&gt;&lt;p&gt;CBER&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" width="22%"&gt;&lt;p&gt;May 12, 2011&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" width="29%"&gt;&lt;p&gt;8 a.m. to 3:30 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" width="37%"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Doubletree Hotel,&amp;nbsp; 8120 Wisconsin Avenue, Bethesda, MD&amp;nbsp; 20814&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agenda&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On May 12, 2011, &amp;nbsp;from&amp;nbsp; 8 a.m. to 3 p.m., in open session, the committee will receive updates and have discussion on the following topics:&amp;nbsp; (1) Structure and Activities of the Laboratory of Immunobiochemistry (the Laboratory), Division of Bacterial, Parasitic, and Allergenic Products, Center for Biologics Evaluation and Research, FDA; (2) enzyme-linked immunosorbent assay replacement of radial immunodiffusion assays for potency determinations of cat and ragweed pollen allergen extracts by the Laboratory; (3) statistical considerations for the design and interpretation of phase III clinical trials of allergenic products; (4) environmental exposure chambers for phase III studies of allergenic products, and (5) International Organization for Standardization (ISO) 17025 accreditation of the Laboratory.&amp;nbsp; In closed session, from 3 p.m. to 3:30 p.m. the Committee will meet to discuss a report of intramural research programs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meeting Materials&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Materials for this meeting will be available on the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','ucm247212.htm')--]"&gt;2011 Meeting Materials, Allergenic Products Advisory Committee page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;a href="http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/CommitteesMeetingMaterials/BloodVaccinesandOtherBiologics/default.htm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Public Participation Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interested persons may present data, information, or views, orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul type="disc"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Written submissions may be made to the contact person on or before May 5, 2011&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled between approximately 11:30 a.m. to 12:30 p.m. &amp;nbsp;Those desiring to make formal oral presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before April 27, 2011.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Time allotted for each presentation may be limited. If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session. The contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by April 28, 2011.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gail Dapolito or Jane Brown&lt;br /&gt;1401 Rockville Pike, HFM-71, Rockville, MD 20852&lt;br /&gt;301-827-0314&lt;br /&gt;FAX: 301-827-0294&lt;br /&gt;e-mail: &lt;a href="mailto:gail.dapolito@fda.hhs.gov"&gt;gail.dapolito@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/a&gt;; &lt;a href="mailto:jane.brown@fda.hhs.gov"&gt;jane.brown@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;FDA Advisory Committee Information Line&lt;br /&gt;1-800-741-8138 (301-443-0572 in the Washington, DC, area) &lt;br /&gt;code 3014512391. Please call the Information Line for up-to-date information on this meeting.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting. If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA's Web site after the meeting. &lt;br /&gt;A notice in the Federal Register about last minute modifications that impact a previously announced advisory committee meeting cannot always be published quickly enough to provide timely notice. Therefore, you should always check the agency's Web site and call the appropriate advisory committee hot line/phone line to learn about possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&lt;br /&gt;Persons attending FDA's advisory committee meetings are advised that the agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets. FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical disabilities or special needs. If you require special accommodations due to a disability, please contact Gail Dapolito at least 7 days in advance of the meeting. FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its advisory committee meetings. Please &lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','ucm111462.htm')--]"&gt;visit our Web site for procedures&lt;/a&gt; on public conduct during advisory committee meetings.&lt;br /&gt;Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5 U.S.C. app. 2).&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
