<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;table id="schedule" border="0" cellspacing="0" summary="This table shows the date, time, and location of the meeting" cellpadding="2" style="width: 100%"&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th id="a1" bgcolor="#cccccc" align="left" style="width: 15%; vertical-align: top"&gt;Center&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a2" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" width="20%" align="left"&gt;Date&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a3" bgcolor="#cccccc" align="left" style="width: 25%; vertical-align: top"&gt;Time&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a4" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" width="40%" align="left"&gt;Location&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td headers="a1" style="width: 15%; vertical-align: top"&gt;OC&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" width="20%" headers="a2"&gt;June 21, 2010&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td headers="a3" style="width: 25%; vertical-align: top"&gt;9:00 a.m. - 5:00 p.m.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" width="40%" headers="a4"&gt;Bethesda Marriott&lt;br /&gt;5151 Pooks Hill Road&lt;br /&gt;Bethesda, MD 20814&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Agenda&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Pediatric Advisory Committee will meet to discuss pediatric-focused safety reviews, as mandated by the Best Pharmaceuticals for Children Act and the Pediatric Research Equity Act, for Kogenate FS (antihemophilic factor (recombinant)), Casodex (bicalutamide), Apidra (insulin glulisine [rDNA]), NovoLog (insulin aspart [rDNA]), Arimidex (anastrozole), Desmopressin Acetate,&amp;nbsp; Prevacid (lansoprazole), Nexium (esomeprazole magnesium), Aciphex (rabeprazole sodium), Prilosec (omeprazole), OraVerse (phentolamine mesylate), Zemuron (rocuronium bromide).&amp;nbsp; The committee will also receive a follow- up presentation on Suprane (desflurane) and an overview on the Pediatric Device Consortia Grants Program.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meeting Materials&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA intends to make the complete set of background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting. If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, all efforts will be made to try and provide the background material at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA&amp;rsquo;s Web site after the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Background material &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','ucm201871.htm')--]"&gt;2010 Meeting Materials, Pediatric Advisory Committee&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Public Participation and Sponsor Information&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interested persons and Sponsors (representatives from industry) may present data, information, or views, orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Written submissions may be made to the contact person on or before June 7, 2010. Comments received on or before June 17, 2010, will be provided to the committee before the meeting.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Oral presentations from the public (excluding Sponsors) will be scheduled between approximately 1 p.m. and 2 p.m on June 21, 2010. Those desiring to make formal oral presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before May 28, 2010. Time allotted for each presentation may be limited. If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session. The contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by May 31, 2010.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Doreen Kezer, MSN&lt;br /&gt;Office of Science and Public Health&lt;br /&gt;Office of the Commissioner&lt;br /&gt;Food and Drug Administration&lt;br /&gt;10903 New Hampshire Ave.&lt;br /&gt;Silver Spring, Maryland 20993&lt;br /&gt;Phone: 301&amp;ndash;796-8524&lt;br /&gt;Fax: 301-796-8616&lt;br /&gt;E-mail: &lt;a href="mailto:doreen.kezer@fda.hhs.gov"&gt;doreen.kezer@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;FDA Advisory Committee Information Line 1-800-741-8138&lt;br /&gt;(301-443-0572 in the Washington DC area) Code:8732310001&lt;br /&gt;Please call the Information Line for up-to-date information on this meeting.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;A notice in the Federal Register about last minute modifications that impact a previously announced advisory committee meeting cannot always be published quickly enough to provide timely notice. Therefore, you should always check the agency&amp;rsquo;s Web site and call the appropriate advisory committee hot line/phone line to learn about possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting. If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA&amp;rsquo;s Web site after the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Persons attending FDA&amp;rsquo;s advisory committee meetings are advised that the agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets. FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical disabilities or special needs. If you require special accommodations due to a disability, please contact Doreen Kezer, MSN at (301) 796-8524 at least 7 days in advance of the meeting. FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its advisory committee meetings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please visit our Web site for &lt;a href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','ucm111462.htm')--]"&gt;procedures on public conduct during advisory committee meetings&lt;/a&gt;. Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5 U.S.C. app.2).&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
