<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="table-responsive"&gt;&lt;table class="table table-bordered table-striped" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="2" width="643" summary="This table shows the date, time, and location of the meeting" border="1"&gt;&lt;thead&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th id="a1" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" scope="row" align="left" style="width: 71px"&gt;Center&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a2" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" scope="col" align="left" style="width: 158px"&gt;Date&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a3" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" scope="col" align="left" style="width: 172px"&gt;Time&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a4" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" scope="col" align="left" style="width: 238px"&gt;Location&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td height="61" valign="top" headers="a1" scope="row" style="width: 71px"&gt;CDER&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" headers="a2" style="width: 158px"&gt;May 2, 2011&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" headers="a3" style="width: 172px"&gt;8:00 a.m. to 4:00 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" headers="a4" style="width: 238px"&gt;FDA White Oak Campus&lt;br /&gt;Building 31&lt;br /&gt;The Great Room (Rm. 1503)&lt;br /&gt;White Oak Conference Center&lt;br /&gt;10903 New Hampshire Avenue&lt;br /&gt;Silver Spring, Maryland&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agenda&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;On May 2, 2011, the committees will discuss safety considerations of ultrasound contrast agents (materials intended to improve the clarity of ultrasound imaging), particularly related to new information and developments since the prior Advisory Committee meeting on the same topic on June 24, 2008. The discussion will include the results of required postmarketing safety studies and data from postmarketing surveillance. Specific drugs to be discussed include: (1) New drug application (NDA) 21-064, perflutren lipid microsphere injectable suspension, Lantheus Medical Imaging, Inc.; (2) NDA 20-899, perflutren protein-type A microspheres injectable suspension, GE Healthcare; and (3) the investigational new drug (IND) application for sulfur hexafluoride microbubble injection, Bracco Diagnostics, Inc. Perflutren lipid microsphere injectable suspension and perflutren protein-type A microspheres injectable suspension are indicated for use in patients with suboptimal echocardiograms to opacify the left ventricular chamber and to improve the delineation of the left ventricular endocardial border (improve the clarity of imaging of specific areas of the left lower side of the heart).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Meeting Materials&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting. If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA&amp;rsquo;s Web site after the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p sizset="26" sizcache="1"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Background Material&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM2005376.htm')--]"&gt;Advisory Committee Calendar&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Public Participation Information&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interested persons may present data, information, or views, orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Written submissions may be made to the contact person on or before April 18, 2011.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled between approximately 1 p.m. and 2 p.m. Those desiring to make formal oral presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before April 8, 2011.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Time allotted for each presentation may be limited. If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session. The contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by April 11, 2011.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;ul sizset="27" sizcache="1"&gt;&lt;li sizset="27" sizcache="1"&gt;Nicole Vesely, Pharm.D.&lt;br /&gt;Center for Drug Evaluation and Research&lt;br /&gt;Food and Drug Administration&lt;br /&gt;10903 New Hampshire Avenue&lt;br /&gt;WO31-2417&lt;br /&gt;Silver Spring, Maryland 20993-0002&lt;br /&gt;Phone: 301-796-9001&lt;br /&gt;Fax: 301-847-8533&lt;br /&gt;E-mail: &lt;a href="mailto:nicole.vesely@fda.hhs.gov"&gt;nicole.vesely@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;FDA Advisory Committee Information Line&lt;br /&gt;1-800-741-8138&lt;br /&gt;(301-443-0572 in the Washington DC area) follow the prompts to the desired center or product area&lt;br /&gt;Please call the Information Line for up-to-date information on this meeting.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;A notice in the Federal Register about last minute modifications that impact a previously announced advisory committee meeting cannot always be published quickly enough to provide timely notice. Therefore, you should always check the agency&amp;rsquo;s Web site and call the appropriate advisory committee hot line/phone line to learn about possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Persons attending FDA&amp;rsquo;s advisory committee meetings are advised that the agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets. FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical disabilities or special needs. If you require special accommodations due to a disability, please contact Nicole Vesely at (301) 796-9001 at least 7 days in advance of the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Information regarding ground transportation, airport information, lodging, driving directions and visitor parking, and security can be accessed at: &lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','ucm241740.htm')--]"&gt;Public Meetings at the FDA White Oak Campus&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p sizset="28" sizcache="1"&gt;FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its advisory committee meetings. Please visit our Web site at &lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','ucm111462.htm')--]"&gt;Public Conduct During FDA Advisory Committee Meetings&lt;/a&gt; for procedures on public conduct during advisory committee meetings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5 U.S.C. app.2).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
