<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;table id="schedule" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="2" summary="This table shows the date, time, and location of the meeting" border="0" style="width: 100%"&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th id="a1" valign="top" align="left" width="10%" bgcolor="#cccccc"&gt;Center&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a2" valign="top" align="left" width="25%" bgcolor="#cccccc"&gt;Date&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a3" valign="top" align="left" width="25%" bgcolor="#cccccc"&gt;Time&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a4" valign="top" align="left" width="40%" bgcolor="#cccccc"&gt;Location&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td valign="top" headers="a1" width="10%"&gt;CDRH&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" headers="a2" width="25%"&gt;January 25- 26, 2011&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" headers="a3" width="25%"&gt;8:00 a.m. - 6:00 p.m.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" headers="a4" width="40%"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Holiday Inn, Main Ballroom&lt;br /&gt;Two Montgomery Village Ave.&lt;br /&gt;Gaithersburg, MD&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h5&gt;Agenda&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;On January 25, 2011, the committee will discuss and make recommendations regarding regulatory classification of Automated External Defibrillators to either reconfirm to class III (subject to premarket approval application (PMA)) or reclassify to class II (subject to premarket notification (510(k))), as directed by section 515(i) of the Federal Food, Drug, and Cosmetic Act (21 U.S.C 360e(i)).&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;On January 26, 2011, the committee will discuss, make recommendations and vote on information related to the PMA supplement for the RX Acculink Carotid Stent System, sponsored by Abbott Vascular. The RX Acculink is indicated for treatment of patients at high and standard risk for adverse events from carotid endarterectomy who require carotid revascularization and meet the criteria outlined as follows:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;1.&amp;nbsp;Patients with neurological symptoms and &amp;gt;50 percent stenosis of the common or internal carotid artery or patients without neurological symptoms and &amp;gt;80 percent (high risk) or &amp;gt;70 percent (standard risk) stenosis of the common or internal carotid artery and&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;2.&amp;nbsp;Patients must have a reference vessel diameter within the range of 4.0 and 9.0 mm at the target lesion.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h5&gt;Meeting Materials&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting.&amp;nbsp;If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA&amp;rsquo;s Web site after the meeting.&amp;nbsp;Background material is available at &lt;u&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/Calendar/default.htm"&gt;&lt;font color="#800080"&gt;http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/Calendar/default.htm&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/u&gt;. Scroll down to the appropriate advisory committee link.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h5&gt;Public Participation and Sponsor Information&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;Interested persons may present data, information, or views, orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committee.&amp;nbsp;Written submissions may be made to the contact person on or before January 18, 2011.&amp;nbsp;Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled for 1 hour at approximately 1 p.m., immediately following lunch on both days.&amp;nbsp;Those individuals interested in making formal oral presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before January 10, 2011.&amp;nbsp;Time allotted for each presentation may be limited.&amp;nbsp;If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session.&amp;nbsp;The contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by January 11, 2011.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;Persons attending FDA's advisory committee meetings are advised that the Agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical disabilities or special needs. If you require special accommodations due to a disability, please contact AnnMarie Williams, Conference Management Staff, 301-796-5966, at least 7 days in advance of the meeting.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its advisory committee meetings.&amp;nbsp;Please visit our Web site at &lt;u&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/AboutAdvisoryCommittees/ucm111462.htm"&gt;http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/AboutAdvisoryCommittees/ucm111462.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/u&gt; for procedures on public conduct during advisory committee meetings.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5 U.S.C. app. 2).&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
