<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;p&gt;&#13;
&lt;table id="schedule" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="2" summary="This table shows the date, time, and location of the meeting" border="0" style="width: 643px"&gt;&#13;
    &lt;tbody&gt;&#13;
        &lt;tr&gt;&#13;
            &lt;th id="a1" valign="top" align="left" bgcolor="#cccccc" style="width: 71px"&gt;Center&lt;/th&gt;&#13;
            &lt;th id="a2" valign="top" align="left" bgcolor="#cccccc" style="width: 158px"&gt;Date&lt;/th&gt;&#13;
            &lt;th id="a3" valign="top" align="left" bgcolor="#cccccc" style="width: 172px"&gt;Time&lt;/th&gt;&#13;
            &lt;th id="a4" valign="top" align="left" bgcolor="#cccccc" style="width: 238px"&gt;Location&lt;/th&gt;&#13;
        &lt;/tr&gt;&#13;
        &lt;tr&gt;&#13;
            &lt;td valign="top" headers="a1" height="61" style="width: 71px"&gt;CDER&lt;/td&gt;&#13;
            &lt;td valign="top" headers="a2" style="width: 158px"&gt;April 12, 2011&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
            &amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&#13;
            &lt;td valign="top" headers="a3" style="width: 172px"&gt;8:00 a.m. to 5:00 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
            &amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&#13;
            &lt;td valign="top" headers="a4" style="width: 238px"&gt;FDA White Oak Campus&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
            Building 31&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
            The Great Room (Rm. 1503)&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
            White Oak Conference Center&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
            10903 New Hampshire Avenue&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
            Silver Spring, Maryland&lt;/td&gt;&#13;
        &lt;/tr&gt;&#13;
    &lt;/tbody&gt;&#13;
&lt;/table&gt;&#13;
&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agenda&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;On April 12, 2011, during the morning session, the committee will discuss supplemental New Drug Application (sNDA) 022334/S-009, trade name Afinitor (everolimus) tablets, application submitted by Novartis Pharmaceuticals Corporation. The proposed indication (use) for this product is for the treatment of patients with advanced neuroendocrine tumors (NET) of gastrointestinal, lung, or pancreatic origin. During the afternoon session, the committee will discuss sNDA 021938/S-013, trade name Sutent (sunitinib malate) capsules, application submitted by C.P. Pharmaceuticals International C.V., represented by Pfizer Inc. (authorized U.S. agent). The proposed indication (use) for this product is for the treatment of unresectable pancreatic neuroendocrine tumors (PNET).&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;h4&gt;Meeting Materials&lt;/h4&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting. If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA&amp;rsquo;s Web site after the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Background material&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;ul sizset="26" sizcache="2"&gt;&#13;
    &lt;li sizset="26" sizcache="2"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;font color="#810081"&gt;&lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','ucm235829.htm')--]"&gt;2011 Meeting Materials, Oncologic Drugs Advisory Committee&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#13;
&lt;h4&gt;Public Participation Information&lt;/h4&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Interested persons may present data, information, or views, orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committee.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;ul&gt;&#13;
    &lt;li&gt;Written submissions may be made to the contact person on or before March 29, 2011.&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
    &lt;li&gt;Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled between approximately 10:30 a.m. to 11:00 a.m. and 3:30 p.m. to 4:00 p.m. Those desiring to make formal oral presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before March 21, 2011.&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Time allotted for each presentation may be limited. If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session. The contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by March 22, 2011.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#13;
&lt;ul sizset="27" sizcache="2"&gt;&#13;
    &lt;li sizset="27" sizcache="2"&gt;Caleb Briggs, Pharm.D.&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
    Center for Drug Evaluation and Research&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
    Food and Drug Administration&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
    10903 New Hampshire Avenue&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
    WO31-2428&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
    Silver Spring, Maryland 20993-0002&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
    Phone: 301-796-9001&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
    Fax: 301-847-8533&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
    E-mail: &lt;a href="mailto:caleb.briggs@fda.hhs.gov"&gt;caleb.briggs@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#13;
&lt;ul&gt;&#13;
    &lt;li&gt;FDA Advisory Committee Information Line&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
    1-800-741-8138&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
    (301-443-0572 in the Washington DC area)&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
    Please call the Information Line for up-to-date information on this meeting.&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;A notice in the Federal Register about last minute modifications that impact a previously announced advisory committee meeting cannot always be published quickly enough to provide timely notice. Therefore, you should always check the agency&amp;rsquo;s Web site and call the appropriate advisory committee hot line/phone line to learn about possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Persons attending FDA&amp;rsquo;s advisory committee meetings are advised that the agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets. FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical disabilities or special needs. If you require special accommodations due to a disability, please contact Caleb Briggs at (301) 796-9001 at least 7 days in advance of the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p sizset="28" sizcache="2"&gt;Information regarding ground transportation, airport information, lodging, driving directions and visitor parking, and security can be accessed at: &lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','ucm241740.htm')--]"&gt;Public Meetings at the FDA White Oak Campus&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p sizset="29" sizcache="2"&gt;FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its advisory committee meetings. Please visit our Web site at &lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','ucm111462.htm')--]"&gt;Public Conduct During FDA Advisory Committee Meetings&lt;/a&gt; for procedures on public conduct during advisory committee meetings.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5 U.S.C. app.2).&lt;!--SS_END_ELEMENT(region1_element1)--&gt;&lt;!--==== END MIDDLE-COLUMN PAGE CONTENT ==== --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
