<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;p sizset="37" sizcache="1"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Date:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;November 18, 2010&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time:&lt;/strong&gt; 1 p.m. &amp;ndash; 5 p.m. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;FDA White Oak Conference Center, Building 31, Room 1503 &lt;br /&gt;10903 New Hampshire Ave.&lt;br /&gt;Silver Spring, MD 20993-0002&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p sizset="38" sizcache="1"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;Information regarding special accommodations due to a disability, visitor parking and transportation may be accessed at:&amp;nbsp; &lt;a href="http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/default.htm"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;font color="#810081"&gt;http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/default.htm&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;; under the heading &amp;ldquo;Resources for You&amp;rdquo; click on &amp;ldquo;White Oak Conference Center Parking and Transportation Information for FDA Advisory Committee Meetings&amp;rdquo;.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p sizset="39" sizcache="1"&gt;&lt;strong sizset="39" sizcache="1"&gt;Agenda&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On November 18, 2010, the committee will (1) Receive an update on the Menthol Report Subcommittee and (2) receive and discuss presentations regarding the data requested by the committee at the March 30 and 31, 2010, meeting of the Tobacco Products Scientific Advisory Committee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p sizset="40" sizcache="1"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong sizset="40" sizcache="1"&gt;Meeting Materials&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;Links to meeting materials will be added as they become available.&amp;nbsp; FDA intends to make the complete background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting. If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA&amp;rsquo;s Web site after the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p sizset="41" sizcache="1"&gt;&lt;strong sizset="41" sizcache="1"&gt;Public Participation Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interested persons may present data, information, or views, orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;Written submissions may be made to the contact person on or before &lt;br /&gt;November 9, 2010.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled between approximately &lt;br /&gt;3:00 p.m. and 4:00 p.m. on November 18, 2010.&amp;nbsp; Those desiring to make formal oral&lt;br /&gt;presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the&lt;br /&gt;general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and&lt;br /&gt;addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time&lt;br /&gt;requested to make their presentation on or before November 1, 2010.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Time allotted for each presentation may be limited.&amp;nbsp; If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session.&amp;nbsp; The contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by November 2, 2010.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p sizset="42" sizcache="1"&gt;&lt;strong sizset="42" sizcache="1"&gt;Contact Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;Caryn Cohen, M.S.&lt;br /&gt;Center for Tobacco Products&lt;br /&gt;Food and Drug Administration&lt;br /&gt;9200 Corporate Boulevard &lt;br /&gt;Rockville, MD 20850&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p sizset="43" sizcache="1"&gt;Phone:&amp;nbsp; 1-877-287-1373 (choose Option 4)&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;FAX:&amp;nbsp; 240-276-3761&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;Email:&amp;nbsp; &lt;a href="mailto:TPSAC@fda.hhs.gov"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;font color="#0000ff"&gt;TPSAC@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;FDA Advisory Committee Information Line&lt;br /&gt;1-800-741-8138&lt;br /&gt;(301-443-0572 in the Washington DC area)&lt;br /&gt;Code: 8732110002&lt;br /&gt;Please call the Information Line for up-to-date information on this meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A notice in the Federal Register about last minute modifications that impact a previously announced advisory committee meeting cannot always be published quickly enough to provide timely notice.&amp;nbsp; Therefore, you should always check the agency&amp;rsquo;s Website and call the appropriate advisory committee hot line/phone line to learn about possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting.&amp;nbsp; If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA&amp;rsquo;s Web site after the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p sizset="44" sizcache="1"&gt;Persons attending FDA&amp;rsquo;s advisory committee meetings are advised that the agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets.&amp;nbsp; FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical disabilities or special needs.&amp;nbsp; If you require special accommodations due to a disability, please contact please contact Caryn Cohen at 1-877-287-1373 (choose Option 4) or &lt;a href="mailto:TPSAC@fda.hhs.gov"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;font color="#0000ff"&gt;TPSAC@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; at least 7 days in advance of the meeting.&amp;nbsp; FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its advisory committee meetings.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p sizset="45" sizcache="1"&gt;Please visit our Web site at &lt;a href="http://www.fda.gov/oc/advisory/default.htm"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;font color="#0000ff"&gt;http://www.fda.gov/oc/advisory/default.htm&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; for procedures on public conduct during advisory committee meetings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5 U.S.C. app.2).&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
