<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0" version="8.0.0.0">
<wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;table id="schedule" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="2" summary="This table shows the date, time, and location of the meeting" border="0" style="width: 643px; height: 93px"&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th id="a1" valign="top" align="left" bgcolor="#cccccc" style="width: 71px"&gt;Center&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a2" valign="top" align="left" bgcolor="#cccccc" style="width: 158px"&gt;Date&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a3" valign="top" align="left" bgcolor="#cccccc" style="width: 172px"&gt;Time&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a4" valign="top" align="left" bgcolor="#cccccc" style="width: 238px"&gt;Location&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td valign="top" headers="a1" style="width: 71px; height: 74px"&gt;CDER&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" headers="a2" style="width: 158px; height: 74px"&gt;September 15-16, 2010&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" headers="a3" style="width: 172px; height: 74px"&gt;8:00 a.m. to 5:00 p.m.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" headers="a4" style="width: 238px; height: 75px"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Inn &amp;amp; Conference Center, University of Maryland University College (UMUC) Marriott Conference Centers&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;3501 University Blvd. East&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adelphi, MD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Phone: 301 985-7300&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Agenda&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;On September 15, 2010, the committee will discuss the results of the Sibutramine Cardiovascular Outcomes Trial (SCOUT) (M01&amp;ndash;392), for new drug application (NDA) 20&amp;ndash;632, MERIDIA (sibutramine hydrochloride monohydrate) Capsules, sponsored by Abbott Laboratories, for treatment of obesity. The SCOUT study was a randomized, double-blind, placebo-controlled trial, which is a kind of clinical trial designed to provide data with strong measures of accuracy and reliability. The SCOUT trial evaluated the potential benefits of weight loss with MERIDIA on major cardiovascular (heart and blood circulation) adverse events. The preliminary results of the SCOUT trial indicated that clinical trial participants who received MERIDIA instead of placebo (no active drug) had a higher incidence of major cardiovascular adverse events that was statistically significant.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;On September 16, 2010, the committee will discuss the safety and efficacy of new drug application (NDA) 22&amp;ndash;529, with the proposed trade name LORQESS (lorcaserin hydrochloride) Tablets, sponsored by Arena Pharmaceuticals, Inc., as an adjunct to diet and exercise for weight management in patients with a body mass index (BMI) of equal to or greater than 30 kilograms (kg) per square meter, or a BMI equal to or greater than 27 kg per square meter if accompanied by weight-related co-morbidities (which include, for example: high blood pressure, heart disease, or diabetes). The BMI is a measure of body weight (mass) based on a person&amp;rsquo;s weight and height, and is a widely-used tool for doctors in assessing optimum weights for a patient.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Meeting Materials&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/b&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting.&amp;nbsp; If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA&amp;rsquo;s Web site after the meeting.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','ucm191113.htm')--]"&gt;Background Material&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Public Participation Information&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;Interested persons may present data, information, or views, orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committee.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Written submissions may be made to the contact person on or before August 31,&amp;nbsp;2010.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled between approximately 1 p.m.&amp;ndash;2 p.m. on both days.&amp;nbsp;Those desiring to make formal oral presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before August 23, 2010.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;Time allotted for each presentation may be limited.&amp;nbsp;If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session.&amp;nbsp;The contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by August 24, 2010.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Contact Information&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;Paul Tran, R.Ph.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;Center for Drug Evaluation and Research&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;Food and Drug Administration&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;10903 New Hampshire Avenue&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;WO31-2417&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;Silver Spring, MD&amp;nbsp;20993-0002&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;Phone: 301-796-9001&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;Fax: 301-847-8533&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;Email: &amp;nbsp;paul.tran@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;FDA Advisory Committee Information Line&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;1-800-741-8138&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;(301-443-0572 in the Washington DC area)&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;Code: 3014512536&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;Please call the Information Line for up-to-date information on this meeting.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;A notice in the Federal Register about last minute modifications that impact a previously announced advisory committee meeting cannot always be published quickly enough to provide timely notice.&amp;nbsp;Therefore, you should always check the agency&amp;rsquo;s Web site and call the appropriate advisory committee hot line/phone line to learn about possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting.&amp;nbsp;If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA&amp;rsquo;s Web site after the meeting.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;Persons attending FDA&amp;rsquo;s advisory committee meetings are advised that the agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets.&amp;nbsp;FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical disabilities or special needs.&amp;nbsp;If you require special accommodations due to a disability, please contact Paul Tran at (301) 827-7001 at least 7 days in advance of the meeting.&amp;nbsp;FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its advisory committee meetings.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;Please visit our Web site &lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','ucm111462.htm')--]"&gt;Public Conduct During FDA Advisory Committee Meetings&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5 U.S.C. app.2).&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1">&amp;nbsp;</wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2">&amp;nbsp;</wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3">&amp;nbsp;</wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
