<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;table class="data" id="schedule" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="2" width="100%" summary="This table shows the date, time, and location of the meeting" border="0"&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th id="a2" valign="top" align="left" width="35%" bgcolor="#cccccc" style="height: 19px"&gt;Date&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a3" valign="top" align="left" width="30%" bgcolor="#cccccc" style="height: 19px"&gt;Time&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a4" valign="top" align="left" width="45%" bgcolor="#cccccc" style="height: 19px"&gt;Location&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td valign="top" headers="a2" width="35%" style="height: 64px"&gt;&lt;!-- InstanceBeginEditable name="col2" --&gt;November 17-18,&amp;nbsp;2011&lt;br /&gt;&lt;!-- InstanceEndEditable --&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" headers="a3" width="30%" style="height: 64px"&gt;&lt;!-- InstanceBeginEditable name="col3" --&gt;8:00 a.m. - 5:00 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;!-- InstanceEndEditable --&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" headers="a4" width="45%" style="height: 65px"&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: left"&gt;&lt;!-- InstanceBeginEditable name="col4" --&gt;Food&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;Drug&amp;nbsp;Administration&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: left"&gt;10903 New Hampshire Ave.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: left"&gt;Building 31 Conference Center&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: left"&gt;Great Room (rm. 1503)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: left"&gt;Silver Spring, MD 20993&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;h2 class="BlueBar"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agenda&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;On November 17, 2011, the Committee will discuss results of a literature review (as required in the &lt;span&gt;Patient Protection and Affordable Care Act) about communicating quantitative risk and benefit information in prescription drug promotional labeling and print advertising, and will also receive a briefing on activities in FDA&amp;rsquo;s Office of Special Health Issues.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;On November 18, 2011, the Committee will discuss implications, for strategic communication, of recent theoretical developments on information use in decision-making. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting.&amp;nbsp;If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA's Web site after the meeting.&amp;nbsp;Background material is available at &lt;a href="http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/Calendar/default.htm"&gt;http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/Calendar/default.htm&lt;/a&gt;. Scroll down to the appropriate advisory committee link.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="BlueBar"&gt;Procedure&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Visitors to the White Oak Campus must have a valid driver's license or other picture ID, and must enter through Building 1. Please note visitors can park in the South-west garage near Building 31 or the North-west parking lot near Building 22 (&lt;a target="" href="[!--$ssDownloadLink('UCM194893')--]"&gt;click here for a campus map&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="BlueBar"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="[!--$ssLink(&amp;quot;ucm197164.htm&amp;quot;)--]"&gt;Other Meeting Materials&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="noindent" style="margin-left: 2em"&gt;&lt;h2 class="BlueBar"&gt;Public Participation Information&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interested persons may present data, information, or views, orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committee.&amp;nbsp;Written submissions may be made to the contact person on or before November 9, 2011.&amp;nbsp;Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled between approximately 1 p.m. and 2 p.m. on November 17, 2011, and 10:30 a.m. and 11:30 a.m. on November 18, 2011.&amp;nbsp;Those individuals interested in making formal oral presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before November 3, 2011.&amp;nbsp;to hear and see the proceedings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Time allotted for each presentation may be limited.&amp;nbsp;If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session.&amp;nbsp;The contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by November 4, 2011.&amp;nbsp;Interested persons can also log on to &lt;a title="https://collaboration.fda.gov/rcac/" target="_blank" href="https://collaboration.fda.gov/rcac/"&gt;&lt;span&gt;https://collaboration.fda.gov/rcac/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;!-- InstanceEndEditable --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="BlueBar"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;!-- InstanceBeginEditable name="contact" --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="listspace"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lee L. Zwanziger, Designated Federal Official&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;10903 New Hampshire Avenue, Building 32, Room 3278&lt;br /&gt;Silver Spring, MD 20993&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Phone 301-796-9151&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;FAX: 301-847-8611&lt;br /&gt;e-mail:&amp;nbsp; RCAC@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FDA Advisory Committee Information Line&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1-800-741-8138&lt;br /&gt;301-443-0572 in the Washington, DC, area&lt;br /&gt;code 8732112560&lt;br /&gt;Please call the Information Line for up-to-date information on this meeting.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div&gt;Persons attending FDA's advisory committee meetings are advised that the Agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets. FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical disabilities or special needs. If you require special accommodations due to a disability, please contact Lee L. Zwanziger at least 7 days in advance of the meeting. FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its advisory committee meetings.&amp;nbsp;Please visit our Web site at &lt;a href="http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/AboutAdvisoryCommittees/ucm111462.htm"&gt;http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/AboutAdvisoryCommittees/ucm111462.htm&lt;/a&gt; for procedures on public conduct during advisory committee meetings.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5 U.S.C. app. 2).&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p align="center"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
