<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;p&gt;DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH AND HUMAN SERVICES&lt;br /&gt;
Food and Drug Administration&lt;br /&gt;
[Docket No. FDA–2010–N–0001]&lt;br /&gt;
Orthopaedic and Rehabilitation Devices Panel of the Medical Devices&lt;br /&gt;
Advisory Committee; Notice of Meeting&lt;br /&gt;
AGENCY: Food and Drug Administration, HHS.&lt;br /&gt;
ACTION: Notice.&lt;br /&gt;
This notice announces a forthcoming meeting of a public advisory&lt;br /&gt;
committee of the Food and Drug Administration (FDA). The meeting will be&lt;br /&gt;
open to the public.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Name of Committee: Orthopaedic and Rehabilitation Devices Panel of the&lt;br /&gt;
Medical Devices Advisory Committee.&lt;br /&gt;
General Function of the Committee: To provide advice and&lt;br /&gt;
recommendations to the agency on FDA’s regulatory issues.&lt;br /&gt;
Date and Time: The meeting will be held on July 27, 2010, from 8 a.m.&lt;br /&gt;
to 6 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Location: Holiday Inn, Ballroom, 2 Montgomery Village Ave.,&lt;br /&gt;
Gaithersburg, MD.&lt;br /&gt;
Contact Person: Tracy Phillips, Food and Drug Administration, Center for&lt;br /&gt;
Devices and Radiological Health, 10903 New Hampshire Ave., Bldg. 66, rm.&lt;br /&gt;
1611, Silver Spring, MD 20993–0002, 301–796–6150 or FDA Advisory&lt;br /&gt;
Committee Information Line, 1–800–741–8138 (301–443–0572 in the&lt;br /&gt;
Washington, DC area), code 3014512521. Please call the Information Line for&lt;br /&gt;
up-to-date information on this meeting. A notice in the Federal Register about&lt;br /&gt;
last minute modifications that impact a previously announced advisory&lt;br /&gt;
committee meeting cannot always be published quickly enough to provide&lt;br /&gt;
timely notice. Therefore, you should always check the agency’s Web site and&lt;br /&gt;
call the appropriate advisory committee hot line/phone line to learn about&lt;br /&gt;
possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&lt;br /&gt;
Agenda: On July 27, 2010, the committee will discuss, make&lt;br /&gt;
recommendations and vote on a premarket approval application for the&lt;br /&gt;
AMPLIFY rhBMP-2 Matrix, sponsored by Medtronic, Inc. The AMPLIFY&lt;br /&gt;
rhBMP-2 Matrix is used for posterolateral fusion treatment of single level&lt;br /&gt;
lumbar (L2–S1) degenerative disc disease.&lt;br /&gt;
FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later&lt;br /&gt;
than 2 business days before the meeting. If FDA is unable to post the&lt;br /&gt;
background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background&lt;br /&gt;
material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory&lt;br /&gt;
committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA’s Web&lt;br /&gt;
site after the meeting. Background material is available at http://www.fda.gov/&lt;br /&gt;
AdvisoryCommittees/Calendar/default.htm. Scroll down to the appropriate&lt;br /&gt;
advisory committee link.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Procedure: Interested persons may present data, information, or views,&lt;br /&gt;
orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committee. Written&lt;br /&gt;
submissions may be made to the contact person on or before July 21, 2010.&lt;br /&gt;
Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled between approximately&lt;br /&gt;
1 and 2 p.m., immediately following lunch. Those desiring to make formal oral&lt;br /&gt;
presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement&lt;br /&gt;
of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the&lt;br /&gt;
names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the&lt;br /&gt;
approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before July 13,&lt;br /&gt;
2010. Time allotted for each presentation may be limited. If the number of&lt;br /&gt;
registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated&lt;br /&gt;
during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery&lt;br /&gt;
to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session. The&lt;br /&gt;
contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak&lt;br /&gt;
by July 14, 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Persons attending FDA’s advisory committee meetings are advised that the&lt;br /&gt;
agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets.&lt;br /&gt;
FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee&lt;br /&gt;
meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical&lt;br /&gt;
disabilities or special needs. If you require special accommodations due to a&lt;br /&gt;
disability, please contact AnnMarie Williams, Conference Management Staff,&lt;br /&gt;
301–796–5966, at least 7 days in advance of the meeting.&lt;br /&gt;
FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its advisory committee&lt;br /&gt;
meetings. Please visit our Web site at http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/&lt;br /&gt;
AboutAdvisoryCommittees/ucm111462.htm for procedures on public conduct&lt;br /&gt;
during advisory committee meetings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act&lt;br /&gt;
(5 U.S.C. app. 2).&lt;br /&gt;
Dated: June 18, 2010.&lt;br /&gt;
Thinh Nguyen,&lt;br /&gt;
Acting Associate Commissioner for Special Medical Programs.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
