<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;table cellspacing="0" cellpadding="2" border="0" summary="This table shows the date, time, and location of the meeting" style="WIDTH: 643px" id="schedule"&gt;     &lt;tbody&gt;         &lt;tr&gt;             &lt;th valign="top" bgcolor="#cccccc" align="left" style="WIDTH: 71px" id="a1"&gt;Center&lt;/th&gt;             &lt;th valign="top" bgcolor="#cccccc" align="left" style="WIDTH: 158px" id="a2"&gt;Date&lt;/th&gt;             &lt;th valign="top" bgcolor="#cccccc" align="left" style="WIDTH: 172px" id="a3"&gt;Time&lt;/th&gt;             &lt;th valign="top" bgcolor="#cccccc" align="left" style="WIDTH: 238px" id="a4"&gt;Location&lt;/th&gt;         &lt;/tr&gt;         &lt;tr&gt;             &lt;td valign="top" height="61" headers="a1" style="WIDTH: 71px"&gt;CDER&lt;/td&gt;             &lt;td valign="top" headers="a2" style="WIDTH: 158px"&gt;December 1, 2011&lt;br /&gt;             &amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;             &lt;td valign="top" headers="a3" style="WIDTH: 172px"&gt;8:00 a.m. to 5:00  p.m.&lt;br /&gt;             &lt;br /&gt;             &amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;             &lt;td valign="top" headers="a4" style="WIDTH: 238px"&gt;FDA White Oak Campus&lt;br /&gt;             Building 31&lt;br /&gt;             The Great Room (Rm. 1503)&lt;br /&gt;             White Oak Conference Center&lt;br /&gt;             10903 New Hampshire Avenue&lt;br /&gt;             Silver Spring, Maryland&lt;/td&gt;         &lt;/tr&gt;     &lt;/tbody&gt; &lt;/table&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h4&gt;Agenda&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;The Food and Drug Administration Amendments Act of 2007 (Public Law 110-85) requires FDA to bring, at least annually, one or more drugs with Risk Evaluation and Mitigation Strategies (REMS) with Elements to Assure Safe Use (ETASU) before its Drug Safety and Risk Management Advisory Committee (DSaRM).  On December 1, 2011, the DSaRM and the Dermatologic and Ophthalmic Drugs Advisory Committees will meet in joint session to discuss REMS-related topics.  During the morning session, the committees will discuss the REMS program for isotretinoin, also known as iPLEDGE, as an example of a REMS that has ETASU. During the afternoon session, the committees will discuss general issues related to the impact of REMS with ETASU on the healthcare system and patient access, such as how programs with ETASU can be better integrated into existing health systems.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h4&gt;Meeting Materials&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting.  If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA&amp;rsquo;s Web site after the meeting.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h4&gt;Background Material&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;ul&gt;     &lt;li&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;font color="#810081"&gt;     &lt;div&gt;&lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM250295')--]"&gt;2011 Meeting Materials, Drug Safety and Risk Management Advisory Committee&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;     &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;h4&gt;Public Participation Information&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;Interested persons may present data, information, or views, orally or in  writing, on issues pending before the committee.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt;     &lt;li&gt;Written submissions may be made to the contact person on or before&amp;nbsp;November 16, 2011.&lt;/li&gt;     &lt;li&gt;Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled between approximately 9:40 a.m. to 10:10 a.m. (for comments related to iPLEDGE), and from 2:20 p.m. to 2:50 p.m. (for other REMS-related comments). Those individuals interested in making formal oral presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before November 7, 2011.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;Time allotted for each presentation may be limited.  If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session. The contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by November 8, 2011.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h4&gt;Webcast Information&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;CDER plans to provide a free of charge, live webcast of the December 1, 2011, Joint Meeting of the Drug Safety and Risk Management Advisory Committee and the Dermatologic and Ophthalmic Drugs Advisory Committee.  While CDER is working to make webcasts available to the public for all advisory committee meetings held at the White Oak campus, there are instances where the webcast transmission is not successful; staff will work to re-establish the transmission as soon as possible.  Further information regarding the webcast, including the web address for the webcast, will be made available at least 2 days in advance of the meeting at the following website: &lt;a href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM250295')--]" target=""&gt;2011 Meeting Materials, Drug Safety and Risk Management Advisory Committee&lt;/a&gt;. CDER plans to post archived webcasts after the meeting, however, in cases where transmission was not successful, archived webcasts will not be available.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;ul&gt;     &lt;li&gt;Kristina A. Toliver, Pharm.D.&lt;br /&gt;     Center for Drug Evaluation and  Research&lt;br /&gt;     Food and Drug Administration&lt;br /&gt;     10903 New Hampshire  Avenue&lt;br /&gt;     WO31-2417&lt;br /&gt;     Silver Spring, Maryland 20993-0002&lt;br /&gt;     Phone:  301-796-9001&lt;br /&gt;     Fax: 301-847-8533&lt;br /&gt;     E-mail: &lt;a href="mailto:DSaRM@fda.hhs.gov"&gt;DSaRM@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;ul&gt;     &lt;li&gt;FDA Advisory Committee Information Line&lt;br /&gt;     1-800-741-8138&lt;br /&gt;     (301-443-0572  in the Washington DC area) follow the prompts to the desired center or product  area&lt;br /&gt;     Please call the Information Line for up-to-date information on this  meeting.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;A notice in the Federal Register about last minute modifications that impact a previously announced advisory committee meeting cannot always be published quickly enough to provide timely notice.  Therefore, you should always check the agency&amp;rsquo;s Web site and call the appropriate advisory committee hot line/phone line to learn about possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Persons attending FDA&amp;rsquo;s advisory committee meetings are advised that the agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets.  FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical disabilities or special needs. If you require special accommodations due to a disability, please contact Kristina Toliver at (301) 796-9001 at least 7 days in advance of the meeting.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Information regarding ground transportation, airport information, lodging, driving directions and visitor parking, and security can be accessed at: &lt;a href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM241740')--]" target=""&gt;Public Meetings at the FDA White Oak Campus&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its  advisory committee meetings. Please visit our Web site at &lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM111462')--]"&gt;Public Conduct During FDA Advisory Committee  Meetings&lt;/a&gt; for  procedures on public conduct during advisory committee meetings.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5  U.S.C. app.2).&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
