<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;p&gt;&lt;table cellspacing="0" cellpadding="2" border="0" id="schedule" style="WIDTH: 643px; HEIGHT: 93px" summary="This table shows the date, time, and location of the meeting"&gt;     &lt;tbody&gt;         &lt;tr&gt;             &lt;th valign="top" bgcolor="#cccccc" align="left" id="a1" style="WIDTH: 71px"&gt;Center&lt;/th&gt;             &lt;th valign="top" bgcolor="#cccccc" align="left" id="a2" style="WIDTH: 158px"&gt;Date&lt;/th&gt;             &lt;th valign="top" bgcolor="#cccccc" align="left" id="a3" style="WIDTH: 172px"&gt;Time&lt;/th&gt;             &lt;th valign="top" bgcolor="#cccccc" align="left" id="a4" style="WIDTH: 238px"&gt;Location&lt;/th&gt;         &lt;/tr&gt;         &lt;tr&gt;             &lt;td valign="top" style="WIDTH: 71px; HEIGHT: 74px" headers="a1"&gt;CDER&lt;/td&gt;             &lt;td valign="top" style="WIDTH: 158px; HEIGHT: 74px" headers="a2"&gt;March 14,  2012&lt;br /&gt;             &amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;             &lt;td valign="top" style="WIDTH: 172px; HEIGHT: 74px" headers="a3"&gt;7:30 a.m. to 3:00  p.m.&lt;br /&gt;             &amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;             &lt;td valign="top" style="WIDTH: 238px; HEIGHT: 75px" headers="a4"&gt;&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Gaylord National Hotel and&lt;/p&gt;             &lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Convention Center&lt;/p&gt;             &lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Maryland Ballroom C&lt;/p&gt;             &lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;201 Waterfront   Street&lt;/p&gt;             &lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;National Harbor, Maryland&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;         &lt;/tr&gt;     &lt;/tbody&gt; &lt;/table&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agenda&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;On March 14, 2012, the committee will discuss the clinical pharmacology aspects of pediatric clinical trial design and dosing to optimize pediatric drug development.  FDA will seek input on how to strategically inform pediatric clinical trial design and dosing by utilizing existing knowledge, including available adult and nonclinical data.  The discussion will include the role of modeling and simulation including physiologically-based pharmacokinetic modeling in pediatric drug development. Modeling and simulation is the application of mathematical approaches to predicting what will happen in a clinical trial with pediatric patients when a particular dose of a drug is used.&lt;!--[if gte mso 9]&gt;&lt;xml&gt;
&lt;w:WordDocument&gt;
&lt;w:View&gt;Normal&lt;/w:View&gt;
&lt;w:Zoom&gt;0&lt;/w:Zoom&gt;
&lt;w:PunctuationKerning /&gt;
&lt;w:ValidateAgainstSchemas /&gt;
&lt;w:SaveIfXMLInvalid&gt;false&lt;/w:SaveIfXMLInvalid&gt;
&lt;w:IgnoreMixedContent&gt;false&lt;/w:IgnoreMixedContent&gt;
&lt;w:AlwaysShowPlaceholderText&gt;false&lt;/w:AlwaysShowPlaceholderText&gt;
&lt;w:Compatibility&gt;
&lt;w:BreakWrappedTables /&gt;
&lt;w:SnapToGridInCell /&gt;
&lt;w:WrapTextWithPunct /&gt;
&lt;w:UseAsianBreakRules /&gt;
&lt;w:DontGrowAutofit /&gt;
&lt;/w:Compatibility&gt;
&lt;w:BrowserLevel&gt;MicrosoftInternetExplorer4&lt;/w:BrowserLevel&gt;
&lt;/w:WordDocument&gt;
&lt;/xml&gt;&lt;![endif]--&gt;&lt;!--[if gte mso 9]&gt;&lt;xml&gt;
&lt;w:LatentStyles DefLockedState="false" LatentStyleCount="156"&gt;
&lt;/w:LatentStyles&gt;
&lt;/xml&gt;&lt;![endif]--&gt;&lt;!--[if gte mso 10]&gt;
&lt;style&gt;
/* Style Definitions */
table.MsoNormalTable
{mso-style-name:"Table Normal";
mso-tstyle-rowband-size:0;
mso-tstyle-colband-size:0;
mso-style-noshow:yes;
mso-style-parent:"";
mso-padding-alt:0in 5.4pt 0in 5.4pt;
mso-para-margin:0in;
mso-para-margin-bottom:.0001pt;
mso-pagination:widow-orphan;
font-size:10.0pt;
font-family:"Times New Roman";
mso-ansi-language:#0400;
mso-fareast-language:#0400;
mso-bidi-language:#0400;}
&lt;/style&gt;
&lt;![endif]--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meeting Materials&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later than  2 business days before the meeting. If FDA is unable to post the background  material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be  made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and  the background material will be posted on FDA&amp;rsquo;s Web site after the meeting.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Background Material&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt;     &lt;li&gt;&lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM286697')--]"&gt;2012 Meeting Materials, Pharmaceutical Science and Clinical  Pharmacology Advisory Committee&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Public Participation Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Interested persons may present data, information, or views, orally or in  writing, on issues pending before the committee.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul class="noindent"&gt;     &lt;li&gt;Written submissions may be made to the contact person on or before February 29,  2012.&lt;/li&gt;     &lt;li&gt;Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled between approximately  10:45 a.m. to 11:15 a.m. Those desiring to make formal  oral presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement  of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the  names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the  approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before February 21,  2012.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;Time allotted for each presentation may be limited. If the number of  registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated  during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to  determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session. The  contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak  by February 22, 2012.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Webcast Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CDER will not be providing a webcast of the Advisory Committee for Pharmaceutical Science and Clinical Pharmacology meeting.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt;     &lt;li&gt;Yvette Waples, Pharm.D.&lt;br /&gt;     Center for Drug  Evaluation and Research&lt;br /&gt;     Food and Drug Administration&lt;br /&gt;     10903 New Hampshire  Avenue&lt;br /&gt;     WO31-2417&lt;br /&gt;     Silver Spring, MD 20993-0002&lt;br /&gt;     Phone:  301-796-9001&lt;br /&gt;     Fax: 301-847-8533&lt;br /&gt;     E-mail:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="mailto:ACPS-CP@fda.hhs.gov"&gt;ACPS-CP@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;ul&gt;     &lt;li&gt;FDA Advisory Committee Information Line&lt;br /&gt;     1-800-741-8138 (301-443-0572  in the Washington DC area)&lt;br /&gt;Please call the Information  Line for up-to-date information on this meeting&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;A notice in the Federal Register about last minute modifications that impact  a previously announced advisory committee meeting cannot always be published  quickly enough to provide timely notice. Therefore, you should always check the  agency&amp;rsquo;s Web site and call the FDA Advisory Committee Information Line to learn about possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Persons attending FDA&amp;rsquo;s advisory committee meetings are advised that the  agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets. FDA  welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee meetings and  will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical disabilities or  special needs. If you require special accommodations due to a disability, please  contact Yvette Waples at (301) 796-9001 at least 7 days in advance of the  meeting.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its  advisory committee meetings. Please visit our Web site at &lt;a href="/AdvisoryCommittees/AboutAdvisoryCommittees/ucm111462.htm" target=""&gt;Public Conduct During FDA Advisory Committee Meetings&lt;/a&gt; for procedures on public conduct  during advisory committee meetings&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5  U.S.C. app.2).&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
