<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;table cellspacing="0" cellpadding="2" border="0" style="width: 643px" summary="This table shows the date, time, and location of the meeting" id="schedule"&gt;     &lt;tbody&gt;         &lt;tr&gt;             &lt;th bgcolor="#cccccc" align="left" valign="top" style="width: 71px" id="a1"&gt;Center&lt;/th&gt;             &lt;th bgcolor="#cccccc" align="left" valign="top" style="width: 158px" id="a2"&gt;Date&lt;/th&gt;             &lt;th bgcolor="#cccccc" align="left" valign="top" style="width: 172px" id="a3"&gt;Time&lt;/th&gt;             &lt;th bgcolor="#cccccc" align="left" valign="top" style="width: 238px" id="a4"&gt;Location&lt;/th&gt;         &lt;/tr&gt;         &lt;tr&gt;             &lt;td height="61" valign="top" style="width: 71px" headers="a1"&gt;CDER&lt;/td&gt;             &lt;td valign="top" style="width: 158px" headers="a2"&gt;March 8, 2011&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;             &lt;td valign="top" style="width: 172px" headers="a3"&gt;8:00 a.m. - 5:00 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;             &amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;             &lt;td valign="top" style="width: 238px" headers="a4"&gt;&lt;div&gt;FDA White Oak Campus&lt;/div&gt;             &lt;div&gt;Building 31, the Great Room&lt;/div&gt;             &lt;div&gt;White Oak Conference Center (Rm. 1503)&lt;/div&gt;             10903 New Hampshire Avenue, Silver Spring, MD&lt;/td&gt;         &lt;/tr&gt;     &lt;/tbody&gt; &lt;/table&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Agenda&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;The Committee will discuss new drug application (NDA) No. 22-383, indacaterol maleate (Arcapta&amp;trade; Neohaler&amp;trade;) by Novartis Pharmaceuticals Corporation, for the long-term once daily maintenance bronchodilator treatment of airflow obstruction in patients with chronic obstructive pulmonary disease (COPD), including chronic bronchitis and/or emphysema&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Meeting Materials&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;FDA intends to make the complete background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting.&amp;nbsp; If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA&amp;rsquo;s Web site after the meeting.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Public Participation Information&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;Interested persons may present data, information, or views, orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committee.&lt;/div&gt; &lt;ul&gt;     &lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;W&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;ritten submissions may be made to the contact person on or before February 22, 2011.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;ul&gt;     &lt;li&gt;Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled between approximately 1:00 p.m. to 2:00 p.m., on March 8, 2011.&amp;nbsp;Those desiring to make formal oral presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before February 11, 2011.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;Time allotted for each presentation may be limited.&amp;nbsp;If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session.&amp;nbsp;The contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by February 14, 2011.&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Contact Information&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;ul&gt;     &lt;li&gt;Kristine T. Khuc, Pharm.D.&lt;br /&gt;     Center for Drug Evaluation and Research&lt;br /&gt;     Food and Drug Administration&lt;br /&gt;     10903 New Hampshire Avenue&lt;br /&gt;     WO31-2417, Silver Spring, MD 20993-0002&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;     Phone:&amp;nbsp;301-796-9001&lt;br /&gt;     FAX: &amp;nbsp;301-847-8533&lt;br /&gt;     E-mail: &lt;a href="mailto:Kristine.Khuc@fda.hhs.gov"&gt;Kristine.Khuc@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;ul&gt;     &lt;li&gt;FDA Advisory Committee Information Line&lt;br /&gt;     1-800-741-8138&lt;br /&gt;     (301-443-0572 in the Washington DC area)- follow the prompts to the desired center or product area&lt;br /&gt;     Please call the Information Line for up-to-date information on this meeting.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;A notice in the Federal Register about last minute modifications that impact a previously announced advisory committee meeting cannot always be published quickly enough to provide timely notice.&amp;nbsp;Therefore, you should always check the agency&amp;rsquo;s Website and call the appropriate advisory committee hot line/phone line to learn about possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting.&amp;nbsp;If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA&amp;rsquo;s Web site after the meeting.&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;Persons attending FDA&amp;rsquo;s advisory committee meetings are advised that the agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets.&amp;nbsp;FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical disabilities or special needs.&amp;nbsp;If you require special accommodations due to a disability, please contact Kristine T. Khuc at (301) 796-9001 at least 7 days in advance of the meeting.&amp;nbsp;FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its advisory committee meetings.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;p&gt;Information regarding ground transportation, airport information, lodging, driving directions and visitor parking, and security can be accessed at: &lt;a href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','ucm241740.htm')--]" target=""&gt;Public Meetings at the FDA White Oak Campus&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Please visit our Web site at &lt;a href="http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/AboutAdvisoryCommittees/ucm111462.htm"&gt;Public Conduct During FDA Advisory Committee Meetings&lt;/a&gt; for procedures on public conduct during advisory committee meetings.&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="text-align: left"&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5 U.S.C. app.2)&lt;/div&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
