<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH AND HUMAN SERVICES&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Food and Drug Administration&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[Docket No. FDA-2011-N-0478]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;General and Plastic Surgery Devices Panel of the Medical Devices Advisory Committee; Amendment of Notice&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;AGENCY:&amp;nbsp; Food and Drug Administration, HHS.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ACTION:&amp;nbsp; Notice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Food and Drug Administration (FDA) is announcing an amendment to the notice of meeting of the General and Plastic Surgery Devices Panel of the Medical Devices Advisory Committee.&amp;nbsp; This meeting was announced in the &lt;u&gt;Federal Register&lt;/u&gt; of July 7, 2011 (76 FR 39882).&amp;nbsp; The amendment is being made to reflect a change in the &lt;u&gt;Contact Person&lt;/u&gt; portion of the document.&amp;nbsp; There are no other changes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;FOR FURTHER INFORMATION CONTACT:&amp;nbsp; James Swink, Center for Devices and Radiological Health, Food and Drug Administration, 10903 New Hampshire Ave., Bldg. 66, rm. 1609, Silver Spring, MD 20993-0002, 301-796-6313, or FDA Advisory Committee Information Line, 1-800-741-8138 (301-443-0572 in the Washington DC area), and follow the prompts to the desired center or product area.&amp;nbsp; Please call the Information Line for up-to-date information on this meeting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SUPPLEMENTARY INFORMATION:&amp;nbsp; In the &lt;u&gt;Federal Register&lt;/u&gt; of July 7, 2011, FDA announced that a meeting of the General and Plastic Surgery Devices Panel of the Medical Devices Advisory Committee would be held on August 30 and 31, 2011. On page 39883, in the first column, the &lt;u&gt;Contact Person&lt;/u&gt; portion of the document is changed to read as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;Contact Person&lt;/u&gt;: James Swink, Center for Devices and Radiological Health, Food and Drug Administration, 10903 New Hampshire Ave., Bldg. 66, rm. 1609, Silver Spring, MD 20993-0002, 301-796-6313, or FDA Advisory Committee Information Line, 1-800-741-8138 (301-443-0572 in the Washington, DC area), and follow the prompts to the desired center or product area.&amp;nbsp; Please call the Information Line for up-to-date information on this meeting.&amp;nbsp; A notice in the &lt;u&gt;Federal Register&lt;/u&gt; about last minute modifications that impact a previously announced advisory committee meeting cannot always be published quickly enough to provide timely notice.&amp;nbsp; Therefore, you should always check the Agency&amp;rsquo;s Web site and call the appropriate advisory committee hot line/phone line to learn about possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This notice is issued under the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5 U.S.C. app. 2) and 21 CFR part 14, relating to the advisory committees.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dated: July 13, 2011.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Leslie Kux,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Acting Assistant Commissioner for Policy.&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
