<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;p&gt;Circulatory System Devices Panel of&lt;br /&gt;
the Medical Devices Advisory&lt;br /&gt;
Committee; Notice of Meeting&lt;br /&gt;
AGENCY: Food and Drug Administration, HHS.&lt;br /&gt;
ACTION: Notice.&lt;br /&gt;
This notice announces a forthcoming meeting of a public advisory committee&lt;br /&gt;
of the Food and Drug Administration (FDA). The meeting will be open to the&lt;br /&gt;
public.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Name of Committee: Circulatory System Devices Panel of the Medical&lt;br /&gt;
Devices Advisory Committee.&lt;br /&gt;
General Function of the Committee:To provide advice and&lt;br /&gt;
recommendations to the agency on FDA’s regulatory issues.&lt;br /&gt;
Date and Time: The meeting will be held on March 18 and 19, 2010, from 8&lt;br /&gt;
a.m. to 6 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Location: College Park Holiday Inn,&lt;br /&gt;
Grand Ballroom, 10000 Baltimore Ave.,&lt;br /&gt;
College Park, MD.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Contact Person: James Swink, Center&lt;br /&gt;
for Devices and Radiological Health,&lt;br /&gt;
Food and Drug Administration, 10903&lt;br /&gt;
New Hampshire Ave., Silver Spring, MD 20993, 301–796–6313,&amp;#160;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;e-mail: James.Swink@fda.hhs.gov, or FDA&lt;br /&gt;
Advisory Committee Information Line, 1–800–741–8138 (301–443–0572 in the&lt;br /&gt;
Washington, DC area), code 3014512625. Please call the Information&lt;br /&gt;
Line for up-to-date information on this meeting. A notice in the Federal&lt;br /&gt;
Register about last minute modifications that impact a previously announced&lt;br /&gt;
advisory committee meeting cannot always be published quickly enough to&lt;br /&gt;
provide timely notice. Therefore, you should always check the agency’s Web&lt;br /&gt;
site and call the appropriate advisory committee hot line/phone line to learn&lt;br /&gt;
about possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&lt;br /&gt;
Agenda: On March 18, 2010, the committee will discuss, make&lt;br /&gt;
recommendations, and vote on the premarket approval application (PMA)&lt;br /&gt;
for the Cardiac Resynchronization Therapy Defibrillators (CRT–Ds)&lt;br /&gt;
sponsored by Boston Scientific. The sponsor is seeking expanded indications&lt;br /&gt;
for the their CRT–Ds to include patients with low left ventricular ejection&lt;br /&gt;
fraction (≤30%) and wide QRS (≥130 ms) who are NYHA Class II (ischemic or&lt;br /&gt;
non-ischemic etiology) or NYHA Class I (ischemic etiology).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
On March 19, 2010, the committee will discuss, make recommendations&lt;br /&gt;
and vote on a PMA for the REVO MRI Pacemaker System sponsored by&lt;br /&gt;
Medtronic. The REVO MRI Pacing System is a pacemaker (with a standard&lt;br /&gt;
pacing indication) that has been specifically designed to be safe for the&lt;br /&gt;
MRI environment under certain MR scanning conditions.&lt;br /&gt;
FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later&lt;br /&gt;
than 2 business days before the meeting. If FDA is unable to post the background&lt;br /&gt;
material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will&lt;br /&gt;
be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee&lt;br /&gt;
meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA’s Web site after&lt;br /&gt;
the meeting. Background material is available at http://www.fda.gov/&lt;br /&gt;
AdvisoryCommittees/Calendar/default.htm, scroll down to the&lt;br /&gt;
appropriate advisory committee link.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Procedure: Interested persons may present data, information, or views,&lt;br /&gt;
orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committee. Written&lt;br /&gt;
submissions may be made to the contact person on or before March 11, 2010.&lt;br /&gt;
Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled immediately following&lt;br /&gt;
lunch. Those desiring to make formal oral presentations should notify the&lt;br /&gt;
contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the&lt;br /&gt;
evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of&lt;br /&gt;
proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time&lt;br /&gt;
requested to make their presentation on or before March 3, 2010. Time allotted&lt;br /&gt;
for each presentation may be limited. If the number of registrants requesting to&lt;br /&gt;
speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled&lt;br /&gt;
open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the&lt;br /&gt;
speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session. The contact person will&lt;br /&gt;
notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by March 4, 2010.&lt;br /&gt;
Persons attending FDA’s advisory committee meetings are advised that the&lt;br /&gt;
agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets.&lt;br /&gt;
FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee&lt;br /&gt;
meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical&lt;br /&gt;
disabilities or special needs. If you require special accommodations due to&lt;br /&gt;
a disability, please contact AnnMarie Williams at 301–796–5966 at least 7&lt;br /&gt;
days in advance of the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its advisory committee&lt;br /&gt;
meetings. Please visit our Web site at http://www.fda.gov/Advisory&lt;br /&gt;
Committees/AboutAdvisoryCommittees/ucm111462.htm for procedures on&lt;br /&gt;
public conduct during advisory committee meetings.&lt;br /&gt;
Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5&lt;br /&gt;
U.S.C. app. 2).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dated: February 4, 2010.&lt;br /&gt;
Jill Hartzler Warner,&lt;br /&gt;
Acting Associate Commissioner for Special&lt;br /&gt;
Medical Programs.&lt;br /&gt;
[FR Doc. 2010–3032 Filed 2–17–10; 8:45 am]&lt;br /&gt;
BILLING CODE 4160–01–S&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
