<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;div class="table-responsive"&gt;&#13;
&lt;table class="table table-hover"&gt;&#13;
    &lt;tbody&gt;&#13;
    &lt;thead&gt;&#13;
        &lt;tr&gt;&#13;
            &lt;th scope="col"&gt;Center&lt;/th&gt;&#13;
            &lt;th scope="col"&gt;Date&lt;/th&gt;&#13;
            &lt;th scope="col"&gt;Time&lt;/th&gt;&#13;
            &lt;th scope="col"&gt;Location&lt;/th&gt;&#13;
        &lt;/tr&gt;&#13;
        &lt;/thead&gt;&#13;
        &lt;tr&gt;&#13;
            &lt;td&gt;OC&lt;/td&gt;&#13;
            &lt;td&gt;May 6, 2014&lt;/td&gt;&#13;
            &lt;td &gt;9:00 a.m. - 5:30 p.m.&lt;/td&gt;&#13;
            &lt;td&gt;&#13;
            Food and Drug Administration&#13;
            10903 New Hampshire Ave.&gt;&#13;
            Building 31, Conference Center&gt;&#13;
            The Great Room (Rm. 1503)&gt;&#13;
            Silver Spring, MD 20993&#13;
            &lt;/td&gt;&#13;
        &lt;/tr&gt;&#13;
    &lt;/tbody&gt;&#13;
&lt;/table&gt;&#13;
&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;h4&gt;Agenda&lt;/h4&gt;&#13;
&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;On May 5-6, 2014, the Committee will meet to discuss methods for identifying the impact and increasing the reach of communications on topics of interest to consumers. The discussion will also address how FDA can evaluate whether its Consumer Updates (&lt;a  href="[!--$ssExternalLink('UCM191400')--]"&gt;http://www.fda.gov/ForConsumers/ConsumerUpdates/default.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a title="Disclaimer Icon" href="http://www.fda.gov/AboutFDA/AboutThisWebsite/WebsitePolicies/Disclaimers/default.htm"&gt; &lt;img src="[!--$wcmUrl('resource','groups/fdagov-public/@system/documents/system/img_fdagov_exitdisclaimer.png')--]" /&gt; &lt;/a&gt;) are reaching the targeted population, and whether they are increasing awareness and understanding of the key risk messages. The discussion will also assess whether the communications are having the intended impact on knowledge, behaviors and/or outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting. If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA's Web site after the meeting. Background material is available on the &lt;a  href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM380631')--]"&gt;RCAC meeting materials page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;h4&gt;Procedure&lt;/h4&gt;&#13;
&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Information regarding special accommodations due to a disability, visitor parking, and transportation may be accessed at &amp;quot;&lt;a  href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM241740')--]"&gt;Public Meetings on the FDA White Oak Campus&lt;/a&gt;&amp;quot; on the FDA website. Please note that visitors to the White Oak Campus must enter through Building 1.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;A notice in the Federal Register about last minute modifications that impact a previously announced advisory committee meeting cannot always be published quickly enough to provide timely notice. Therefore, you should always check the Agency's Web site at &lt;a  href="[!--$ssExternalLink('UCM296707')--]"&gt;http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/default.htm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a title="Disclaimer Icon" href="http://www.fda.gov/AboutFDA/AboutThisWebsite/WebsitePolicies/Disclaimers/default.htm"&gt; &lt;img src="[!--$wcmUrl('resource','groups/fdagov-public/@system/documents/system/img_fdagov_exitdisclaimer.png')--]" /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt; and scroll down to the appropriate advisory committee meeting link, or call the advisory committee information line to learn about possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;h4&gt;Public Participation Information&lt;/h4&gt;&#13;
&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Interested persons may present data, information, or views, orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committee.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;ul&gt;&#13;
    &lt;li&gt;Written submissions may be made to the contact person on or before April 28, 2014.&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
    &lt;li&gt;Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled between approximately 1 p.m. and 2 p.m. on May 5, 2014.&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
   &lt;li&gt; Those individuals desiring to make formal oral presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before April 18, 2014. Time allotted for each presentation may be limited. If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session.&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
    &lt;li&gt;The contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by April 21, 2014.&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Interested persons can also log on to &lt;a  href="[!--$ssExternalLink('UCM323619')--]"&gt;https://collaboration.fda.gov/rcac/&lt;/a&gt; to hear and see the proceedings.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;h4&gt;Contact Information&lt;/h4&gt;&#13;
&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Luis G. Bravo, Designated Federal Official&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;P&gt;10903 New Hampshire Ave., Building 32, Room 3274&lt;br&gt;&#13;
Silver Spring, Maryland 20993&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;strong&gt;Phone: 240-402-5274&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
Fax: 301-847-8609&lt;br&gt;&#13;
E-mail: &lt;a href="mailto:RCAC@fda.hhs.gov"&gt;RCAC@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;ul&gt;&#13;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FDA Advisory Committee Information Line&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
    1-800-741-8138&lt;br&gt;&#13;
    (301-443-0572 in the Washington DC area)&lt;br&gt;&#13;
    Please call the Information Line for up-to-date information on this meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#13;
&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Persons attending FDA&amp;rsquo;s advisory committee meetings are advised that the agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical disabilities or special needs. If you require special accommodations due to a disability, please contact Luis G. Bravo at least 7 days in advance of the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its advisory committee meetings. Please visit our Web site at &lt;a  href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM111462')--]"&gt;http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/AboutAdvisoryCommittees/ucm111462.htm&lt;/a&gt; for procedures on public conduct during advisory committee meetings.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5 U.S.C. app. 2). Official FR Notice&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
