<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;div class="table-responsive"&gt;&lt;table class="table table-condensed table-bordered align-top" summary="This table shows the date, time, and location of the meeting"&gt;&lt;thead&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th bgcolor="#cccccc" scope="col"&gt;Center&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th bgcolor="#cccccc" scope="col"&gt;Date&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th bgcolor="#cccccc" scope="col"&gt;Time&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th bgcolor="#cccccc" scope="col"&gt;Location&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;CDRH&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;May 13, 2014&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;8:00 a.m. - 6:00 p.m.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Holiday Inn Express/Highlands Conference Center&lt;br /&gt;Oak I and II Conference Rooms&lt;br /&gt;20260 Goldenrod Lane&lt;br /&gt;Germantown, MD 20876&lt;br /&gt;301-605-1434&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH AND HUMAN SERVICES&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Food and Drug Administration&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[Docket No. FDA-2014-N-0314]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ophthalmic Devices Panel of the Medical Devices Advisory Committee; Notice of Meeting&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;AGENCY: Food and Drug Administration, HHS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ACTION: Notice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This notice announces a forthcoming meeting of a public advisory committee of the Food and Drug Administration (FDA).&amp;nbsp; The meeting will be open to the public.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Name of Committee: Ophthalmic Devices Panel of the Medical Devices Advisory Committee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Function of the Committee&lt;/strong&gt;:&amp;nbsp; To provide advice and recommendations to the Agency on FDA's regulatory issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Date and Time&lt;/strong&gt;: The meeting will be held on May 13, 2014, from 8 a.m. to 6 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location&lt;/strong&gt;:&amp;nbsp; Holiday Inn Express/Highlands Conference Center, Oak I and II Conference Rooms, 20260 Goldenrod Lane, Germantown, MD 20876.&amp;nbsp; The hotel's phone number is 301-605-1434.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact Person&lt;/strong&gt;: Natasha Facey, Center for Devices and Radiological Health, Food and Drug Administration, 10903 New Hampshire Ave., Bldg. 66, rm. 1552, Silver Spring, MD 20993, 301-796-5290, &lt;a href="mailto:Natasha.Facey@fda.hhs.gov"&gt;Natasha.Facey@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/a&gt;, or FDA Advisory Committee Information Line, 1-800-741-8138 (301-443-0572 in the Washington, DC area).&amp;nbsp; A notice in the Federal Register about last minute modifications that impact a previously announced advisory committee meeting cannot always be published quickly enough to provide timely notice.&amp;nbsp; Therefore, you should always check the Agency's Web site at &lt;a href="http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/default.htm"&gt;http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/default.htm&lt;/a&gt; and scroll down to the appropriate advisory committee meeting link, or call the advisory committee information line to learn about possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agenda&lt;/strong&gt;:&amp;nbsp; On May 13, 2014, the committee will discuss and make recommendations regarding the guidance documents for contact lenses and contact lens accessories.&amp;nbsp; The guidance for contact lenses entitled &amp;quot;Premarket Notification [510(k)] Guidance Document for Class II Daily Wear Contact Lenses&amp;quot; and can be found at: &lt;a href="http://www.fda.gov/medicaldevices/deviceregulationandguidance/guidancedocuments/ucm080928.htm"&gt;http://www.fda.gov/medicaldevices/deviceregulationandguidance/guidancedocuments/ucm080928.htm&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp; The guidance for contact lens accessories entitled &amp;quot;Premarket Notification [510(k)] Guidance Document for Contact Lens Care Products&amp;quot; and can be found at: &lt;a href="http://www.fda.gov/downloads/medicaldevices/deviceregulationandguidance/guidancedocuments/ucm080218.pdf"&gt;http://www.fda.gov/downloads/medicaldevices/deviceregulationandguidance/guidancedocuments/ucm080218.pdf&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp; The discussion will include topics such as microbiological and chemical pre-clinical testing, revision of pre-clinical test requirements to address patient non-compliance, modification of rigid gas permeable lens care regimens, and labeling for these devices.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting.&amp;nbsp; If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA's Web site after the meeting.&amp;nbsp; Background material is available at &lt;a href="http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/CommitteesMeetingMaterials/MedicalDevices/MedicalDevicesAdvisoryCommittee/default.htm"&gt;http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/CommitteesMeetingMaterials/MedicalDevices/&lt;br /&gt;MedicalDevicesAdvisoryCommittee/default.htm&lt;/a&gt;. Scroll down to the appropriate advisory committee meeting link.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Procedure&lt;/strong&gt;:&amp;nbsp; Interested persons may present data, information, or views, orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committee.&amp;nbsp; Written submissions may be made to the contact person on or before May 6, 2014.&amp;nbsp; Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled between approximately 1 p.m. and 2 p.m. on May 13, 2014.&amp;nbsp; Those individuals interested in making formal oral presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before April 25, 2014.&amp;nbsp; Time allotted for each presentation may be limited.&amp;nbsp; If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session.&amp;nbsp; The contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by April 29, 2014.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA is opening a docket for public comment on this document.&amp;nbsp; The docket number is FDA-2014-N-0314.&amp;nbsp; The docket will close on May 23, 2014.&amp;nbsp; Interested persons are encouraged to use the docket to submit electronic or written comments regarding this meeting.&amp;nbsp; Comments received on or before May 6, 2014, will be provided to the committee.&amp;nbsp; Comments received after that date will be taken into consideration by the Agency.&amp;nbsp; Submit electronic comments on this meeting to &lt;a href="http://www.regulations.gov"&gt;http://www.regulations.gov&lt;/a&gt; or written comments to the Division of Dockets Management (HFA-305), Food and Drug Administration, 5630 Fishers Lane, rm. 1061, Rockville, MD 20852.&amp;nbsp; It is only necessary to send one set of comments.&amp;nbsp; Identify comments with the docket number found in brackets in the heading of this document.&amp;nbsp; Received comments may be seen in the Divisions of Dockets Management between 9 a.m. and 4 p.m., Monday through Friday, and will be posted to the docket at &lt;a href="http://www.regulations.gov"&gt;http://www.regulations.gov&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Persons attending FDA's advisory committee meetings are advised that the Agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical disabilities or special needs. If you require special accommodations due to a disability, please contact James Clark at &lt;a href="mailto:James.Clark@fda.hhs.gov"&gt;James.Clark@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp; or 301-796-5293 at least 7 days in advance of the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its advisory committee meetings.&amp;nbsp; Please visit our Web site at &lt;a href="http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/AboutAdvisoryCommittees/ucm111462.htm"&gt;http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/AboutAdvisoryCommittees/ucm111462.htm&lt;/a&gt; for procedures on public conduct during advisory committee meetings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5 U.S.C. app. 2).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dated: April 7, 2014.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jill Hartzler Warner,&lt;br /&gt;Acting Associate Commissioner for Special Medical Programs.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
