<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;div class="table-responsive"&gt;&lt;table class="table table-striped table-bordered table-condensed" summary="This table shows the date, time, and location of the meeting"&gt;&lt;thead&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th scope="col"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Center&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th scope="col"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Date&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th scope="col"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th scope="col"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;CDRH&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;June 17, 2014&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;8:00 a.m. - 6:00 p.m.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;FDA White Oak Campus&lt;br /&gt;10903 New Hampshire Ave.&lt;br /&gt;Building 31 Conference Center&lt;br /&gt;the Great Room (rm. 1503)&lt;br /&gt;Silver Spring, MD 20993&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH AND HUMAN SERVICES&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Food and Drug Administration&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[Docket No. FDA-2014-N-0001]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gastroenterology and Urology Devices Panel of the Medical Devices Advisory Committee; Notice of Meeting&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;AGENCY: Food and Drug Administration, HHS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ACTION: Notice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This notice announces a forthcoming meeting of a public advisory committee of the Food and Drug Administration (FDA). The meeting will be open to the public.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Name of Committee&lt;/strong&gt;: Gastroenterology and Urology Devices Panel of the Medical Devices Advisory Committee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Function of the Committee&lt;/strong&gt;: To provide advice and recommendations to the Agency on FDA's regulatory issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Date and Time&lt;/strong&gt;:&amp;nbsp; The meeting will be held on June 17, 2014, from 8 a.m. to 6 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location&lt;/strong&gt;: FDA White Oak Campus, 10903 New Hampshire Ave., Building 31 Conference Center, the Great Room (rm. 1503), Silver Spring, MD 20993-0002. Information regarding special accommodations due to a disability, visitor parking, and transportation may be accessed at: &lt;a href="http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/default.htm"&gt;http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/default.htm&lt;/a&gt;; under the heading &amp;quot;Resources for You,&amp;quot; click on &amp;quot;Public Meetings at the FDA White Oak Campus.&amp;quot; Please note that visitors to the White Oak Campus must enter through Building. 1.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact Person&lt;/strong&gt;: Abbas Bandukwala, Center for Devices and Radiological Health, Food and Drug Administration, 10903 New Hampshire Ave., Bldg. 66, rm. 1535, Silver Spring MD 20993-0002, 301-796-6386, email: &lt;a href="mailto:Abbas.Bandukwala@fda.hhs.gov"&gt;Abbas.Bandukwala@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/a&gt;, or FDA Advisory Committee Information Line, 1-800-741-8138 (301-443-0572 in the Washington, DC area). A notice in the Federal Register about last minute modifications that impact a previously announced advisory committee meeting cannot always be published quickly enough to provide timely notice. Therefore, you should always check the Agency's Web site at &lt;a href="http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/default.htm"&gt;http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/default.htm&lt;/a&gt; and scroll down to the appropriate advisory committee meeting link, or call the advisory committee information line to learn about possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agenda&lt;/strong&gt;: On June 17, 2014, the committee will discuss, make recommendations, and vote on information regarding the premarket application (PMA) for the Maestro&amp;reg; Rechargeable System sponsored by Enteromedics, Inc. The Maestro&amp;reg; Rechargeable System provides VBLOC Therapy. The implantable device is a neuromodulator, which delivers high frequency (5000 Hertz), controllable electrical pulses to the intra-abdominal vagus nerve trunks. The effect of VBLOC therapy is reported to suppress neural signals carried by the vagus nerve trunks, resulting in decreased hunger pangs, decreased digestive enzyme secretion and calorie absorption, and increased satiety. The device consists of implantable electronic device components that deliver VBLOC therapy, and external components that regulate device performance.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The proposed indication for use for the Maestro&amp;reg; Rechargeable System, as stated in the PMA, is as follows:&lt;br /&gt;The Maestro&amp;reg; Rechargeable System is indicated for use in weight reduction in adult patients with obesity that have a Body Mass Index (BMI) of at least 40 kilograms per square meter (kg/m2), or a BMI of at least 35 kg/m2 with one or more obesity related comorbid conditions, and have failed a more conservative weight reduction alternative.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting. If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA's Web site after the meeting. Background material is available at &lt;a href="http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/CommitteesMeetingMaterials/MedicalDevices/MedicalDevicesAdvisoryCommittee/default.htm"&gt;http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/CommitteesMeetingMaterials/MedicalDevices/&lt;br /&gt;MedicalDevicesAdvisoryCommittee/default.htm&lt;/a&gt;. Scroll down to the appropriate advisory committee meeting link.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Procedure&lt;/strong&gt;: Interested persons may present data, information, or views, orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committee. Written submissions may be made to the contact person on or before May 13, 2014. Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled between approximately 1 p.m. and 2 p.m. Those individuals interested in making formal oral presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before May 5, 2014. Time allotted for each presentation may be limited. If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session.&amp;nbsp; The contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by May 6, 2014.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Persons attending FDA's advisory committee meetings are advised that the Agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical disabilities or special needs. If you require special accommodations due to a disability, please contact James Clark at &lt;a href="mailto:James.Clark@fda.hhs.gov"&gt;James.Clark@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/a&gt;, or 301-796-5293 at least 7 days in advance of the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its advisory committee meetings.&amp;nbsp; Please visit our Web site at &lt;a href="http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/AboutAdvisoryCommittees/ucm111462.htm"&gt;http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/AboutAdvisoryCommittees/ucm111462.htm&lt;/a&gt; for procedures on public conduct during advisory committee meetings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5 U.S.C. app. 2).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dated:&amp;nbsp; April 15, 2014.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Leslie Kux,&lt;br /&gt;Assistant Commissioner for Policy.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
