<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;table border="1" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0" width="98%"&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th valign="top"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Center&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th valign="top"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Date&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th valign="top"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th valign="top"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td valign="top"&gt;&lt;p&gt;CBER&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top"&gt;&lt;p&gt;January 15, 2013&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top"&gt;&lt;p&gt;2 p.m. to 5:30 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top"&gt;&lt;p&gt;National Institutes of Health, 9000 Wisconsin Avenue, Bethesda, MD&amp;nbsp; 20892; Building 29B, Conference Room, &amp;nbsp;C&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agenda&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;On January 15, 2013 from 2 p.m. to approximately 4:30 p.m., the Committee will meet, by teleconference, in open session, to hear updates on the research programs in the Laboratory of Immunology, Division of Therapeutic Proteins, Office of Biotechnology Products, Center for Drug Evaluation and Research, FDA.&amp;nbsp; From approximately 4:30 p.m. to 5:30 p.m., the meeting will be closed to permit discussion where disclosure would constitute a clearly unwarranted invasion of personal privacy (5 U.S.C. 552b(c)(6)).&amp;nbsp; The committee will discuss reports of the intramural research programs and make recommendations regarding personnel staffing decisions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meeting Materials&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Materials for this meeting will be available on the &lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM331864')--]"&gt;2013 Meeting Materials, Cellular, Tissue and Gene Therapies Advisory Committee&lt;/a&gt; page.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Public Participation Information&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interested persons may present data, information, or views, orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Written submissions may be made to the contact person on or before January 8, 2013.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled between approximately 3:30&amp;nbsp; p.m. and 4:30 p.m. &amp;nbsp;Those individuals interested in making formal oral presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before December 31, 2012.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Time allotted for each presentation may be limited. If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session. The contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by January 2, 2013.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gail Dapolito, 301-827-1289, Fax, 301-827-0294, e-mail: &lt;a href="mailto:gail.dapolito@fda.hhs.gov"&gt;gail.dapolito@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;FDA Advisory Committee Information Line&lt;br /&gt;1-800-741-8138 (301-443-0572 in the Washington, DC, area) &lt;br /&gt;Please call the Information Line for up-to-date information on this meeting.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting. If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA&amp;rsquo;s Web site after the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A notice in the Federal Register about last minute modifications that impact a previously announced advisory committee meeting cannot always be published quickly enough to provide timely notice. Therefore, you should always check the agency&amp;rsquo;s Web site and call the appropriate advisory committee hot line/phone line to learn about possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The public is welcome to attend the meeting at the specified location where a speakerphone will be provided.&amp;nbsp; Public participation in the meeting is limited to the use of the spearkerphone in the conference room.&amp;nbsp; Important information about transportation and directions to the NIH campus, parking and security procedures is available on the Internet at &lt;a href="http://www.nih.gov/about/visitor/index.htm"&gt;http://www.nih.gov/about/visitor/index.htm&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp; (FDA has verified the Web site address, but FDA is not responsible for any subsequent changes to the Web site after this document publishes in the Federal Register). Visitors must show two forms of identification, one of which must be a government-issued photo identification such as a Federal employee badge, driver&amp;rsquo;s license, passport, green card, etc. Detailed information about security procedures is located at &lt;a href="http://www.nih.gov/about/visitorsecurity.htm"&gt;http://www.nih.gov/about/visitorsecurity.htm&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp; Due to the limited available parking, visitors are encouraged to use public transportation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Persons attending FDA&amp;rsquo;s advisory committee meetings are advised that the agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets. FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical disabilities or special needs. If you require special accommodations due to a disability, please contact Bryan Emery at least 7 days in advance of the meeting. FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its advisory committee meetings. Please visit our Web site at &lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM111462')--]"&gt;http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/AboutAdvisoryCommittees/ucm111462.htm&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;for procedures on public conduct during advisory committee meetings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5 U.S.C. app. 2).&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
