<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;h5&gt;Date:&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;p&gt;April 30, 2013&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h5&gt;Time:&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;p&gt;On April 30, 2013, from 8:30 a.m. to 3:00 p.m., the meeting is open to the public.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;From 3:30 p.m. to 5:30 p.m., the meeting will be closed to the public, to permit discussion and review of trade secret and/or confidential commercial information (5 U.S.C. 552b(c)(4)).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h5&gt;Location:&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conference Room 020B&lt;br /&gt;Center for Tobacco Products&lt;br /&gt;9200 Corporate Boulevard&lt;br /&gt;Rockville, MD&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 20850&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seating for this meeting may be limited, so the public is encouraged to watch the free webcast instead of traveling to the meeting.&amp;nbsp; The link for the webcast will be available at approximately 8:15 a.m. on April 30, 2013, on the TPSAC website&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h5&gt;Agenda:&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;p&gt;Modified risk tobacco products (MRTPs) are tobacco products that are sold or distributed for use to reduce harm or the risk of tobacco-related disease associated with commercially marketed tobacco products.&amp;nbsp; Before an MRTP can be introduced or delivered for introduction into interstate commerce, an order from FDA under section 911(g) (21 U.S.C. 387k(g)) of the Federal Food, Drug, and Cosmetic Act (FD&amp;amp;C Act) must be in effect with respect to the tobacco product.&amp;nbsp; 21 U.S.C. 387k(a).&amp;nbsp; Any person may submit an application seeking an order under section 911(g) of the FD&amp;amp;C Act.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Section 911(f) of the FD&amp;amp;C Act (21 U.S.C. 387k(f)) requires FDA to refer modified risk tobacco product applications to the Tobacco Products Scientific Advisory Committee (TPSAC) for its recommendations. TPSAC is required to report its recommendations on an application to FDA no later than 60 days after the date the application is referred to them.&amp;nbsp; 21 U.S.C. 387k(f)(2).&amp;nbsp; On April 30, 2013, FDA will present information to the committee on the process it will use to refer individual modified risk tobacco product applications to TPSAC.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h5&gt;Meeting Materials:&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;p&gt;Links to meeting materials will be added as they become available.&amp;nbsp; FDA intends to make complete background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting. If FDA is unable to post the background material on its website prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and will be posted on FDA&amp;rsquo;s website after the meeting.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h5&gt;Public Participation Information:&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interested persons may present data, information, or views, orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Written submissions may be made to the contact person on or before April 23, 2013.&amp;nbsp; Please send 20 paper copies, and one electronic copy, of your submission to:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Caryn Cohen, M.S.&lt;br /&gt;Office of Science&lt;br /&gt;Center for Tobacco Products&lt;br /&gt;Food and Drug Administration&lt;br /&gt;9200 Corporate Boulevard &lt;br /&gt;Rockville, MD 20850&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Copies must be received by 4 p.m. April 23, 2013.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled between approximately &lt;br /&gt;11:00 a.m. and noon on April 30, 2013.&amp;nbsp; Those individuals interested in making formal oral presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before April 15, 2013.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Time allotted for each presentation may be limited.&amp;nbsp; If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session.&amp;nbsp; The contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by April 16, 2013.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h5&gt;Contact Information&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;p&gt;Caryn Cohen, M.S.&lt;br /&gt;Center for Tobacco Products&lt;br /&gt;Food and Drug Administration&lt;br /&gt;9200 Corporate Boulevard &lt;br /&gt;Rockville, MD 20850&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Phone:&amp;nbsp; 1-877-287-1373 (choose Option 5)&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;FAX:&amp;nbsp; 240-276-3655&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;Email: &lt;a href="mailto:TPSAC@fda.hhs.gov"&gt;TPSAC@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA Advisory Committee Information Line&lt;br /&gt;1-800-741-8138&lt;br /&gt;(301-443-0572 in the Washington DC area)&lt;br /&gt;Please call the Information Line for up-to-date information on this meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A notice in the Federal Register about last minute modifications that impact a previously announced advisory committee meeting cannot always be published quickly enough to provide timely notice.&amp;nbsp; Therefore, you should always check the agency&amp;rsquo;s Website and call the appropriate advisory committee hot line/phone line to learn about possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting.&amp;nbsp; If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA&amp;rsquo;s Web site after the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Persons attending FDA&amp;rsquo;s advisory committee meetings are advised that the agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets.&amp;nbsp; FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical disabilities or special needs.&amp;nbsp; If you require special accommodations due to a disability, please contact Caryn Cohen at least 7 days in advance of the meeting.&amp;nbsp; FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its advisory committee meetings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please visit our Web site at &lt;a href="http://www.fda.gov/oc/advisory/default.htm2"&gt;http://www.fda.gov/oc/advisory/default.htm2&lt;/a&gt; for procedures on public conduct during advisory committee meetings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5 U.S.C. app.2).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
