<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;table cellspacing="0" cellpadding="2" border="0" id="schedule" style="WIDTH: 643px" summary="This table shows the date, time, and location of the meeting"&gt;     &lt;tbody&gt;         &lt;tr&gt;             &lt;th bgcolor="#cccccc" align="left" valign="top" id="a1" style="WIDTH: 71px"&gt;Center&lt;/th&gt;             &lt;th bgcolor="#cccccc" align="left" valign="top" id="a2" style="WIDTH: 158px"&gt;Date&lt;/th&gt;             &lt;th bgcolor="#cccccc" align="left" valign="top" id="a3" style="WIDTH: 172px"&gt;Time&lt;/th&gt;             &lt;th bgcolor="#cccccc" align="left" valign="top" id="a4" style="WIDTH: 238px"&gt;Location&lt;/th&gt;         &lt;/tr&gt;         &lt;tr&gt;             &lt;td valign="top" height="61" style="WIDTH: 71px" headers="a1"&gt;CDER&lt;/td&gt;             &lt;td valign="top" style="WIDTH: 158px" headers="a2"&gt;June 20, 2012&lt;br /&gt;             &amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;             &lt;td valign="top" style="WIDTH: 172px" headers="a3"&gt;8:00 a.m. to 5:00 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;             &amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;             &lt;td valign="top" style="WIDTH: 238px" headers="a4"&gt;FDA White Oak Campus&lt;br /&gt;             Building  31&lt;br /&gt;             The Great Room (Rm. 1503)&lt;br /&gt;             White Oak Conference Center&lt;br /&gt;             10903 New  Hampshire Avenue&lt;br /&gt;             Silver Spring, Maryland&lt;/td&gt;         &lt;/tr&gt;     &lt;/tbody&gt; &lt;/table&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Agenda&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;During the morning session, the committee will discuss New Drug Application (NDA) 203213, with the established name semuloparin sodium injection, application submitted by sanofi-aventis U.S. LLC.  The proposed indication (use) for this product is for the prophylaxis of venous thromboembolism (VTE) in patients receiving chemotherapy for locally advanced or metastatic pancreatic or lung cancer or for locally advanced or metastatic solid tumors with a VTE risk score &amp;ge; 3.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;During the afternoon session, the committee will discuss New Drug Application (NDA) 202714, with the proposed trade name Kyprolis (carfilzomib) for injection, application submitted by Onyx Pharmaceuticals, Inc. The proposed indication (use) for this product is for the treatment of patients with relapsed and refractory (recurring and/or not responsive to other treatments) multiple myeloma who have received at least 2 prior lines of therapy that included a proteasome inhibitor and an immunomodulatory agent.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Meeting Materials&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later than  2 business days before the meeting. If FDA is unable to post the background  material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be  made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and  the background material will be posted on FDA&amp;rsquo;s Web site after the meeting.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Background Material:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM285400')--]" target=""&gt;2012 Meeting Materials, Oncologic Drugs Advisory Committee&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;Public Participation Information&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div&gt;Interested persons may present data, information, or views, orally or in  writing, on issues pending before the committee.&lt;/div&gt; &lt;ul&gt;     &lt;li&gt;Written submissions may be made to the contact person on or before June 6,  2012.&lt;/li&gt;     &lt;li&gt;Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled between approximately 10:30 a.m. to 11 a.m. and 3:30 p.m. to 4 p.m. on June 20, 2012. Those desiring to make formal oral presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before May 29, 2012.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;Time allotted for each presentation may be limited.  If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session.  The contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by May 30, 2012.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Webcast Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;CDER plans to provide a free of charge, live webcast of the June 20, 2012, meeting of the Oncologic Drugs Advisory Committee.  While CDER is working to make webcasts available to the public for all advisory committee meetings held at the White Oak campus, there are instances where the webcast transmission is not successful; staff will work to re-establish the transmission as soon as possible.  Further information regarding the webcast, including the web address for the webcast, will be made available at least 2 days in advance of the meeting at the following website: &lt;a href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM285400')--]" target=""&gt;2012 Meeting Materials, Oncologic Drugs Advisory Committee&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="footnote_number"&gt; CDER plans to post archived webcasts after the meeting, however, in cases where transmission was not successful, archived webcasts will not be available.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt;     &lt;li&gt;Caleb Briggs, Pharm.D.&lt;br /&gt;     Center for Drug  Evaluation and Research&lt;br /&gt;     Food and Drug Administration&lt;br /&gt;     10903 New Hampshire  Avenue&lt;br /&gt;     WO31-2417&lt;br /&gt;     Silver Spring, MD&amp;nbsp;20993-0002&lt;br /&gt;     Phone:  301-796-9001&lt;br /&gt;     Fax: 301-847-8533&lt;br /&gt;     E-mail: &lt;a href="mailto:ODAC@fda.hhs.gov"&gt;ODAC@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;ul&gt;     &lt;li&gt;FDA Advisory Committee Information Line&lt;br /&gt;     1-800-741-8138&lt;br /&gt;     (301-443-0572  in the Washington DC area)&lt;br /&gt;     Please call the Information Line for up-to-date  information on this meeting.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;A notice in the Federal Register about last minute modifications that impact a previously announced advisory committee meeting cannot always be published quickly enough to provide timely notice.  Therefore, you should always check the agency&amp;rsquo;s Web site and call the FDA Advisory Committee Information Line to learn about possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Persons attending FDA&amp;rsquo;s advisory committee meetings are advised that the agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets.  FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical disabilities or special needs. If you require special accommodations due to a disability, please contact Caleb Briggs at (301) 796-9001 at least 7 days in advance of the meeting.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Information regarding special accommodations due to  a disability, visitor parking and transportation may be accessed at: &lt;a href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM241740')--]" target=""&gt;Public Meetings at the White Oak Campus&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its  advisory committee meetings.&amp;nbsp;Please visit our Web site at &lt;a href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM111462')--]" target=""&gt;Public Conduct During FDA Advisory Committee Meetings&lt;/a&gt; for procedures on public conduct  during advisory committee meetings.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5  U.S.C. app.2).&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
