<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;table id="schedule" border="0" cellspacing="0" summary="This table shows the date, time, and location of the meeting" cellpadding="2" style="width: 100%"&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th id="a1" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" width="10%" align="left"&gt;Center&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a2" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" width="25%" align="left"&gt;Date&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a3" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" width="25%" align="left"&gt;Time&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a4" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" width="40%" align="left"&gt;Location&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td valign="top" width="10%" headers="a1"&gt;OC&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" width="25%" headers="a2"&gt;August 16, 2013&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" width="25%" headers="a3"&gt;9:00 a.m. - 5:00 p.m.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" width="40%" headers="a4" align="left"&gt;FDA White Oak Campus&lt;br /&gt;10903 New Hampshire Ave.&lt;br /&gt;Building 31 Conference Center (rm. 1503) &lt;br /&gt;Silver Spring, MD 20993-0002&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Agenda&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;On August 16, 2013, the Committee will discuss how FDA can communicate more effectively with health care professionals and other stakeholders about the public health risks posed by counterfeit and unapproved drugs, in addition to safe purchasing practices, and how FDA can evaluate that communication and its impact.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meeting Materials&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting.&amp;nbsp; If FDA is unable to post the background material on its website prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA's Web site after the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Background material&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM335072')--]"&gt;2013 Meeting Materials, Risk Communication Advisory Committee&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Procedure&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Information regarding special accommodations due to a disability, visitor parking, and transportation may be accessed at &amp;quot;&lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM241740')--]"&gt;Public Meetings on the FDA White Oak Campus&lt;/a&gt;&amp;quot; on the FDA website. Please note that visitors to the White Oak Campus must enter through Building 1.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A notice in the &lt;em&gt;Federal Register&lt;/em&gt; about last minute modifications that impact a previously announced advisory committee meeting cannot always be published quickly enough to provide timely notice.&amp;nbsp; Therefore, you should always check the Agency's website at &lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('nodelink','1840')--]"&gt;www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/default.htm&lt;/a&gt; and scroll down to the appropriate advisory committee meeting link, or call the advisory committee information line to learn about possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Public Participation Information&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interested persons may present data, information, or views, orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committee.&amp;nbsp; Written submissions may be made to the contact person on or before August 8, 2013.&amp;nbsp; Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled between approximately 1 p.m. and 2 p.m.&amp;nbsp; Those individuals interested in making formal oral presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before July 31, 2013.&amp;nbsp; Time allotted for each presentation may be limited.&amp;nbsp; If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session.&amp;nbsp; The contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by August 1, 2013.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Persons attending FDA's advisory committee meetings are advised that the Agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical disabilities or special needs. If you require special accommodations due to a disability, please contact Luis G. Bravo at least 7 days in advance of the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its advisory committee meetings. &amp;nbsp;Please visit our Web site for &lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','ucm111462.htm')--]"&gt;procedures on public conduct during advisory committee meetings&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Luis G. Bravo&lt;br /&gt;Food and Drug Administration&lt;br /&gt;10903 New Hampshire Ave.&lt;br /&gt;Bldg. 32, rm. 3274&lt;br /&gt;Silver Spring, Maryland 20993-0002&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Phone: 240-402-5274&lt;br /&gt;Fax: 301-847-8609&lt;br /&gt;E-mail: &lt;a href="mailto:RCAC@fda.hhs.gov"&gt;RCAC@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;FDA Advisory Committee Information Line&lt;br /&gt;1-800-741-8138&lt;br /&gt;(301-443-0572 in the Washington DC area)&lt;br /&gt;Please call the Information Line for up-to-date information on this meeting.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5 U.S.C. app.2).&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
