<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;table id="schedule" border="0" cellspacing="0" summary="This table shows the date, time, and location of the meeting" cellpadding="2" style="margin-top: 10px; width: 643px; height: 93px"&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th id="a1" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" align="left" style="width: 71px"&gt;Center&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a2" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" align="left" style="width: 158px"&gt;Date&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a3" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" align="left" style="width: 172px"&gt;Time&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a4" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" align="left" style="width: 238px"&gt;Location&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td valign="top" headers="a1" style="width: 71px; height: 74px"&gt;CFSAN&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" headers="a2" style="width: 158px; height: 74px"&gt;September 23-24, 2013&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" headers="a3" style="width: 172px; height: 74px"&gt;8:30 a.m. &amp;ndash; 5 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" headers="a4" style="width: 238px; height: 75px"&gt;FDA White Oak Conference Center&lt;br /&gt;Building 31, Room 1503&lt;br /&gt;10903 New Hampshire Avenue&lt;br /&gt;Silver Spring, MM 20993&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agenda&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Food Advisory Committee will meet to discuss detection signals for noteworthy chemical hazards in foods, dietary supplements, and cosmetics and consider possible sources of information, data on chemical hazards, and how CFSAN might recognize and best take advantage of those data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meeting Materials&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting. If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA's Web site after the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Background Material&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The background materials will be posted at least five days before the meeting start date.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM364255')--]"&gt;2013 Food Advisory Committee Meeting Materials&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Public Participation Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interested persons may present data, information, or views, orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="noindent"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Written submissions may be made to the contact person on or before September 16, 2013.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled between approximately 11:00 a.m. to 12:00 p.m. on September 24, 2013. Those individuals interested in making formal oral presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before August 26, 2013.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Time allotted for each presentation may be limited. If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session. The contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by September 9, 2013.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Webcast Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p sizcache="1" sizset="38"&gt;CFSAN plans to provide a free of charge, live webcast of the September 23-24, 2013, meeting of the Food and Drug Advisory Committee. While CFSAN is working to make webcasts available to the public for all advisory committee meetings held at the White Oak campus, there are instances where the webcast transmission is not successful; staff will work to re-establish the transmission as soon as possible. Interested persons can also log on to &lt;a target="_blank" href="[!--$ssExternalLink('UCM367549')--]"&gt;https://collaboration.fda.gov/foodsac913/&lt;/a&gt; to hear and view the proceedings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul sizcache="1" sizset="39"&gt;&lt;li sizcache="1" sizset="39"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Karen L. Strambler, M.B.A.&lt;br /&gt;Center for Food Safety and Applied Nutrition&lt;br /&gt;Food and Drug Administration&lt;br /&gt;5100 Paint Branch Parkway&lt;br /&gt;College Park, MD 20740&lt;br /&gt;Telephone: (240) 402-2589&lt;br /&gt;Fax: (301) 436-2637&lt;br /&gt;Email: &lt;a href="mailto:FoodAdvisoryCommittee@fda.hhs.gov"&gt;FoodAdvisoryCommittee@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;FDA Advisory Committee Information Line&lt;br /&gt;1-800-741-8138 (301-443-0572 in the Washington DC area)&lt;br /&gt;Please call the Information Line for up-to-date information on this meeting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;A notice in the Federal Register about last minute modifications that impact a previously announced advisory committee meeting cannot always be published quickly enough to provide timely notice. Therefore, you should always check the agency's Web site and call the FDA Advisory Committee Information Line to learn about possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Persons attending FDA's advisory committee meetings are advised that the agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets. FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical disabilities or special needs. If you require special accommodations due to a disability, please contact Karen Strambler at least 7 days in advance of the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Information regarding ground transportation, airport information, lodging, driving directions and visitor parking, and security can be accessed at: &lt;a title="http://www.fda.gov/AboutFDA/WorkingatFDA/BuildingsandFacilities/WhiteOakCampusInformation/ucm241740.htm" href="http://www.fda.gov/AboutFDA/WorkingatFDA/BuildingsandFacilities/WhiteOakCampusInformation/ucm241740.htm"&gt;&lt;span title="http://www.fda.gov/AboutFDA/WorkingatFDA/BuildingsandFacilities/WhiteOakCampusInformation/ucm241740.htm"&gt;Public Meetings at the FDA White Oak Campus&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p sizcache="1" sizset="41"&gt;FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its advisory committee meetings. Please visit our Web site at &lt;a target="" href="http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/AboutAdvisoryCommittees/ucm111462.htm"&gt;Public Conduct During FDA Advisory Committee Meetings&lt;/a&gt; for procedures on public conduct during advisory committee meetings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5 U.S.C. app.2).&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
