<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;table border="1" cellspacing="0" summary="Meeting data layout" cellpadding="0" width="98%"&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" width="7%" scope="col" align="left" th=""&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Center&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" width="16%" scope="col" align="left" th=""&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Date&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" width="51%" scope="col" align="left" th=""&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" width="26%" scope="col" align="left" th=""&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td valign="top" align="left"&gt;CBER&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" align="left"&gt;November 1, 2013&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" align="left"&gt;November 1 from 8:00 a.m. to approximately 4:30 p.m.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" align="left"&gt;5630 Fishers Lane, &lt;br /&gt;Room 1066.&lt;br /&gt;Rockville, MD 20857&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agenda&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On November 1, 2013, the Committee will meet in open session to discuss MP Biomedicals' biologic license application for the MP Diagnostics HTLV Blot 2.4, a Western Blot intended for use as a confirmatory test for blood donors.&amp;nbsp; In the afternoon, the committee will hear update presentations on the following topics:&amp;nbsp; (1) The April 2013 FDA public workshop on multiplex detection of transfusion transmissible agents and blood cell antigens in blood donations and (2) FDA safety communications on new boxed warnings for immune globulin products and hydroxyethyl starch solutions.&amp;nbsp; Following the update presentations, the committee will meet in open session to hear presentations on the research programs of the Laboratory of Biochemistry and Vascular Biology, Division of Hematology, Office of Blood Research and Review, Center for Biologics Evaluation and Research, FDA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Closed Committee Deliberations&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;On November 1, 2013, from approximately 4 p.m. to 4:30 p.m., the meeting will be closed to permit discussion where disclosure would constitute a clearly unwarranted invasion of personal privacy (5 U.S.C. 552b(c)(6)).&amp;nbsp; The committee will discuss the site visit report of the intramural research programs and make recommendations regarding personnel staffing decisions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meeting Materials&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Materials for this meeting will be available at: &lt;a href="http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/CommitteesMeetingMaterials/BloodVaccinesandOtherBiologics/default.htm"&gt;the Blood, Vaccines and Other Biologics Advisory Committee main page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Public Participation Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Interested persons may present data, information, or views, orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul type="disc"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Written submissions may be made to the contact person on or before October 24, 2013&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Oral presentations on November 1, 2013 from the public will be scheduled between approximately 11:00 a.m. and 11:30 a.m. Afternoon presentations will be scheduled between approximately 3:30 p.m. and 4 p.m.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Those individuals interested in making formal oral presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before October 16, 2013.&amp;nbsp; Time allotted for each presentation may be limited.&amp;nbsp; If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session.&amp;nbsp; The contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by October 17, 2013.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;For those unable to attend in person, the meeting will also be Web cast. The Web cast will be available at the following link. &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Blood Products Advisory Committee November 1, 2013: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://fda.yorkcast.com/webcast/Viewer/?peid=18390c01dfff405681afa644b1837e5a1d"&gt;http://fda.yorkcast.com/webcast/Viewer/?peid=18390c01dfff405681afa644b1837e5a1d&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bryan Emery or Pearline Muckelvene&lt;br /&gt;1401 Rockville Pike, HFM-71, Rockville, MD 20852&lt;br /&gt;301-827-1281 or 301-827-1277&lt;br /&gt;FAX: 301-827-0294&lt;br /&gt;e-mail: &lt;a href="mailto:Bryan.Emery@fda.hhs.gov"&gt;Bryan.Emery@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/a&gt; or email: Pearline.Muckelvene@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;FDA Advisory Committee Information Line&lt;br /&gt;1-800-741-8138 (301-443-0572 in the Washington, DC, area). Please call the Information Line for up-to-date information on this meeting.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting. If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA&amp;rsquo;s Web site after the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A notice in the Federal Register about last minute modifications that impact a previously announced advisory committee meeting cannot always be published quickly enough to provide timely notice. Therefore, you should always check the agency&amp;rsquo;s Web site and call the appropriate advisory committee hot line/phone line to learn about possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Persons attending FDA&amp;rsquo;s advisory committee meetings are advised that the agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets. Seating for this meeting may be limited, so the public is encouraged to watch the free webcast if you are unable to attend.&amp;nbsp; The link for the webcast will be available at 8 a.m. November 1, 2013 at the links above.&amp;nbsp; FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical disabilities or special needs. If you require special accommodations due to a disability, please contact Bryan Emery or Pearline Muckelvene at least 7 days in advance of the meeting. FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its advisory committee meetings. Please visit our Web site for&amp;nbsp;&lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM111462')--]"&gt;procedures on public conduct during advisory committee meetings&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5 U.S.C. app. 2). &lt;a target="_blank" href="[!--$ssExternalLink('UCM368420')--]"&gt;Official FR Notice&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
