<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;p&gt;&lt;table id="schedule" border="0" cellspacing="0" summary="This table shows the date, time, and location of the meeting" cellpadding="2" style="width: 643px; height: 93px"&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th id="a1" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" align="left" style="width: 71px"&gt;Center&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a2" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" align="left" style="width: 158px"&gt;Date&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a3" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" align="left" style="width: 172px"&gt;Time&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a4" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" align="left" style="width: 238px"&gt;Location&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td valign="top" headers="a1" style="width: 71px; height: 74px"&gt;CDER&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" headers="a2" style="width: 158px; height: 74px"&gt;November 5,&amp;nbsp;2013&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" headers="a3" style="width: 172px; height: 74px"&gt;8:00 a.m. to 5:00 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" headers="a4" style="width: 238px; height: 75px"&gt;FDA White Oak Campus&lt;br /&gt;Building 31&lt;br /&gt;The Great Room (Rm. 1503)&lt;br /&gt;White Oak Conference Center&lt;br /&gt;10903 New Hampshire Avenue&lt;br /&gt;Silver Spring, Maryland&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agenda&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;During the morning session, there will be a presentation and general discussion of the potential applicability of pharmacological and cellular manipulation of the immune system, as a potential therapeutic intervention in various pediatric cancers. The recent, dramatic results of inhibition of the PD-1/PD-L1 axis and checkpoint inhibitors on normal T cells in melanoma and other adult cancers strongly suggest a potential role for such agents in the management of childhood cancer. Information will be presented regarding pediatric development plans for two products that are in late stage development for various adult oncology indications. The subcommittee will consider and discuss issues relating to the development of each product for potential pediatric use and provide guidance to facilitate the formulation of Written Requests for pediatric studies, if appropriate. The two products under consideration are: (1) nivolumab, application submitted by Bristol Myers Squibb Co.; and (2) MK-3475, application submitted by Merck Sharp and Dohme.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;During the afternoon session, information will be presented regarding pediatric development plans for LEE011, application submitted by Novartis Pharmaceuticals Corporation, a product in early-stage development for adult and pediatric oncology indications. The subcommittee will consider and discuss issues relating to the development of this product for possible pediatric use and provide guidance to facilitate the formulation of Written Requests for pediatric studies, if appropriate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meeting Materials&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting. If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA&amp;rsquo;s Web site after the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Background Material&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul sizcache="1" sizset="41"&gt;&lt;li sizcache="1" sizset="41"&gt;&lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM341089')--]"&gt;2013 Meeting Materials, Oncologic Drugs Advisory Committee&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Public Participation Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interested persons may present data, information, or views, orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="noindent"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Written submissions may be made to the contact person on or before October&amp;nbsp;30, 2013.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled between approximately 10:15 a.m. to 10:45 a.m., and 1:20 p.m. to 1:50 p.m. Those desiring to make formal oral presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before October 28, 2013.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Time allotted for each presentation may be limited. If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session. The contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by October 29, 2013.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Webcast Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p sizcache="1" sizset="42"&gt;CDER plans to provide a free of charge, live webcast of the November 5, 2013, meeting of the Pediatric Oncology Subcommittee of the Oncologic Drugs Advisory Committee. While CDER is working to make webcasts available to the public for all advisory committee meetings held at the White Oak campus, there are instances where the webcast transmission is not successful; staff will work to re-establish the transmission as soon as possible. Further information regarding the webcast, including the web address for the webcast, will be made available at least 2 days in advance of the meeting at the following website: &lt;a target="" href="http://wcms.fda.gov/FDAgov/AdvisoryCommittees/CommitteesMeetingMaterials/Drugs/OncologicDrugsAdvisoryCommittee/ucm341089.htm"&gt;2013 Meeting Materials, Oncologic Drugs Advisory Committee&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p sizcache="1" sizset="38"&gt;CDER plans to post archived webcasts after the meeting, however, in cases where transmission was not successful, archived webcasts will not be available.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul sizcache="1" sizset="43"&gt;&lt;li sizcache="1" sizset="43"&gt;Caleb Briggs, PharmD&lt;br /&gt;Center for Drug Evaluation and Research&lt;br /&gt;Food and Drug Administration&lt;br /&gt;10903 New Hampshire Avenue&lt;br /&gt;WO31-2417&lt;br /&gt;Silver Spring, MD 20993-0002&lt;br /&gt;Phone: 301-796-9001&lt;br /&gt;Fax: 301-847-8533&lt;br /&gt;E-mail:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="mailto:ODAC@fda.hhs.gov"&gt;ODAC@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;FDA Advisory Committee Information Line&lt;br /&gt;1-800-741-8138 (301-443-0572 in the Washington DC area)&lt;br /&gt;Please call the Information Line for up-to-date information on this meeting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;A notice in the Federal Register about last minute modifications that impact a previously announced advisory committee meeting cannot always be published quickly enough to provide timely notice. Therefore, you should always check the agency&amp;rsquo;s Website and call the FDA Advisory Committee Information Line to learn about possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Persons attending FDA&amp;rsquo;s advisory committee meetings are advised that the agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets. FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical disabilities or special needs. If you require special accommodations due to a disability, please contact Caleb Briggs at (301) 796-9001 at least 7 days in advance of the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p sizcache="1" sizset="44"&gt;Information regarding ground transportation, airport information, lodging, driving directions and visitor parking, and security can be accessed at: &lt;a target="" href="http://wcms.fda.gov/FDAgov/AboutFDA/WorkingatFDA/BuildingsandFacilities/WhiteOakCampusInformation/ucm241740.htm"&gt;Public Meetings at the FDA White Oak Campus&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="footnote_number"&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p sizcache="1" sizset="45"&gt;FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its advisory committee meetings. Please visit our Web site at &lt;a target="" href="http://wcms.fda.gov/FDAgov/AdvisoryCommittees/AboutAdvisoryCommittees/ucm111462.htm"&gt;Public Conduct During FDA Advisory Committee Meetings&lt;/a&gt; for procedures on public conduct during advisory committee meetings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5 U.S.C. app.2).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
