<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;div class="table-responsive"&gt;&lt;table class="table" border="0" cellspacing="0" summary="This table shows the date, time, and location of the meeting" cellpadding="2" sizset="0" sizcache="12" style="width: 643px; height: 146px"&gt;&lt;tbody sizset="0" sizcache="11"&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th id="a1" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" align="left" style="width: 71px"&gt;Center&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a2" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" align="left" style="width: 158px"&gt;Date&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a3" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" align="left" style="width: 172px"&gt;Time&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a4" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" align="left" style="width: 238px"&gt;Location&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td valign="top" headers="a1" style="width: 71px; height: 127px"&gt;CDER&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" headers="a2" style="width: 158px; height: 127px"&gt;September 11, 2015&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" headers="a3" style="width: 172px; height: 127px"&gt;8:00 a.m. to 9:30 a.m.&lt;br /&gt;(Closed Session)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;9:30 a.m. to 5:00 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;(Open Session)&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" headers="a4" style="width: 238px; height: 128px"&gt;FDA White Oak Campus&lt;br /&gt;10903 New Hampshire Avenue&lt;br /&gt;Building 31 Conference Center&lt;br /&gt;The Great Room (Rm. 1503)&lt;br /&gt;Silver Spring, Maryland&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Agenda&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 1em 0px"&gt;The committees will discuss new drug application (NDA) 208090, oxycodone extended-release capsules for oral use, submitted by Collegium Pharmaceuticals, proposed for the management of pain severe enough to require daily, around-the-clock, long-term opioid treatment and for which alternative options are inadequate. This product has been formulated with the intent to provide abuse-deterrent properties. Pharmacokinetic data demonstrate that, in order to deliver the intended amount of oxycodone, the drug product must be taken with food. The committees will be asked to discuss the potential safety risks and the potential effects on efficacy associated with the extent of the food effect, and potential fluctuations in oxycodone levels that may occur if the product is not taken consistently with the same amount of food. In addition, the committees will be asked to review and discuss whether the data characterizing the abuse-deterrent properties support the likelihood that this drug product will have a meaningful effect on abuse and whether potential benefits to the public from abuse-deterrent properties outweigh potential risks to patients from the effect of food. The committees will be asked to vote on whether this product should be approved for marketing in the United States.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Closed Presentation of Data&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;On September 11, 2015, from 8:00 a.m. to 9:30 a.m., the meeting will be closed to permit discussion and review of trade secret and/or confidential commercial information (5 U.S.C. 552b(c)(4)). During this session, the committees will discuss the drug development program of an investigational product..&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Meeting Materials&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 1em 0px"&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting. If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA&amp;rsquo;s Web site after the meeting. Background material is available at: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM433361')--]"&gt;2015 Meeting Materials, Anesthetic and Analgesic Drug Products Advisory Committee&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Public Participation Information&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 1em 0px"&gt;On September 11, 2015, from 9:30 a.m. to 5 p.m., the meeting is open to the public. Interested persons may present data, information, or views, orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul type="disc"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Written submissions may be made to the contact person on or before August 27, 2015.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled between approximately 1:00 p.m. to 2:00 p.m. on September 11, 2015. Those individuals interested in making formal oral presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before August 19, 2015.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 1em 0px"&gt;Time allotted for each presentation may be limited. If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session. The contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by August 20, 2015..&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Webcast Information&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 1em 0px"&gt;CDER plans to provide a free of charge, live webcast of the open session of the September 11, 2015, joint meeting of the Anesthetic and Analgesic Drug Products Advisory Committee and the Drug Safety and Risk Management Advisory Committee. While CDER is working to make webcasts available to the public for all advisory committee meetings held at the White Oak campus, there are instances where the webcast transmission is not successful; staff will work to re-establish the transmission as soon as possible. Further information regarding the webcast, including the web address for the webcast, will be made available at least 2 days in advance of the meeting at the following website: &lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM433361')--]"&gt;2015 Meeting Materials, Anesthetic and Analgesic Drug Products Advisory Committee&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 1em 0px"&gt;CDER plans to post archived webcasts after the meeting, however, in cases where transmission was not successful, archived webcasts will not be available.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Contact Information&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stephanie L. Begansky, PharmD&lt;br /&gt;Center for Drug Evaluation and Research&lt;br /&gt;Food and Drug Administration&lt;br /&gt;10903 New Hampshire Avenue &lt;br /&gt;WO31-2417&lt;br /&gt;Silver Spring, MD&amp;nbsp; 20993-0002&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Phone: 301-796-9001&lt;br /&gt;Fax: 301-847-8533&lt;br /&gt;Email: &lt;a href="mailto:AADPAC@fda.hhs.gov"&gt;AADPAC@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;FDA Advisory Committee Information Line 1-800-741-8138&lt;br /&gt;(301-443-0572 in the Washington DC area) &lt;br /&gt;Please call the Information Line for up-to-date information on this meeting.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;A notice in the Federal Register about last minute modifications that impact a previously announced advisory committee meeting cannot always be published quickly enough to provide timely notice. Therefore, you should always check the agency&amp;rsquo;s Web site and call the FDA Advisory Committee Information Line to learn about possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Persons attending FDA&amp;rsquo;s advisory committee meetings are advised that the agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets. FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical disabilities or special needs. If you require special accommodations due to a disability, please contact Stephanie Begansky at (301) 796-9001 at least 7 days in advance of the meeting..&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Answers to commonly asked questions including information regarding special accommodations due to a disability, visitor parking, and transportation may be accessed at: &lt;a target="" href="/FDAgov/AdvisoryCommittees/AboutAdvisoryCommittees/ucm408555.htm"&gt;Common Questions and Answers about FDA Advisory Committee Meetings&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its advisory committee meetings. Please visit our Web site at &lt;a target="" href="/FDAgov/AdvisoryCommittees/AboutAdvisoryCommittees/ucm111462.htm"&gt;Public Conduct During FDA Advisory Committee Meetings&lt;/a&gt; for procedures on public conduct during advisory committee meetings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5 U.S.C. app.2).&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
