<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;table id="schedule" border="0" cellspacing="0" summary="This table shows the date, time, and location of the meeting" cellpadding="2" style="width: 100%"&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th id="a1" bgcolor="#cccccc" align="left" style="width: 15%; vertical-align: top"&gt;Center&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a2" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" width="20%" align="left"&gt;Date&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a3" bgcolor="#cccccc" align="left" style="width: 25%; vertical-align: top"&gt;Time&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a4" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" width="40%" align="left"&gt;Location&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td headers="a1" style="width: 15%; vertical-align: top"&gt;CDRH&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" width="20%" headers="a2"&gt;December 12, 2014&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td headers="a3" style="width: 25%; vertical-align: top"&gt;8:00 a.m. - 6:00 p.m.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" width="40%" headers="a4"&gt;Holiday Inn Washington-College Park&lt;br /&gt;10000 Baltimore Ave.&lt;br /&gt;College Park, MD 20740&lt;br /&gt;1-800-315-2621 &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;p&gt;DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH AND HUMAN SERVICES&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Food and Drug Administration&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[Docket No. FDA-2014-N-0001]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Orthopaedic and Rehabilitation Devices Panel of the Medical Devices Advisory Committee; Notice of Meeting&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;AGENCY:&amp;nbsp; Food and Drug Administration, HHS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ACTION:&amp;nbsp; Notice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This notice announces a forthcoming meeting of a public advisory committee of the Food and Drug Administration (FDA).&amp;nbsp; The meeting will be open to the public.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Name of Committee&lt;/u&gt;:&amp;nbsp; Orthopaedic and Rehabilitation Devices Panel of the Medical Devices Advisory Committee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;General Function of the Committee&lt;/u&gt;:&amp;nbsp; To provide advice and recommendations to the Agency on FDA's regulatory issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Date and Time&lt;/u&gt;:&amp;nbsp; The meeting will be held on December 12, 2014, from 8 a.m. to 6 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Location&lt;/u&gt;:&amp;nbsp; Holiday Inn Washington-College Park, 10000 Baltimore Ave., College Park, MD 20740. The hotel phone number is 1-800-315-2621.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Contact Person&lt;/u&gt;:&amp;nbsp; S.J. Anderson, Center for Devices and Radiological Health, Food and Drug Administration, 10903 New Hampshire Ave., Bldg. 66, rm. 1643, Silver Spring MD 20993-0002, &lt;a href="mailto:Sara.Anderson@fda.hhs.gov"&gt;Sara.Anderson@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/a&gt;, 301-796-7047, or FDA Advisory Committee Information Line, 1-800-741-8138 (301-443-0572 in the Washington, DC area).&amp;nbsp; A notice in the Federal Register about last minute modifications that impact a previously announced advisory committee meeting cannot always be published quickly enough to provide timely notice.&amp;nbsp; Therefore, you should always check the Agency's Web site at &lt;a href="http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/default.htm"&gt;http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/default.htm&lt;/a&gt; and scroll down to the appropriate advisory committee meeting link, or call the advisory committee information line to learn about possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Agenda&lt;/u&gt;:&amp;nbsp; On December 12, 2014, the committee will discuss, make recommendations, and vote on information regarding the premarket approval application for the Superion InterSpinous Spacer device sponsored by Vertiflex Incorporated.&amp;nbsp; The proposed Indication for Use for the Superion InterSpinous Spacer device, as stated in the PMA, is as follows:&amp;nbsp; the Superion InterSpinous Spacer (the Superion ISS) is intended to treat skeletally mature patients suffering from pain, numbness, and/or cramping in the legs (neurogenic intermittent claudication) secondary to a diagnosis of moderate lumbar spinal stenosis, with or without Grade 1 spondylolisthesis, confirmed by X-ray, MRI and/or CT evidence of thickened ligamentum flavum, narrowed lateral recess, and/or central canal or foraminal narrowing. The Superion ISS is indicated for those patients with impaired physical function who experience relief in flexion from symptoms of leg/buttock/groin pain, numbness, and/or cramping, with or without back pain. The Superion ISS may be implanted at one or two adjacent lumbar (L) levels in patients in whom treatment is indicated at no more than two levels, from L1 to L5.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting.&amp;nbsp; If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA's Web site after the meeting.&amp;nbsp; Background material is available at &lt;a href="http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/CommitteesMeetingMaterials/MedicalDevices/MedicalDevicesAdvisoryCommittee/default.htm"&gt;http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/CommitteesMeetingMaterials/MedicalDevices/MedicalDevicesAdvisoryCommittee/default.htm&lt;/a&gt;. Scroll down to the appropriate advisory committee meeting link.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Procedure&lt;/u&gt;:&amp;nbsp; Interested persons may present data, information, or views, orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committee.&amp;nbsp; Written submissions may be made to the contact person on or before November 13, 2014.&amp;nbsp; Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled between approximately 1 p.m. and 2 p.m. on December 12, 2014.&amp;nbsp; Those individuals interested in making formal oral presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before November 5, 2014. Time allotted for each presentation may be limited.&amp;nbsp; If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session.&amp;nbsp; The contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by November 6, 2014.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Persons attending FDA's advisory committee meetings are advised that the Agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical disabilities or special needs. If you require special accommodations due to a disability, please contact AnnMarie Williams, at 301-796-5966. &lt;a href="mailto:Annmarie.williams@fda.hhs.gov"&gt;Annmarie.williams@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/a&gt; at least 7 days in advance of the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its advisory committee meetings.&amp;nbsp; Please visit our Web site at &lt;a href="http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/AboutAdvisoryCommittees/ucm111462.htm"&gt;http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/AboutAdvisoryCommittees/ucm111462.htm&lt;/a&gt; for procedures on public conduct during advisory committee meetings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5 U.S.C. app. 2).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dated: September 16, 2014.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jill Hartzler Warner,&lt;br /&gt;Associate Commissioner for Special Medical Programs.&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
