<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;div class="table-responsive"&gt;&lt;table class="table" border="0" cellspacing="0" summary="This table shows the date, time, and location of the meeting" cellpadding="2" sizcache="12" sizset="0" style="width: 643px; height: 146px"&gt;&lt;tbody sizcache="11" sizset="0"&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th id="a1" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" align="left" style="width: 71px"&gt;Center&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a2" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" align="left" style="width: 158px"&gt;Date&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a3" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" align="left" style="width: 172px"&gt;Time&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a4" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" align="left" style="width: 238px"&gt;Location&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td valign="top" headers="a1" style="width: 71px; height: 127px"&gt;CDER&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" headers="a2" style="width: 158px; height: 127px"&gt;June 17, 2015&lt;br /&gt;June 18, 2015&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" headers="a3" style="width: 172px; height: 127px"&gt;8:30 a.m. to 5:00 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;8:30 a.m. to 11:30 a.m.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" headers="a4" style="width: 238px; height: 128px"&gt;FDA White Oak Campus&lt;br /&gt;10903 New Hampshire Avenue&lt;br /&gt;Building 31 Conference Center&lt;br /&gt;The Great Room (Rm. 1503)&lt;br /&gt;Silver Spring, Maryland&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Agenda&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 1em 0px"&gt;On June 17, 2015, during the morning session, the committee will receive updates on certain issues to follow up on discussions from the last meeting including the options for obtaining access to investigational new drugs and the processes FDA plans to use to add or remove drugs from the section 503A bulk drug substances list.&amp;nbsp;During this session, the committee will also discuss revisions FDA is considering to the list of drug products that may not be compounded under the exemptions provided by the FD&amp;amp;C Act because the drug products have been withdrawn or removed from the market because such drug products or components of such drug products have been found to be unsafe or not effective.&amp;nbsp;The list of those drug products is currently codified at 21 CFR 216.24.&amp;nbsp;FDA now is considering whether to amend the rule to add four more drugs to the list:&amp;nbsp;Aprotinin, ondansetron hydrochloride, bromocriptine mesylate, and acetaminophen.&amp;nbsp;As previously explained in the Federal Register of July 2, 2014 (79 FR 37687 at 37689 through 37690), the list may specify that a drug may not be compounded in any form, or, alternatively, may expressly exclude a particular formulation, indication, dosage form, or route of administration from an entry on the list because an approved drug containing the same active ingredient(s) has not been withdrawn or removed from the market.&amp;nbsp;Moreover, a drug may be listed only with regard to certain formulations, indications, routes of administration, or dosage forms because it has been found to be unsafe or not effective in those particular formulations, indications, routes of administration, or dosage forms.&amp;nbsp;FDA plans to seek the committee&amp;rsquo;s advice concerning the inclusion of these products.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 1em 0px"&gt;On June 17, 2015, during the afternoon session, the committee will discuss four bulk drug substances nominated for inclusion on the section 503A bulk drug substances list.&amp;nbsp;FDA intends to discuss the following nominated bulk drug substances:&amp;nbsp;Brilliant Blue G, tranilast, N-acetyl-D-glucosamine, and oxitriptan.&amp;nbsp;The nominators of these substances will be invited to make a short presentation supporting the nomination.&amp;nbsp;Other nominated substances will be discussed at future committee meetings. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div&gt;During the morning session on June 18, 2015, the committee will discuss the criteria FDA is proposing to use to evaluate drug products or categories of drug products for identification as demonstrably difficult to compound.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Meeting Materials&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 1em 0px"&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting. If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA&amp;rsquo;s Web site after the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Background Material&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul sizcache="1" sizset="43"&gt;&lt;li sizcache="1" sizset="43"&gt;&lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM431285')--]"&gt;2015 Meeting Materials, Pharmacy Compounding Advisory Committee&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Public Participation Information&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 1em 0px"&gt;Interested persons may present data, information, or views, orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul sizcache="5" sizset="27"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Written submissions may be made to the contact person on or before June 9, 2015.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled between approximately 11:00 a.m. to 11:15 a.m. and 3:45 p.m. to 4:00 p.m. on June 17, 2015 and between approximately 9:15 a.m. to 9:45 a.m.&amp;nbsp;on June 18, 2015.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 1em 0px"&gt;Those individuals interested in making formal oral presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before June 4, 2015.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 1em 0px"&gt;Time allotted for each presentation may be limited. If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session. The contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by June 8, 2015.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Webcast Information&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 1em 0px"&gt;CDER plans to provide a free of charge, live webcast of the June 17-18, 2015 meeting of the Pharmacy Compounding Advisory Committee. While CDER is working to make webcasts available to the public for all advisory committee meetings held at the White Oak campus, there are instances where the webcast transmission is not successful; staff will work to re-establish the transmission as soon as possible. Further information regarding the webcast, including the web address for the webcast, will be made available at least 2 days in advance of the meeting at the following website: &lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM431285')--]"&gt;2015 Meeting Materials, Pharmacy Compounding Advisory Committee&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CDER plans to post archived webcasts after the meeting, however, in cases where transmission was not successful, archived webcasts will not be available.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Contact Information&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul sizcache="1" sizset="45"&gt;&lt;li sizcache="1" sizset="45"&gt;Jayne E. Peterson, B.S. Pharm., J.D.&lt;br /&gt;Center for Drug Evalulation and Research&lt;br /&gt;Food and Drug Administration&lt;br /&gt;10903 New Hampshire Avenue&lt;br /&gt;WO31-2417&lt;br /&gt;Silver Spring, Maryland 20993-0002&lt;br /&gt;Telephone: (301) 796-9001&lt;br /&gt;Fax: (301) 847-8533&lt;br /&gt;E-mail: &lt;a href="mailto:PCAC@fda.hhs.gov"&gt;PCAC@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul sizcache="5" sizset="30"&gt;&lt;li&gt;FDA Advisory Committee Information Line&lt;br /&gt;1-800-741-8138 (301-443-0572 in the Washington DC area)&lt;br /&gt;Please call the Information Line for up-to-date information on this meeting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 1em 0px"&gt;A notice in the Federal Register about last minute modifications that impact a previously announced advisory committee meeting cannot always be published quickly enough to provide timely notice. Therefore, you should always check the agency&amp;rsquo;s Web site and call the appropriate advisory committee hot line/phone line to learn about possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 1em 0px"&gt;Persons attending FDA&amp;rsquo;s advisory committee meetings are advised that the agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets. FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical disabilities or special needs. If you require special accommodations due to a disability, please contact Jayne Peterson at (301) 796-9001 at least 7 days in advance of the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 1em 0px"&gt;Information regarding ground transportation, airport information, lodging, driving directions and visitor parking, and security can be accessed at: &lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM241740')--]"&gt;Public Meetings at the FDA White Oak Campus&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 1em 0px"&gt;FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its advisory committee meetings. Please visit our Web site at: &lt;a target="" href="http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/AboutAdvisoryCommittees/ucm111462.htm"&gt;Public Conduct During FDA Advisory Committee Meetings&lt;/a&gt; for procedures on public conduct during advisory committee meetings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 1em 0px"&gt;Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5 U.S.C. app.2).&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
