<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UPDATED INFORMATION&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Agenda portion has been changed for the April 15, 2015 Meeting of the Cardiovascular and Renal Drugs Advisory Committee. There are no other changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Agenda portion is changed to read as follows: &lt;br /&gt;The committee will discuss the new drug application (NDA) 204958, cangrelor injection, submitted by The Medicines Company, for the proposed indication of reduction of thrombotic cardiovascular events in patients with coronary artery disease (CAD) undergoing percutaneous coronary intervention (PCI)--(PCI refers to the opening of narrowed blood vessels supplying the heart muscle by a balloon inserted through an artery puncture with or without a stent) who have not received an oral P2Y12 inhibitor prior to the PCI procedure and in whom oral therapy with P2Y12 inhibitors is not feasible or desirable (P2Y12 is a protein involved in blood clotting. Inhibiting this protein is a key mechanism of action of cangrelor).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ORIGINAL INFORMATION&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="table-responsive"&gt;&lt;table class="table" border="0" cellspacing="0" summary="This table shows the date, time, and location of the meeting" cellpadding="2" sizcache="12" sizset="0" style="width: 643px; height: 146px"&gt;&lt;tbody sizcache="11" sizset="0"&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th id="a1" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" align="left" style="width: 71px"&gt;Center&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a2" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" align="left" style="width: 158px"&gt;Date&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a3" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" align="left" style="width: 172px"&gt;Time&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a4" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" align="left" style="width: 238px"&gt;Location&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td valign="top" headers="a1" style="width: 71px; height: 127px"&gt;CDER&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" headers="a2" style="width: 158px; height: 127px"&gt;April 15, 2015&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" headers="a3" style="width: 172px; height: 127px"&gt;8:00 a.m. to 4:00 p.m.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" headers="a4" style="width: 238px; height: 128px"&gt;FDA White Oak Campus&lt;br /&gt;10903 New Hampshire Avenue&lt;br /&gt;Building 31 Conference Center&lt;br /&gt;The Great Room (Rm. 1503)&lt;br /&gt;Silver Spring, Maryland&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Agenda&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 1em 0px"&gt;The committee will discuss the new drug application (NDA) 204958 cangrelor injection, submitted by The Medicines Company for the proposed indication of reduction of thrombotic cardiovascular events including stent thrombosis (events related to blood clots in a stent, a device inserted to keep the artery open) in patients with coronary artery disease (CAD) undergoing percutaneous coronary intervention (PCI). PCI refers to the opening of narrowed blood vessels supplying the heart muscle by a balloon inserted through an artery puncture with or without a stent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Meeting Materials&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 1em 0px"&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting. If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA&amp;rsquo;s Web site after the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Background Material&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul sizcache="1" sizset="43"&gt;&lt;li sizcache="1" sizset="43"&gt;&lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM436189')--]"&gt;2015 Meeting Materials, Cardiovascular and Renal Drugs Advisory Committee&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Public Participation Information&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 1em 0px"&gt;Interested persons may present data, information, or views, orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul sizcache="5" sizset="27"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Written submissions may be made to the contact person on or before April 1, 2015.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled between approximately 1:00 p.m. to 2:00 p.m. on April 15, 2015. Those individuals interested in making formal oral presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before March 24, 2015.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 1em 0px"&gt;Time allotted for each presentation may be limited. If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session. The contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by March 25, 2015.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Webcast Information&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 1em 0px"&gt;CDER plans to provide a free of charge, live webcast of the April 15, 2015, meeting of the Cardiovascular and Renal Drugs Advisory Committee. While CDER is working to make webcasts available to the public for all advisory committee meetings held at the White Oak campus, there are instances where the webcast transmission is not successful; staff will work to re-establish the transmission as soon as possible. Further information regarding the webcast, including the web address for the webcast, will be made available at least 2 days in advance of the meeting at the following website: &lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM436189')--]"&gt;2015 Meeting Materials, Cardiovascular and Renal Drugs Advisory Committee&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 1em 0px"&gt;CDER plans to post archived webcasts after the meeting, however, in cases where transmission was not successful, archived webcasts will not be available.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Contact Information&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul sizcache="1" sizset="45"&gt;&lt;li sizcache="1" sizset="45"&gt;Kristina A. Toliver, PharmD&lt;br /&gt;Center for Drug Evalulation and Research&lt;br /&gt;Food and Drug Administration&lt;br /&gt;10903 New Hampshire Avenue&lt;br /&gt;WO31-2417&lt;br /&gt;Silver Spring, Maryland 20993-0002&lt;br /&gt;Telephone: (301) 796-9001&lt;br /&gt;Fax: (301) 847-8533&lt;br /&gt;E-mail: &lt;a href="mailto:CRDAC@fda.hhs.gov"&gt;CRDAC@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul sizcache="5" sizset="30"&gt;&lt;li&gt;FDA Advisory Committee Information Line&lt;br /&gt;1-800-741-8138&lt;br /&gt;(301-443-0572 in the Washington DC area)&lt;br /&gt;Please call the Information Line for up-to-date information on this meeting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 1em 0px"&gt;A notice in the Federal Register about last minute modifications that impact a previously announced advisory committee meeting cannot always be published quickly enough to provide timely notice. Therefore, you should always check the agency&amp;rsquo;s Web site and call the FDA Advisory Committee Information Line to learn about possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 1em 0px"&gt;Persons attending FDA&amp;rsquo;s advisory committee meetings are advised that the agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets. FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical disabilities or special needs. If you require special accommodations due to a disability, please contact Kristina Toliver at (301) 796-9001 at least 7 days in advance of the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 1em 0px"&gt;Answers to commonly asked questions including information regarding special accommodations due to a disability, visitor parking, and transportation may be accessed at: &lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM408555')--]"&gt;Common Questions and Answers about FDA Advisory Committee Meetings&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 1em 0px"&gt;FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its advisory committee meetings. Please visit our Web site at &lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM111462')--]"&gt;Public Conduct During FDA Advisory Committee Meetings&lt;/a&gt; for procedures on public conduct during advisory committee meetings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="margin: 1em 0px"&gt;Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5 U.S.C. app.2).&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
