<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;div class="table-responsive"&gt;&lt;table class="table table-bordered" summary="This table shows the date, time, and location of the meeting"&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;thead&gt;&lt;tr class="text-center" style="background-color: #dddddd"&gt;&lt;th id="a1"&gt;Center&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a2"&gt;Date&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a3"&gt;Time&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a4"&gt;Location&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td headers="a1"&gt;NCTR&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td headers="a2"&gt;November 6, 2014&lt;br /&gt;November 7, 2014&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td headers="a3"&gt;8:15 a.m. -&amp;nbsp;4:15 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;8:00 a.m. - 2:00 p.m.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td headers="a4"&gt;&lt;p&gt;NCTR SAB&lt;br /&gt;3900 NCTR Rd.&lt;br /&gt;Conference Room B-12&lt;br /&gt;Jeferson, AR 72079&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Agenda&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;On November 6, 2014, the NCTR Director will welcome the participants and provide a Center-wide update on scientific initiatives and accomplishments during the past year. The SAB will be presented with an overview of the Division of Microbiology Subcommittee and the Subcommittee Site Visit Report. Following the public session, the SAB will hear an update from each of NCTR's research Divisions, the Office of Science Coordination, followed by an update on NCTR's Global Interactions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;On November 7, 2014, the Office of the Chief Scientist will update the SAB on their research needs, and discuss opportunities for collaboration to help address these needs, followed by a report from the National Toxicology Program of the National Institutes of Environmental Health Sciences on current and future collaboration.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Center for Biological Evaluation and Research, the Center for Drug Evaluation and Research, the Center for Devices and Radiological Health, the Center for Veterinary Medicine, the Center for Tobacco Products, the Office of Regulatory Affairs, and the Center for Food Safety and Applied Nutrition will each briefly discuss their Center- specific research strategic needs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Following an open discussion of all the information presented, the &lt;br /&gt;open session of the meeting will close so that SAB members can discuss &lt;br /&gt;personnel issues at NCTR.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Meeting Materials&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no &lt;br /&gt;later than 2 business days before the meeting. If FDA is unable to post &lt;br /&gt;the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the &lt;br /&gt;background material will be made publicly available at the location of &lt;br /&gt;the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be &lt;br /&gt;posted on FDA's Web site after the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Background material&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM379827')--]"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;font color="#0066cc"&gt;November 2014 Meeting Materials&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Procedure&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interested persons may present data, information, or views, orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committee. Written submissions may be made to the contact person on or before October 30, 2014. Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled between approximately 12 noon to 1 p.m. on November 6, 2014. Those individuals interested in making formal oral presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before October 22, 2014. Time allotted for each presentation may be limited. If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing &lt;br /&gt;session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session. The contact person will notify nterested persons regarding their request to speak by October 23, 2014.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Closed Committee Deliberations&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;On November 7, 2014, from 12 noon &lt;br /&gt;to 2 p.m., the meeting will be closed to permit discussion where disclosure would constitute a clearly unwarranted invasion of personal privacy (5 U.S.C. 552b(c)(6)). This portion of the meeting will be closed to permit discussion of information concerning individuals associated with the research programs at NCTR.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Persons attending FDA's advisory committee meetings are advised that the Agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical disabilities or special needs. If you require special accommodations due to a disability, please contact Donna Mendrick at least 7 days in advance of the meeting.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Contact Information&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Donna Mendrick&lt;br /&gt;Food and Drug Administration&lt;br /&gt;10903 New Hampshire Ave.&lt;br /&gt;Bldg. 32, Room 2208&lt;br /&gt;Silver Spring, Maryland 20993-0002&lt;br /&gt;Phone: 301-796-8892&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
