<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;table id="schedule" border="0" cellspacing="0" summary="This table shows the date, time, and location of the meeting" cellpadding="2" style="width: 100%"&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th id="a1" bgcolor="#cccccc" align="left" style="width: 15%; vertical-align: top"&gt;Center&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a2" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" width="20%" align="left"&gt;Date&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a3" bgcolor="#cccccc" align="left" style="width: 25%; vertical-align: top"&gt;Time&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a4" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" width="40%" align="left"&gt;Location&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td headers="a1" style="width: 15%; vertical-align: top"&gt;CDRH&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" width="20%" headers="a2"&gt;November 14, 2014&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td headers="a3" style="width: 25%; vertical-align: top"&gt;8:00 a.m. - 6:00 p.m.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td valign="top" width="40%" headers="a4"&gt;Hilton Washington D.C. North/Gaithersburg&lt;br /&gt;Montgomery Ballroom&lt;br /&gt;620 Perry Pkwy.&lt;br /&gt;Gaithersburg, MD 20877&lt;br /&gt;301-977-8900 &lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;p&gt;DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH AND HUMAN SERVICES&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Food and Drug Administration&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[Docket No. FDA-2014-N-0001]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ophthalmic Devices Panel of the Medical Devices Advisory Committee; Notice of Meeting&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;AGENCY:&amp;nbsp; Food and Drug Administration, HHS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ACTION:&amp;nbsp; Notice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This notice announces a forthcoming meeting of a public advisory committee of the Food and Drug Administration (FDA).&amp;nbsp; The meeting will be open to the public.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Name of Committee&lt;/u&gt;:&amp;nbsp; Ophthalmic Devices Panel of the Medical Devices Advisory Committee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;General Function of the Committee&lt;/u&gt;:&amp;nbsp; To provide advice and recommendations to the Agency on FDA's regulatory issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Date and Time&lt;/u&gt;:&amp;nbsp; The meeting will be held on November 14, 2014, from 8 a.m. to 6 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Location&lt;/u&gt;: Hilton Washington D.C. North/Gaithersburg, Montgomery Ballroom, 620 Perry Pkwy., Gaithersburg, MD 20877.&amp;nbsp; The hotel's telephone number is 301-977-8900.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Contact Person&lt;/u&gt;:&amp;nbsp; Natasha Facey, Center for Devices and Radiological Health, Food and Drug Administration, 10903 New Hampshire Ave., Bldg. 66, rm. 1552, Silver Spring, MD 20993, 301-796-5290, &lt;a href="mailto:Natasha.Facey@fda.hhs.gov"&gt;Natasha.Facey@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/a&gt;, or FDA Advisory Committee Information Line, 1-800-741-8138 (301-443-0572 in the Washington, DC area).&amp;nbsp; A notice in the Federal Register about last minute modifications that impact a previously announced advisory committee meeting cannot always be published quickly enough to provide timely notice.&amp;nbsp; Therefore, you should always check the Agency's Web site at &lt;a href="http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/default.htm"&gt;http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/default.htm&lt;/a&gt; and scroll down to the appropriate advisory committee meeting link, or call the advisory committee information line to learn about possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Agenda&lt;/u&gt;:&amp;nbsp; On November 14, 2014, the committee will discuss, make recommendations, and vote on information related to the premarket approval application for the AcrySof&amp;reg; IQ ReSTOR&amp;reg; Multifocal Toric Posterior Chamber Intraocular Lens submitted by applicant Alcon Laboratories, Inc.&amp;nbsp; This intraocular lens combines the optical properties of a +3 diopter multifocal intraocular lens with the optical properties of a toric intraocular lens.&amp;nbsp; The proposed indication for use is:&amp;nbsp; The AcrySof&amp;reg; IQ ReSTOR&amp;reg; Multifocal Toric Posterior Chamber Intraocular Lens (IOL) are intended for primary implantation for the visual correction of aphakia and pre-existing astigmatism secondary to removal of a cataractous lens in adult patients with and without presbyopia, who desire near, intermediate and distance vision, reduction of residual refractive cylinder, and increased spectacle independence.&amp;nbsp; The lens is intended to be placed in the capsular bag.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting.&amp;nbsp; If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA's Web site after the meeting.&amp;nbsp; Background material is available at &lt;a href="http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/CommitteesMeetingMaterials/MedicalDevices/MedicalDevicesAdvisoryCommittee/default.htm"&gt;http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/CommitteesMeetingMaterials/MedicalDevices/MedicalDevicesAdvisoryCommittee/default.htm&lt;/a&gt;. Scroll down to the appropriate advisory committee meeting link.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Procedure&lt;/u&gt;:&amp;nbsp; Interested persons may present data, information, or views, orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committee.&amp;nbsp; Written submissions may be made to the contact person on or before November 10, 2014.&amp;nbsp; Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled between approximately 1 p.m. and 2 p.m.&amp;nbsp; Those individuals interested in making formal oral presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before October 30, 2014.&amp;nbsp; Time allotted for each presentation may be limited.&amp;nbsp; If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session.&amp;nbsp; The contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by November 3, 2014.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Persons attending FDA's advisory committee meetings are advised that the Agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical disabilities or special needs. If you require special accommodations due to a disability, please contact James Clark at &lt;a href="mailto:James.Clark@fda.hhs.gov"&gt;James.Clark@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/a&gt; or 301-796-5293 at least 7 days in advance of the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its advisory committee meetings.&amp;nbsp; Please visit our Web site at &lt;a href="http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/AboutAdvisoryCommittees/ucm111462.htm"&gt;http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/AboutAdvisoryCommittees/ucm111462.htm&lt;/a&gt; for procedures on public conduct during advisory committee meetings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5 U.S.C. app. 2).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Date:&amp;nbsp; September 22, 2014.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jill Hartzler Warner, &lt;br /&gt;Associate Commissioner for Special Medical Programs.&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
