<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UPDATED INFORMATION&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;The Agenda portion has been changed for the November 18, 2014 Drug Safety and Risk Management Advisory Committee meeting. There are no other changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Agenda portion is changed to add the dosage form, manufacturer, and indications for the product at issue and reads as follows:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Food and Drug Administration Amendments Act of 2007 requires FDA to bring, at least annually, one or more drugs with Risk Evaluation and Mitigation Strategies (REMS) with elements to assure safe use (ETASU) before its Drug Safety and Risk Management Advisory Committee (DSaRM).The Agency plans to discuss the risk management of eculizumab (SOLIRIS) injection, Alexion Pharmaceuticals, which is approved for (1) the treatment of patients with paroxysmal nocturnal hemoglobinuria to reduce hemolysis and (2) the treatment of patients with atypical hemolytic uremic syndrome to inhibit complement mediated thrombotic microangiopathy. The Agency will seek the committee&amp;rsquo;s comments as to whether the REMS with ETASU for this drug assures safe use, is not unduly burdensome to patient access to the drug, and to the extent practicable, minimizes the burden to the health care delivery system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="table-responsive"&gt;&lt;table class="table" border="0" cellspacing="0" summary="This table shows the date, time, and location of the meeting" cellpadding="2" sizcache="12" sizset="0" style="width: 643px"&gt;&lt;tbody sizcache="11" sizset="0"&gt;&lt;tr id="rrtr0"&gt;&lt;th id="a1" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" align="left" style="width: 71px"&gt;Center&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a2" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" align="left" style="width: 158px"&gt;Date&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a3" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" align="left" style="width: 172px"&gt;Time&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a4" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" align="left" style="width: 238px"&gt;Location&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr id="rrtr1"&gt;&lt;td id="rrtd0" height="61" valign="top" headers="a1" style="width: 71px"&gt;CDER&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td id="rrtd1" valign="top" headers="a2" style="width: 158px"&gt;November 18, 2014&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td id="rrtd2" valign="top" headers="a3" style="width: 172px"&gt;9:00 a.m. to 4:00 p.m..&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td id="rrtd3" valign="top" headers="a4" style="width: 238px"&gt;FDA White Oak Campus&lt;br /&gt;10903 New Hampshire Avenue&lt;br /&gt;Building 31 Conference Center&lt;br /&gt;The Great Room (Rm. 1503)&lt;br /&gt;Silver Spring, Maryland&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Agenda&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The committee will discuss the Food and Drug Administration Amendments Act of 2007 which requires FDA to bring, at least annually, one or more drugs with Risk Evaluation and Mitigation Strategies (REMS) with elements to assure safe use (ETASU) before the Drug Safety and Risk Management (DSaRM) Advisory Committee. The Agency plans to discuss the risk management of eculizumab (SOLIRIS). The Agency will seek public input whether the REMS with ETASU for this drug assures safe use of the drug, is not unduly burdensome on patient access to the drug, and to the extent practicable, minimizes the burden on the health care delivery system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Meeting Materials&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting. If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA&amp;rsquo;s Web site after the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Background Material&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul sizcache="1" sizset="43"&gt;&lt;li sizcache="1" sizset="43"&gt;&lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM380883')--]"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;font color="#0066cc"&gt;2014 Meeting Materials, Drug Safety and Risk Management Advisory Committee&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Public Participation Information&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interested persons may present data, information, or views, orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Written submissions may be made to the contact person on or before November 3, 2014.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled between approximately 1:00 p.m. to 2:00 p.m. on November 18, 2014. Those individuals interested in making formal oral presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before October 24, 2014.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Time allotted for each presentation may be limited. If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session. The contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by October 27, 2014.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Webcast Information&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p sizcache="1" sizset="44"&gt;CDER plans to provide a free of charge, live webcast of the November 18, 2014, meeting of the Drug Safety and Risk Management Advisory Committee. While CDER is working to make webcasts available to the public for all advisory committee meetings held at the White Oak campus, there are instances where the webcast transmission is not successful; staff will work to re-establish the transmission as soon as possible. Further information regarding the webcast, including the web address for the webcast, will be made available at least 2 days in advance of the meeting at the following website: &lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM380883')--]"&gt;&lt;font color="#005f9f"&gt;2014 Meeting Materials, Drug Safety and Risk Management Advisory Committee&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CDER plans to post archived webcasts after the meeting, however, in cases where transmission was not successful, archived webcasts will not be available.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Contact Information&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul sizcache="1" sizset="45"&gt;&lt;li sizcache="1" sizset="45"&gt;Kristina A. Toliver, PharmD&lt;br /&gt;Center for Drug Evaluation and Research&lt;br /&gt;Food and Drug Administration&lt;br /&gt;10903 New Hampshire Avenue&lt;br /&gt;WO31-2417&lt;br /&gt;Silver Spring, MD 20993-0002&lt;br /&gt;Phone: 301-796-9001&lt;br /&gt;Fax: 301-847-8533&lt;br /&gt;E-mail: &lt;a href="mailto:DSaRM@fda.hhs.gov"&gt;&lt;font color="#005f9f"&gt;DSaRM@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul sizcache="5" sizset="30"&gt;&lt;li&gt;FDA Advisory Committee Information Line&lt;br /&gt;1-800-741-8138&lt;br /&gt;(301-443-0572 in the Washington DC area)- follow the prompts to the desired center or product area&lt;br /&gt;Please call the Information Line for up-to-date information on this meeting.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;A notice in the Federal Register about last minute modifications that impact a previously announced advisory committee meeting cannot always be published quickly enough to provide timely notice. Therefore, you should always check the agency&amp;rsquo;s Web site and call the FDA Advisory Committee Information Line to learn about possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Persons attending FDA&amp;rsquo;s advisory committee meetings are advised that the agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets. FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical disabilities or special needs. If you require special accommodations due to a disability, please contact Kristina Toliver at (301) 796-9001 at least 7 days in advance of the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Information regarding ground transportation, airport information, lodging, driving directions and visitor parking, and security can be accessed at: &lt;a target="" href="http://wcms.fda.gov/FDAgov/AboutFDA/WorkingatFDA/BuildingsandFacilities/WhiteOakCampusInformation/ucm241740.htm"&gt;&lt;font color="#005f9f"&gt;Public Meetings at the FDA White Oak Campus.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its advisory committee meetings. Please visit our Web site at &lt;a target="" href="http://wcms.fda.gov/FDAgov/AdvisoryCommittees/AboutAdvisoryCommittees/ucm111462.htm"&gt;&lt;font color="#005f9f"&gt;Public Conduct During FDA Advisory Committee Meetings&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt; for procedures on public conduct during advisory committee meetings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5 U.S.C. app.2).&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
