<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UPDATED INFORMATION&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;/strong&gt;The Agenda and Public Participation Information portions have been changed for the October 21, 2014 Pulmonary-Allergy Drugs Advisory Committee meeting. There are no other changes.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The Agenda portion is changed to add age parameters for the indication and reads as follows:&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
The committee will discuss supplemental new drug application (sNDA) 203188, for ivacaftor oral tablets, submitted by Vertex Pharmaceuticals for the treatment of cystic fibrosis in patients 6 years and older with a R117H mutation in the cystic fibrosis transmembrane conductance regulator (CFTR) gene.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The Public Participation Information portion is changed to extend the deadlines for written submissions and notification of individuals interested in making formal oral presentations and reads as follows: Interested persons may present data, information, or views, orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committee.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;ul&gt;&#13;
    &lt;li&gt;Written submissions may be made to the contact person on or before October 16, 2014.&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
    &lt;li&gt;Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled between approximately 1:00 p.m. to 2:00 p.m. on October 21, 2014. Those individuals interested in making formal oral presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested to make the presentation on or before October 10, 2014.&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Time allotted for each presentation may be limited. If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session. The contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by October 14, 2014.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;hr /&gt;&#13;
&lt;h2&gt;ORIGINAL INFORMATION&lt;/h2&gt;&#13;
&lt;div class="table-responsive"&gt;&#13;
&lt;table class="table" border="0" cellspacing="0" summary="This table shows the date, time, and location of the meeting" cellpadding="2" sizset="0" sizcache="12" style="width: 643px"&gt;&#13;
    &lt;tbody sizset="0" sizcache="11"&gt;&#13;
        &lt;tr id="rrtr0"&gt;&#13;
            &lt;th id="a1" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" align="left" style="width: 71px"&gt;Center&lt;/th&gt;&#13;
            &lt;th id="a2" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" align="left" style="width: 158px"&gt;Date&lt;/th&gt;&#13;
            &lt;th id="a3" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" align="left" style="width: 172px"&gt;Time&lt;/th&gt;&#13;
            &lt;th id="a4" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" align="left" style="width: 238px"&gt;Location&lt;/th&gt;&#13;
        &lt;/tr&gt;&#13;
        &lt;tr id="rrtr1"&gt;&#13;
            &lt;td id="rrtd0" height="61" valign="top" headers="a1" style="width: 71px"&gt;CDER&lt;/td&gt;&#13;
            &lt;td id="rrtd1" valign="top" headers="a2" style="width: 158px"&gt;October 21, 2014&lt;/td&gt;&#13;
            &lt;td id="rrtd2" valign="top" headers="a3" style="width: 172px"&gt;8:00 a.m. to 4:00 p.m..&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
            &amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&#13;
            &lt;td id="rrtd3" valign="top" headers="a4" style="width: 238px"&gt;FDA White Oak Campus&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
            10903 New Hampshire Avenue&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
            Building 31 Conference Center&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
            The Great Room (Rm. 1503)&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
            Silver Spring, Maryland&lt;/td&gt;&#13;
        &lt;/tr&gt;&#13;
    &lt;/tbody&gt;&#13;
&lt;/table&gt;&#13;
&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;h2&gt;Agenda&lt;/h2&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The committee will discuss supplemental new drug application (sNDA) 203188, ivacaftor oral tablets, submitted by Vertex Pharmaceuticals Inc., for the treatment of cystic fibrosis in patients with an R117H mutation in the cystic fibrosis transmembrane conductance regulator (CFTR) gene.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;h2&gt;Meeting Materials&lt;/h2&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting. If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA&amp;rsquo;s Web site after the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;h2&gt;Background Material&lt;/h2&gt;&#13;
&lt;ul sizset="43" sizcache="1"&gt;&#13;
    &lt;li sizset="43" sizcache="1"&gt;&lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM380897')--]"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;font color="#0066cc"&gt;2014 Meeting Materials, Pulmonary-Allergy Drugs Advisory Committee&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Public Participation Information&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Interested persons may present data, information, or views, orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committee.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;ul&gt;&#13;
    &lt;li&gt;Written submissions may be made to the contact person on or before October 14, 2014.&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
    &lt;li&gt;Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled between approximately 1:00 p.m. to 2:00 p.m. on October 21, 2014. Those individuals interested in making formal oral presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before October 6, 2014.&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Time allotted for each presentation may be limited. If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session. The contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by October 7, 2014.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;h2&gt;Webcast Information&lt;/h2&gt;&#13;
&lt;p sizset="44" sizcache="1"&gt;CDER plans to provide a free of charge, live webcast of the October 21, 2014, meeting of the Pulmonary-Allergy Drugs Advisory Committee. While CDER is working to make webcasts available to the public for all advisory committee meetings held at the White Oak campus, there are instances where the webcast transmission is not successful; staff will work to re-establish the transmission as soon as possible. Further information regarding the webcast, including the web address for the webcast, will be made available at least 2 days in advance of the meeting at the following website: &lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM380897')--]"&gt;&lt;font color="#005f9f"&gt;2014 Meeting Materials, Pulmonary-Allergy Drugs Advisory Committee&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;CDER plans to post archived webcasts after the meeting, however, in cases where transmission was not successful, archived webcasts will not be available&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;h2&gt;Contact Information&lt;/h2&gt;&#13;
&lt;ul sizset="45" sizcache="1"&gt;&#13;
    &lt;li sizset="45" sizcache="1"&gt;Cindy Hong, PharmD&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
    Center for Drug Evaluation and Research&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
    Food and Drug Administration&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
    10903 New Hampshire Avenue&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
    WO31-2417&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
    Silver Spring, MD 20993-0002&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
    Phone: 301-796-9001&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
    Fax: 301-847-8533&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
    E-mail: &lt;a href="mailto:PADAC@fda.hhs.gov"&gt;&lt;font color="#005f9f"&gt;PADAC@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#13;
&lt;ul sizset="30" sizcache="5"&gt;&#13;
    &lt;li&gt;FDA Advisory Committee Information Line&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
    1-800-741-8138&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
    (301-443-0572 in the Washington DC area)- follow the prompts to the desired center or product area&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
    Please call the Information Line for up-to-date information on this meeting.&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;A notice in the Federal Register about last minute modifications that impact a previously announced advisory committee meeting cannot always be published quickly enough to provide timely notice. Therefore, you should always check the agency&amp;rsquo;s Web site and call the FDA Advisory Committee Information Line to learn about possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Persons attending FDA&amp;rsquo;s advisory committee meetings are advised that the agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets. FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical disabilities or special needs. If you require special accommodations due to a disability, please contact Cindy Hong at (301) 796-9001 at least 7 days in advance of the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Information regarding ground transportation, airport information, lodging, driving directions and visitor parking, and security can be accessed at: &lt;a target="" href="http://wcms.fda.gov/FDAgov/AboutFDA/WorkingatFDA/BuildingsandFacilities/WhiteOakCampusInformation/ucm241740.htm"&gt;&lt;font color="#005f9f"&gt;Public Meetings at the FDA White Oak Campus.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its advisory committee meetings. Please visit our Web site at &lt;a target="" href="http://wcms.fda.gov/FDAgov/AdvisoryCommittees/AboutAdvisoryCommittees/ucm111462.htm"&gt;&lt;font color="#005f9f"&gt;Public Conduct During FDA Advisory Committee Meetings&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt; for procedures on public conduct during advisory committee meetings.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5 U.S.C. app.2).&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
