<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;div class="table-responsive"&gt;&lt;table class="table table-bordered"&gt;&lt;thead&gt;&lt;tr style="background-color: #dddddd"&gt;&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Center&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Date&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Time&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th scope="col"&gt;Location&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;OC&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;November 20, 2014&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;8:30 a.m. -12:45 p.m.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Food and Drug Administration&lt;br /&gt;10903 New Hampshire Ave.&lt;br /&gt;Bldg. 31, Rm. 1503,&lt;br /&gt;Sections B and C&lt;br /&gt;Silver Spring, MD 20993-0002&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;For those unable to attend in person, the meeting will also be webcast. The link for the webcast is available at &lt;a target="_blank" href="[!--$ssExternalLink('UCM420341')--]"&gt;https://collaboration.fda.gov/scienceboard112014&lt;/a&gt;. Information regarding special accommodations due to a disability, visitor parking, and transportation may be accessed at &lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM241740')--]"&gt;Public Meetings at the FDA White Oak Campus&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Agenda&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;On November 20, 2014, the Science Board will be provided with progress reports from two subcommittees, the Commissioner&amp;rsquo;s Fellowship Program Evaluation subcommittee and the Science Moving Forward subcommittee. The Board will be asked to support the formation of a new subcommittee to evaluate the Office of Regulatory Affairs&amp;rsquo; current investments in the Food Emergency Response Network cooperative agreement program and funding for state laboratories to achieve International Organization for Standardization accreditation. The Board will also be asked to support the formation of a new subcommittee to evaluate the Centers of Excellence in Regulatory Science and Innovation program. A recipient of one of the fiscal year 2013 Scientific Achievement Awards (selected by the Board) will provide an overview of the activities for which the award was given.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meeting Materials&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA intends to make the complete background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting. If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA&amp;rsquo;s Web site after the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Background Material&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM381792')--]"&gt;2014 Meeting Materials, Science Board to the FDA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Public Participation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interested persons may present data, information, or views, orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committee.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Written submissions pertaining to the issues before the Board on November 20, 2014, may be made to the contact person on or before Thursday, November 13, 2014.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled between 12 p.m. and 12:30 p.m. on November 20, 2014. Those individuals interested in making formal oral presentations regarding topics discussed on November 20, 2014, should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before Wednesday, November, 5, 2014.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Time allotted for each presentation may be limited. If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session. The contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak at the November 20, 2014, meeting by Thursday, November 6, 2014.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Martha Monser&lt;br /&gt;Office of Chief Scientist&lt;br /&gt;Office of the Commissioner&lt;br /&gt;Food and Drug Administration&lt;br /&gt;White Oak Bldg 1, Room 3309&lt;br /&gt;10903 New Hampshire Ave.&lt;br /&gt;Silver Spring, Maryland 20993&lt;br /&gt;Phone: 301&amp;ndash;796-4627&lt;br /&gt;Fax: 301-847-3536&lt;br /&gt;E-mail: &lt;a href="mailto:martha.monser@fda.hhs.gov"&gt;martha.monser@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A notice in the &lt;em&gt;Federal Register&lt;/em&gt; about last minute modifications that impact a previously announced advisory committee meeting cannot always be published quickly enough to provide timely notice. Therefore, you should always check the Agency&amp;rsquo;s Web site at &lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM2005799')--]"&gt;http://www.fda.gov/AdvisoryCommittees/default.htm&lt;/a&gt; and scroll down to the appropriate advisory committee meeting link, or call the advisory committee information line to learn about possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;FDA Advisory Committee Information Line 1-800-741-8138&lt;br /&gt;(301-443-0572 in the Washington DC area) and follow the prompts to the desired center or product area.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Persons attending FDA&amp;rsquo;s advisory committee meetings are advised that the agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets. FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with physical disabilities or special needs. If you require special accommodations due to a disability, please contact Martha Monser at (301) 796-4627 at least 7 days in advance of the meeting. FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its advisory committee meetings. Please visit our Web site for &lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM111462')--]"&gt;procedures on public conduct during advisory committee meetings&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5 U.S.C. app.2).&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
