<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wcm:root xmlns:wcm="http://www.stellent.com/wcm-data/ns/8.0.0">
  <wcm:element name="MainContent">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UPDATED INFORMATION&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The start time, agenda and public participation information for the October 27, 2015 Pharmacy Compounding Advisory Committee (PCAC) meeting have changed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The drug quinacrine has been removed as a topic for discussion at this meeting and therefore the start time for the October 27, 2015 PCAC meeting &lt;strong&gt;has changed to 10:00 a.m&lt;/strong&gt;. The time should be updated to read: &amp;ldquo;10:00 a.m. to 5:30 p.m.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Agenda portion for the October 27, 2015 PCAC meeting is changed to read as follows:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On October 27, 2015, during the morning and afternoon sessions, the committee will discuss five bulk drug substances nominated for inclusion on the section 503A bulk drug substances list. FDA intends to discuss the following nominated bulk drug substances: Methylsulfonylmethane, curcumin, germanium sesquioxide, rubidium chloride, and deoxy-D-glucose. The nominators of these substances will be invited to make a short presentation supporting the nomination.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The public session for oral presentations scheduled for 9:45 a.m. to 10:00 a.m. on October 27, 2015 has been cancelled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are no changes for the October 28, 2015 PCAC meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ORIGINAL INFORMATION&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="table-responsive"&gt;&lt;table class="table table-bordered table-striped" border="1" cellspacing="0" summary="This table shows the date, time, and location of the meeting" cellpadding="2" sizset="0" sizcache="12" style="width: 643px"&gt;&lt;tbody sizset="0" sizcache="11"&gt;&lt;tr id="rrtr0"&gt;&lt;th id="a1" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" align="left" style="width: 71px"&gt;Center&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a2" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" align="left" style="width: 158px"&gt;Date&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a3" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" align="left" style="width: 172px"&gt;Time&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th id="a4" bgcolor="#cccccc" valign="top" align="left" style="width: 238px"&gt;Location&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr id="rrtr1"&gt;&lt;td id="rrtd0" height="61" valign="top" headers="a1" style="width: 71px"&gt;CDER&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td id="rrtd1" valign="top" headers="a2" style="width: 158px"&gt;October 27, 2015&lt;br /&gt;October 28, 2015&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td id="rrtd2" valign="top" headers="a3" style="width: 172px"&gt;8:00 a.m.to 5:30 p.m.&lt;br /&gt;8:30 a.m. to 4:45 p.m&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td id="rrtd3" valign="top" headers="a4" style="width: 238px"&gt;FDA White Oak Campus&lt;br /&gt;10903 New Hampshire Avenue&lt;br /&gt;Building 31 Conference Center&lt;br /&gt;The Great Room (Rm. 1503)&lt;br /&gt;Silver Spring, Maryland&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Agenda&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;On October 27, 2015, during the morning session, the committee will discuss a revision FDA is considering to the list of drug products that may not be compounded under the exemptions provided by the FD&amp;amp;C Act because the drug product has been withdrawn or removed from the market because such drug product or such components of drug products have been found to be unsafe or not effective. The list of those drug products is currently codified at 21 CFR 216.24. FDA now is considering whether to amend the regulation to add one more drug to the list: Quinacrine: All drug products containing quinacrine for intrauterine administration. As explained in the Federal Register of July 2, 2014, (79 FR 37687 at 37689 through 37690), the list may specify that a drug may not be compounded in any form, or, alternatively, may expressly exclude a particular formulation, indication, dosage form, or route of administration from an entry on the list because an approved drug containing the same active ingredient(s) has not been withdrawn or removed from the market. Moreover, a drug may be listed only with regard to certain formulations, indications, routes of administration, or dosage forms because it has been found to be unsafe or not effective in those particular formulations, indications, routes of administration, or dosage forms. FDA plans to seek the committee&amp;rsquo;s advice concerning the inclusion of this drug product.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On October 27, 2015, during the morning and afternoon sessions, the committee will discuss six bulk drug substances nominated for inclusion on the section 503A bulk drug substances list. FDA intends to discuss the following nominated bulk drug substances: Quinacrine hydrochloride, methylsulfonylmethane, curcumin, germanium sesquioxide, rubidium chloride, and deoxy-D-glucose. The nominators of these substances will be invited to make a short presentation supporting the nomination.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On October 28, 2015, during the morning and afternoon sessions, the committee will discuss four bulk drug substances nominated for inclusion on the section 503A bulk drug substances list. FDA intends to discuss the following nominated bulk drug substances: Alanyl-L-glutamine, glutaraldehyde, glycyrrhizin, and domperidone. Other nominated substances will be discussed at future committee meetings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Meeting Materials&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA intends to make background material available to the public no later than 2 business days before the meeting. If FDA is unable to post the background material on its Web site prior to the meeting, the background material will be made publicly available at the location of the advisory committee meeting, and the background material will be posted on FDA&amp;rsquo;s Web site after the meeting. Background material is available at: &lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM431285')--]"&gt;2015 Meeting Materials, Pharmacy Compounding Advisory Committee&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Public Participation Information&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interested persons may present data, information, or views, orally or in writing, on issues pending before the committee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Written submissions may be made to the contact person on or before October 13, 2015.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Oral presentations from the public will be scheduled between approximately 9:45 a.m. to 10:00 a.m., 1:30 p.m. to 1:45 p.m. and 4:15 p.m. to 4:30 p.m. on October 27, 2015, and between approximately 11:00 a.m. to 11:15 a.m. and 2:45 p.m.to 3:30 p.m. on October 28, 2015.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those individuals interested in making formal oral presentations should notify the contact person and submit a brief statement of the general nature of the evidence or arguments they wish to present, the names and addresses of proposed participants, and an indication of the approximate time requested to make their presentation on or before October 9, 2015.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Time allotted for each presentation may be limited. If the number of registrants requesting to speak is greater than can be reasonably accommodated during the scheduled open public hearing session, FDA may conduct a lottery to determine the speakers for the scheduled open public hearing session. The contact person will notify interested persons regarding their request to speak by October 13, 2015.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Webcast Information&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p sizset="44" sizcache="1"&gt;CDER plans to provide a free of charge, live webcast of the October 27-28, 2015, meeting of the Pharmacy Compounding Advisory Committee. While CDER is working to make webcasts available to the public for all advisory committee meetings held at the White Oak campus, there are instances where the webcast transmission is not successful; staff will work to re-establish the transmission as soon as possible. Further information regarding the webcast, including the web address for the webcast, will be made available at least 2 days in advance of the meeting at the following website: &lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM431285')--]"&gt;2015 Meeting Materials, Pharmacy Compounding Advisory Committee&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CDER plans to post archived webcasts after the meeting, however, in cases where transmission was not successful, archived webcasts will not be available&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Contact Information&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul sizset="45" sizcache="1"&gt;&lt;li sizset="45" sizcache="1"&gt;Cindy Hong, PharmD&lt;br /&gt;Center for Drug Evaluation and Research&lt;br /&gt;Food and Drug Administration&lt;br /&gt;10903 New Hampshire Avenue&lt;br /&gt;WO31-2417&lt;br /&gt;Silver Spring, MD 20993-0002&lt;br /&gt;Phone: 301-796-9001&lt;br /&gt;Fax: 301-847-8533&lt;br /&gt;E-mail: &lt;a href="mailto:PCAC@fda.hhs.gov"&gt;PCAC@fda.hhs.gov&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul sizset="30" sizcache="5"&gt;&lt;li&gt;FDA Advisory Committee Information Line&lt;br /&gt;1-800-741-8138&lt;br /&gt;(301-443-0572 in the Washington DC area)- follow the prompts to the desired center or product area&lt;br /&gt;Please call the Information Line for up-to-date information on this meeting.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;A notice in the Federal Register about last minute modifications that impact a previously announced advisory committee meeting cannot always be published quickly enough to provide timely notice. Therefore, you should always check the agency&amp;rsquo;s Web site and call the appropriate advisory committee hot line/phone line to learn about possible modifications before coming to the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Persons attending FDA&amp;rsquo;s advisory committee meetings are advised that the agency is not responsible for providing access to electrical outlets. FDA welcomes the attendance of the public at its advisory committee meetings and will make every effort to accommodate persons with disabilities. If you require accommodations due to a disability, please contact Cindy Hong at (301) 796-9001 at least 7 days in advance of the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Answers to commonly asked questions including information regarding special accommodations due to a disability, visitor parking, and transportation may be accessed at: &lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM408555')--]"&gt;Common Questions and Answers about FDA Advisory Committee Meetings&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FDA is committed to the orderly conduct of its advisory committee meetings. Please visit our Web site at &lt;a target="" href="[!--$wcmUrl('link','UCM111462')--]"&gt;Public Conduct During FDA Advisory Committee Meetings&lt;/a&gt; for procedures on public conduct during advisory committee meetings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Notice of this meeting is given under the Federal Advisory Committee Act (5 U.S.C. app.2).&lt;/p&gt;</wcm:element>
<wcm:element name="MainList1"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList2"></wcm:element>
  <wcm:element name="MainList3"></wcm:element>
</wcm:root>
